<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]2012[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1190080</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>2012</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Dr. Adrian Helmsley, part of a worldwide geophysical team investigating the effect on the earth of radiation from unprecedented solar storms, learns that the earth's core is heating up. He warns U.S. President Thomas Wilson that the crust of the earth is becoming unstable and that without proper preparations for saving a fraction of the world's population, the entire race is doomed. Meanwhile, writer Jackson Curtis stumbles on the same information. While the world's leaders race to build "arks" to escape the impending cataclysm, Curtis struggles to find a way to save his family. Meanwhile, volcanic eruptions and earthquakes of unprecedented strength wreak havoc around the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zaqam2RNscH5ooYFWInV6hjx6y5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pvxmYJcgrLiYC6G2IQTn1PPNems.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]300[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0416449</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>300</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Based on Frank Miller's graphic novel, "300" is very loosely based the 480 B.C. Battle of Thermopylae, where the King of Sparta led his army against the advancing Persians; the battle is said to have inspired all of Greece to band together against the Persians, and helped usher in the world's first democracy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9W49fy5G7v9Ed3CXtvMi41YqZtt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eGhjeUbzttA3E4flxdAm8gHz4h4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Aliens[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090605</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aliens</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Ripley's lifepod is found by a salvage crew over 50 years later, she finds that terra-formers are on the very planet they found the alien species. When the company sends a family of colonists out to investigate her story—all contact is lost with the planet and colonists. They enlist Ripley and the colonial marines to return and search for answers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r1x5JGpyqZU8PYhbs4UcrO1Xb6x.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jMBpJFRtrtIXymer93XLavPwI3P.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Armageddon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120591</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Armageddon</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When an asteroid threatens to collide with Earth, NASA honcho Dan Truman determines the only way to stop it is to drill into its surface and detonate a nuclear bomb. This leads him to renowned driller Harry Stamper, who agrees to helm the dangerous space mission provided he can bring along his own hotshot crew. Among them is the cocksure A.J. who Harry thinks isn't good enough for his daughter, until the mission proves otherwise.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eTM3qtGhDU8cvjpoa6KEt5E2auU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sODk4VuMTt8S56zYFOr1Kx8BFqu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Avatar[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0499549</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avatar</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the 22nd century, a paraplegic Marine is dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission, but becomes torn between following orders and protecting an alien civilization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jRXYjXNq0Cs2TcJjLkki24MLp7u.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8I37NtDffNV7AZlDa7uDvvqhovU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120611</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Daywalker known as "Blade" - a half-vampire, half-mortal man - becomes the protector of humanity against an underground army of vampires.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hx0sdduAsr4rq03RZKZzglR25z7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hZnnUq0mrUQ3e54SJVca4mf2oAQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Bloodsport[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0092675</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bloodsport</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>U.S. soldier Frank Dux has come to Hong Kong to be accepted into the Kumite, a highly secret and extremely violent martial arts competition. While trying to gain access into the underground world of clandestine fighters, he also has to avoid military officers who consider him to be AWOL. After enduring a difficult training and beginning a romance with journalist Janice Kent, Frank is given the opportunity to fight. But can he survive?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kndxR9TRK0kJ5hxzDprRSS80F2W.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tUb8CWB4k1dyAfzCt7N7jHvS3Y.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Cliffhanger[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106582</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Cliffhanger</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A year after losing his friend in a tragic 4,000-foot fall, former ranger Gabe Walker and his partner, Hal, are called to return to the same peak to rescue a group of stranded climbers, only to learn the climbers are actually thieving hijackers who are looking for boxes full of money.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8v2nPPLvhEVlfXu08UZ0djK31be.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yCOwgIIO0gYd7aEeyJ4oGM4h9Iy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Cloverfield[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1060277</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Cloverfield</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Five young New Yorkers throw their friend a going-away party the night that a monster the size of a skyscraper descends upon the city. Told from the point of view of their video camera, the film is a document of their attempt to survive the most surreal, horrifying event of their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qIegUGJqyMMCRjkKV1s7A9MqdJ8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6ms6RdNcQUAnjBY26aM85xC2wV0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Commando[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088944</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Commando</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>John Matrix, the former leader of a special commando strike force that always got the toughest jobs done, is forced back into action when his young daughter is kidnapped. To find her, Matrix has to fight his way through an array of punks, killers, one of his former commandos, and a fully equipped private army. With the help of a feisty stewardess and an old friend, Matrix has only a few hours to overcome his greatest challenge: finding his daughter before she's killed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ollPAAAgZ7euU8VisfqU3cuXhZ6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gvao0WZchzudp2oMF5sjgzwHY0q.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Conan the Barbarian[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0816462</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Conan the Barbarian</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A quest that begins as a personal vendetta for the fierce Cimmerian warrior soon turns into an epic battle against hulking rivals, horrific monsters, and impossible odds, as Conan realizes he is the only hope of saving the great nations of Hyboria from an encroaching reign of supernatural evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5Z7bmszrF0uQxilCC6bjrLo9u9H.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6B5bTuZEyLrAYNG1IX1GeBQZP11.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Constantine[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0360486</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Constantine</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>John Constantine has literally been to Hell and back. When he teams up with a policewoman to solve the mysterious suicide of her twin sister, their investigation takes them through the world of demons and angels that exists beneath the landscape of contemporary Los Angeles.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vPYgvd2MwHlxTamAOjwVQp4qs1W.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tIG8FwHRiHLOlWJdizp2oxdkSL2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Death Proof[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1028528</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Death Proof</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Austin's hottest DJ, Jungle Julia, sets out into the night to unwind with her two friends Shanna and Arlene. Covertly tracking their moves is Stuntman Mike, a scarred rebel leering from behind the wheel of his muscle car, revving just feet away.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vtu6H4NWnQVqEp3aanUq3hNeeot.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c7k9ZZb1MoFzJeyjphKRMLHOgqU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Death Race 2000[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0072856</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Death Race 2000</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a boorish future, the government sponsors a popular, but bloody, cross-country race in which points are scored by mowing down pedestrians. Five teams, each comprised of a male and female, compete using cars equipped with deadly weapons. Frankenstein, the mysterious returning champion, has become America's hero, but this time he has a passenger from the underground resistance.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zfk6wdv430Jj606dI4moiuOZ3wx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lYWZjOKSGSkRUYvoysZNrZ6JcmI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Death Wish[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0071402</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Death Wish</title>
	<year>1974</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After his wife is murdered by street punks, a pacifistic New York City architect becomes a one-man vigilante squad, prowling the streets for would-be muggers after dark.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rNksI6UiuTgLtBy69WvKT1PrG0R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AiNPLAT4ltKanMm0IKjbGG39SE0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Demolition Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106697</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Demolition Man</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Simon Phoenix, a violent criminal cryogenically frozen in 1996, escapes during a parole hearing in 2032 in the utopia of San Angeles. Police are incapable of dealing with his violent ways and turn to his captor, who had also been cryogenically frozen after being wrongfully accused of killing 30 innocent people while apprehending Phoenix.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pxWuGsyzVQSqHWxVQLy4XUcopIL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4pl165EUdvveHCr4J4YcHVA1MnD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Die Hard[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0095016</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>NYPD cop John McClane's plan to reconcile with his estranged wife is thrown for a serious loop when, minutes after he arrives at her office, the entire building is overtaken by a group of terrorists. With little help from the LAPD, wisecracking McClane sets out to single-handedly rescue the hostages and bring the bad guys down.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yFihWxQcmqcaBR31QM6Y8gT6aYV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rahJyvdMruvqUmSLWRQKYS57mx8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Die Hard 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0099423</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard 2</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Off-duty cop John McClane is gripped with a feeling of déjà vu when, on a snowy Christmas Eve in the nation’s capital, terrorists seize a major international airport, holding thousands of holiday travelers hostage. Renegade military commandos led by a murderous rogue officer plot to rescue a drug lord from justice and are prepared for every contingency except one: McClane’s smart-mouthed heroics.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aLPtvDbigpHIZVVLnBjjbl5J0sh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fgkgab4Rel0nOI3B3scHeNB4Mn6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Die Hard: With a Vengeance[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0112864</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard: With a Vengeance</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>New York detective John McClane is back and kicking bad-guy butt in the third installment of this action-packed series, which finds him teaming with civilian Zeus Carver to prevent the loss of innocent lives. McClane thought he'd seen it all, until a genius named Simon engages McClane, his new "partner" -- and his beloved city -- in a deadly game that demands their concentration.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lwTE6cUhGxRaJvQ5VPdletIGDPh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qk0A79253qOG8bStPIEN7VEXSij.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Edge of Tomorrow[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1631867</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Edge of Tomorrow</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Major Bill Cage is an officer who has never seen a day of combat when he is unceremoniously demoted and dropped into combat. Cage is killed within minutes, managing to take an alpha alien down with him. He awakens back at the beginning of the same day and is forced to fight and die again... and again - as physical contact with the alien has thrown him into a time loop.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xjw5trHV7Mwo61P0kCTy8paEkgO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4V1yIoAKPMRQwGBaSses8Bp2nsi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Enter the Dragon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0070034</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Enter the Dragon</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A martial artist agrees to spy on a reclusive crime lord using his invitation to a tournament there as cover.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zN7OOSARMLVzl9xJqkW2CcZ3xhY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6uChT8jRjTwcVo4X5pIUctsl1qN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Equilibrium[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0238380</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Equilibrium</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a dystopian future, a totalitarian regime maintains peace by subduing the populace with a drug, and displays of emotion are punishable by death. A man in charge of enforcing the law rises to overthrow the system.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yQuovle5Ov6q69XSdTNdH52eANc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/huZZBPyYUnMPCnrAFyJhnwYsQx9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Face/Off[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119094</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Face/Off</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In order to foil a terrorist plot, an FBI agent undergoes facial transplant surgery and assumes the identity of a criminal mastermind, who murdered his only son. The plan turns sour when the criminal wakes up prematurely and seeks revenge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/69Xzn8UdPbVnmqSChKz2RTpoNfB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yeIpgoZWzbNqkeSYPwhNZQ5xCRX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fight Club[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0137523</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fight Club</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A ticking-time-bomb insomniac and a slippery soap salesman channel primal male aggression into a shocking new form of therapy. Their concept catches on, with underground "fight clubs" forming in every town, until an eccentric gets in the way and ignites an out-of-control spiral toward oblivion.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pB8BM7pdSp6B6Ih7QZ4DrQ3PmJK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hZkgoQYus5vegHoetLkCJzb17zJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]First Blood[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083944</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>First Blood</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When former Green Beret John Rambo is harassed by local law enforcement and arrested for vagrancy, the Vietnam vet snaps, runs for the hills and rat-a-tat-tats his way into the action-movie hall of fame. Hounded by a relentless sheriff, Rambo employs heavy-handed guerilla tactics to shake the cops off his tail.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a9sa6ERZCpplbPEO7OMWE763CLD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hCxxOJojCUFyuahDx167glJgp7E.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]From Dusk Till Dawn[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116367</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>From Dusk Till Dawn</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Seth Gecko and his younger brother Richard are on the run after a bloody bank robbery in Texas. They escape across the border into Mexico and will be home-free the next morning, when they pay off the local kingpin. They just have to survive 'from dusk till dawn' at the rendezvous point, which turns out to be a Hell of a strip joint.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sV3kIAmvJ9tPz4Lq5fuf9LLMxte.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9JcMUzQy9gPqDmJJGH3AcL145mv.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Grindhouse[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0462322</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Grindhouse</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Two full-length feature horror movies written by Quentin Tarantino and Robert Rodriguez put together as a two-film feature. Including fake movie trailers in between both movies.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jl3K6T8Mridd2dWmcdBpKyHyt6Y.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zhNJ1SQwIh2EpTst9ofaAHRV2UL.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Hancock[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0448157</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hancock</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Hancock is a down-and-out superhero who's forced to employ a PR expert to help repair his image when the public grows weary of all the damage he's inflicted during his lifesaving heroics. The agent's idea of imprisoning the antihero to make the world miss him proves successful, but will Hancock stick to his new sense of purpose or slip back into old habits?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7DyuV2G0hLEqHeueDfOqhZ2DVut.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xh0ZRdnL4pSqfW73HBf97xiNEFP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Hard Target[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107076</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hard Target</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a woman's father goes missing, she enlists a local to aid in her search.  The pair soon discover that her father has died at the hands of a wealthy sportsman who hunts homeless men as a form of recreation.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kufvuQYWdl82sYzmhy2naBLyMui.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oSA2dPUhF3y1rlTG9CDgaqN0vYQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Highlander[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091203</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Highlander</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>He fought his first battle on the Scottish Highlands in 1536. He will fight his greatest battle on the streets of New York City in 1986. His name is Connor MacLeod. He is immortal.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8Z8dptJEypuLoOQro1WugD855YE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1S7uCBV4rvQR24kh0TldWhjLV3F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]I Am Legend[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0480249</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>I Am Legend</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Robert Neville is a scientist who was unable to stop the spread of the terrible virus that was incurable and man-made. Immune, Neville is now the last human survivor in what is left of New York City and perhaps the world. For three years, Neville has faithfully sent out daily radio messages, desperate to find any other survivors who might be out there. But he is not alone.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iPDkaSdKk2jRLTM65UOEoKtsIZ8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lhVVIWKR13khBvjFz8XyZ2GM0JS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]I, Robot[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0343818</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>I, Robot</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 2035, where robots are commonplace and abide by the three laws of robotics, a technophobic cop investigates an apparent suicide. Suspecting that a robot may be responsible for the death, his investigation leads him to believe that humanity may be in danger.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/efwv6F2lGaghjPpBRSINHtoEiZB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lOXVbF2mBK0xUt8sLInF3TIk5YS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Inception[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1375666</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Inception</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Cobb, a skilled thief who commits corporate espionage by infiltrating the subconscious of his targets is offered a chance to regain his old life as payment for a task considered to be impossible: "inception", the implantation of another person's idea into a target's subconscious.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/edv5CZvWj09upOsy2Y6IwDhK8bt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8ZTVqvKDQ8emSGUEMjsS4yHAwrp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Iron Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0371746</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Iron Man</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After being held captive in an Afghan cave, billionaire engineer Tony Stark creates a unique weaponized suit of armor to fight evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/78lPtwv72eTNqFW9COBYI0dWDJa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cyecB7godJ6kNHGONFjUyVN9OX5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Jurassic Park[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107290</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Jurassic Park</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A wealthy entrepreneur secretly creates a theme park featuring living dinosaurs drawn from prehistoric DNA. Before opening day, he invites a team of experts and his two eager grandchildren to experience the park and help calm anxious investors. However, the park is anything but amusing as the security systems go off-line and the dinosaurs escape.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oU7Oq2kFAAlGqbU4VoAE36g4hoI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1FN6pHFDDlhT7oVhABKKGtG6ga7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Jurassic World[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0369610</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Jurassic World</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Twenty-two years after the events of Jurassic Park, Isla Nublar now features a fully functioning dinosaur theme park, Jurassic World, as originally envisioned by John Hammond.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A0LZHXUzo5C60Oahvt7VxvwuzHw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aIGIYJTyOkEVUmEd3z5x6diYsFx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Kill Bill: Vol. 1[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0266697</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Kill Bill: Vol. 1</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An assassin is shot by her ruthless employer, Bill, and other members of their assassination circle – but she lives to plot her vengeance.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v7TaX8kXMXs5yFFGR41guUDNcnB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lVy5Zqcty2NfemqKYbVJfdg44rK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Kill Bill: Vol. 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0378194</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Kill Bill: Vol. 2</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Bride unwaveringly continues on her roaring rampage of revenge against the band of assassins who had tried to kill her and her unborn child. She visits each of her former associates one-by-one, checking off the victims on her Death List Five until there's nothing left to do … but kill Bill.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2yhg0mZQMhDyvUQ4rG1IZ4oIA8L.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/70EtzaGfO2d8X5n8SLI4s61KuJh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Looper[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1276104</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Looper</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the futuristic action thriller Looper, time travel will be invented but it will be illegal and only available on the black market. When the mob wants to get rid of someone, they will send their target 30 years into the past where a looper, a hired gun, like Joe is waiting to mop up. Joe is getting rich and life is good until the day the mob decides to close the loop, sending back Joe's future self for assassination.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sNjL6SqErDBE8OUZlrDLkexfsCj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8UiZP1dTIPRYkIcwR84zZTwgKpZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mad Max[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079501</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mad Max</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the ravaged near future, a savage motorcycle gang rules the road. Terrorizing innocent civilians while tearing up the streets, the ruthless gang laughs in the face ofa police force hell-bent on stopping them. But they underestimate one officer: Max Rockatansky. And when the bikers brutalize Max's best friend and family, they send him into a mad frenzy that leaves him with only one thing left in the world to live for – revenge!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LrI4GiCSrChgkdskVZiwv643Kg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uL5DoOuMho1QY7OK5IqacYH9QHK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mad Max: Fury Road[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1392190</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mad Max: Fury Road</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An apocalyptic story set in the furthest reaches of our planet, in a stark desert landscape where humanity is broken, and most everyone is crazed fighting for the necessities of life. Within this world exist two rebels on the run who just might be able to restore order.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8tZYtuWezp8JbcsvHYO0O46tFbo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nlCHUWjY9XWbuEUQauCBgnY8ymF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Men in Black 3[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1409024</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Men in Black 3</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Agents J and K are back...in time. J has seen some inexplicable things in his 15 years with the Men in Black, but nothing, not even aliens, perplexes him as much as his wry, reticent partner. But when K's life and the fate of the planet are put at stake, Agent J will have to travel back in time to put things right. J discovers that there are secrets to the universe that K never told him - secrets that will reveal themselves as he teams up with the young Agent K to save his partner, the agency, and the future of humankind.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/90DdoEStzeObs96fsYf4GG544iN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5AhpUb8CAP0jZ4Wrn7AsRUYjZxB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Midway[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6924650</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Midway</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The story of the Battle of Midway, and the leaders and soldiers who used their instincts, fortitude and bravery to overcome massive odds.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hj8pyoNnynGeJTAbl7jcLZO8Uhx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5xegGPhCSVMKbyh6zeT6Th0BWLB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Minority Report[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0181689</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Minority Report</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>John Anderton is a top 'Precrime' cop in the late-21st century, when technology can predict crimes before they're committed. But Anderton becomes the quarry when another investigator targets him for a murder charge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ccqpHq5tk5W4ymbSbuoy4uYOxFI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qq4H9JfBKQ5DarMLI6lhUQjn9D7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mission: Impossible - Fallout[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4912910</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When an IMF mission ends badly, the world is faced with dire consequences. As Ethan Hunt takes it upon himself to fulfill his original briefing, the CIA begin to question his loyalty and his motives. The IMF team find themselves in a race against time, hunted by assassins while trying to prevent a global catastrophe.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AkJQpZp9WoNdj7pLYSj1L0RcMMN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aw4FOsWr2FY373nKSxbpNi3fz4F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mission: Impossible - Ghost Protocol[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1229238</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mission: Impossible - Ghost Protocol</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Ethan Hunt and his team are racing against time to track down a dangerous terrorist named Hendricks, who has gained access to Russian nuclear launch codes and is planning a strike on the United States. An attempt to stop him ends in an explosion causing severe destruction to the Kremlin and the IMF to be implicated in the bombing, forcing the President to disavow them. No longer being aided by the government, Ethan and his team chase Hendricks around the globe, although they might still be too late to stop a disaster.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/psiWp3VTjznfokmGQG9uqiiknQQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hqyjzDRCs1N5gEsh2gklzPdsEFD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mortal Kombat[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0113855</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mortal Kombat</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For nine generations an evil sorcerer has been victorious in hand-to-hand battle against his mortal enemies. If he wins a tenth Mortal Kombat tournament, desolation and evil will reign over the multiverse forever. To save Earth, three warriors must overcome seemingly insurmountable odds, their own inner demons, and superhuman foes in this action/adventure movie based on one of the most popular video games of all time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fcK7tzSSXMYiMN8E9KlZJL1BYyp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eDg6HPCnQaUhTOdZB3LzJjpnGtT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mr. & Mrs. Smith[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0356910</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mr. & Mrs. Smith</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After five (or six) years of vanilla-wedded bliss, ordinary suburbanites John and Jane Smith are stuck in a huge rut. Unbeknownst to each other, they are both coolly lethal, highly-paid assassins working for rival organisations. When they discover they're each other's next target, their secret lives collide in a spicy, explosive mix of wicked comedy, pent-up passion, nonstop action and high-tech weaponry.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wzIO3ytxeSNt1wRpXLIdkNbGoDm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iFaWUETEE2umP1WY0LUAmjSpzm7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]No Time to Die[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2382320</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>No Time to Die</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bond has left active service and is enjoying a tranquil life in Jamaica. His peace is short-lived when his old friend Felix Leiter from the CIA turns up asking for help. The mission to rescue a kidnapped scientist turns out to be far more treacherous than expected, leading Bond onto the trail of a mysterious villain armed with dangerous new technology.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iUgygt3fscRoKWCV1d0C7FbM9TP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r2GAjd4rNOHJh6i6Y0FntmYuPQW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Olympus Has Fallen[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2302755</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Olympus Has Fallen</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the White House (Secret Service Code: "Olympus") is captured by a terrorist mastermind and the President is kidnapped, disgraced former Presidential guard Mike Banning finds himself trapped within the building. As the national security team scrambles to respond, they are forced to rely on Banning's inside knowledge to help retake the White House, save the President and avert an even bigger disaster.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ei2qjTiDpgKGuoSEntPCSAIhuvQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6u5WHyEzphjs8wAT3JGw9Dhv180.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pacific Rim[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1663662</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pacific Rim</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As war between humankind and monstrous sea creatures wages on, a former pilot and a trainee are paired up to drive a seemingly obsolete special weapon in a desperate effort to save the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8wo4eN8dWKaKlxhSvBz19uvj8gA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ig7qUy7drkEFZNCK7gi0hMn1WMN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Passenger 57[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0105104</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Passenger 57</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An infamous terrorist has evaded capture for a long time by being extremely clever and ruthless. Things get interesting when he hijacks a plane carrying famous security expert John Cutter, who isn't about to stand for this sort of thing.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4VBN8pQxGHjeZWcNv1V1xSw0OKC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LhJq6RA0v9BDlsO9W22ZxGBCnT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Phone Booth[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0183649</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Phone Booth</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A slick New York publicist who picks up a ringing receiver in a phone booth is told that if he hangs up, he'll be killed... and the little red light from a laser rifle sight is proof that the caller isn't kidding.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o9b4cA1USAUXz0oxwWVja7sMNFa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oBU55I99gZTRYag25Q5eJUKZeG6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pitch Black[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0134847</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pitch Black</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When their ship crash-lands on a remote planet, the marooned passengers soon learn that escaped convict Riddick isn't the only thing they have to fear. Deadly creatures lurk in the shadows, waiting to attack in the dark, and the planet is rapidly plunging into the utter blackness of a total eclipse. With the body count rising, the doomed survivors are forced to turn to Riddick with his eerie eyes to guide them through the darkness to safety. With time running out, there's only one rule: Stay in the light.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3AnlxZ5CZnhKKzjgFyY6EHxmOyl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mZGwhwIwYuF0G9XLS8j23dhNfUC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Planet of the Apes[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063442</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Planet of the Apes</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Astronaut Taylor crash lands on a distant planet ruled by apes who use a primitive race of humans for experimentation and sport. Soon Taylor finds himself among the hunted, his life in the hands of a benevolent chimpanzee scientist.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2r9iKnlSYEk4daQadsXfcjHfIjQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dQS3L3USI7Zhcq41abzMZF8dXCm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Point Break[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0102685</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Point Break</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In Los Angeles, a gang of bank robbers who call themselves The Ex-Presidents commit their crimes while wearing masks of Reagan, Carter, Nixon and Johnson. Believing that the members of the gang could be surfers, the F.B.I. sends young agent Johnny Utah to the beach undercover to mix with the surfers and gather information.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eGSfqknufcsXmM2Rb59H9SiNd4T.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yGOHbICOQwlJ20UjK8F2ChGJjvl.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Predator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093773</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Predator</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A team of elite commandos on a secret mission in a Central American jungle come to find themselves hunted by an extraterrestrial warrior.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k3mW4qfJo6SKqe6laRyNGnbB9n5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/YL3GPOiDcNraIJOVDCZsoOBoDy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rambo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0462499</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rambo</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When governments fail to act on behalf of captive missionaries, ex-Green Beret John James Rambo sets aside his peaceful existence along the Salween River in a war-torn region of Thailand to take action.  Although he's still haunted by violent memories of his time as a U.S. soldier during the Vietnam War, Rambo can hardly turn his back on the aid workers who so desperately need his help.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r8LPeldxskHrGJTPfhICguCip2H.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r60nF76y6Lw3A82Og9bdyRzuo1E.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rambo: First Blood Part II[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0089880</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rambo: First Blood Part II</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>John Rambo is released from prison by the government for a top-secret covert mission to the last place on Earth he'd want to return - the jungles of Vietnam.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pzPdwOitmTleVE3YPMfIQgLh84p.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iUCNrTKQZRKmKMEMIznm2UlUmEd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ready Player One[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1677720</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ready Player One</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the creator of a popular video game system dies, a virtual contest is created to compete for his fortune.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pU1ULUq8D3iRxl1fdX2lZIzdHuI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dbrLfmFNFEJWv8rLnjpgCKlXWSy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Red Sonja[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0089893</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Red Sonja</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The tyrant Gedren seeks the total power in a world of barbarism. She raids the city Hablac and kills the keeper of a talisman that gives her great power. Red Sonja, sister of the keeper, sets out with her magic sword to overthrow Gedren.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qYJFrmSjy0HpzmvnIuGpuFUzXbs.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dmm4IYzNH3U8pPHP3WZJm05DOey.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]RoboCop[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093870</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>RoboCop</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a violent, near-apocalyptic Detroit, evil corporation Omni Consumer Products wins a contract from the city government to privatize the police force. To test their crime-eradicating cyborgs, the company leads street cop Alex Murphy into an armed confrontation with crime lord Boddicker so they can use his body to support their untested RoboCop prototype. But when RoboCop learns of the company's nefarious plans, he turns on his masters.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hHtOgGb3NihlyRATHlKPaFApbrd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vMGkly71Jm2KwHN407mxheMGUYR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rollerball[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0073631</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rollerball</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a corporate-controlled future, an ultra-violent sport known as Rollerball represents the world, and one of its powerful athletes is out to defy those who want him out of the game.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cmcipEfexlhVLYQXqeSWp1YcsPY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1JwLeunKPVPgcP2HpGWiAPvNlMN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rush Hour[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120812</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rush Hour</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Hong Kong Inspector Lee is summoned to Los Angeles to investigate a kidnapping, the FBI doesn't want any outside help and assigns cocky LAPD Detective James Carter to distract Lee from the case. Not content to watch the action from the sidelines, Lee and Carter form an unlikely partnership and investigate the case themselves.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/we7wOLVFgxhzLzUt0qNe50xdIQZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r4yFYBEcV247B9VXi1307fIhVqN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Sin City[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0401792</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Sin City</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Welcome to Sin City. This town beckons to the tough, the corrupt, the brokenhearted. Some call it dark… Hard-boiled. Then there are those who call it home — Crooked cops, sexy dames, desperate vigilantes. Some are seeking revenge, others lust after redemption, and then there are those hoping for a little of both. A universe of unlikely and reluctant heroes still trying to do the right thing in a city that refuses to care.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/i66G50wATMmPrvpP95f0XP6ZdVS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t9kQnqiaxQ8TLB25rTzDKLd0fdM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Skyfall[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1074638</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Skyfall</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Bond's latest assignment goes gravely wrong, agents around the world are exposed and MI6 headquarters is attacked. While M faces challenges to her authority and position from Gareth Mallory, the new Chairman of the Intelligence and Security Committee, it's up to Bond, aided only by field agent Eve, to locate the mastermind behind the attack.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d0IVecFQvsGdSbnMAHqiYsNYaJT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hoQhlAskVNgLQhArnH7reWP4pUp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Source Code[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0945513</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Source Code</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When decorated soldier Captain Colter Stevens wakes up in the body of an unknown man, he discovers he's part of a mission to find the bomber of a Chicago commuter train.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AtQDTlj3MFOXJd5C9OopaRo3rRo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/noHDKhzbwP6DfoaO2xRFLVrpX0N.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Trek[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0796366</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The fate of the galaxy rests in the hands of bitter rivals. One, James Kirk, is a delinquent, thrill-seeking Iowa farm boy. The other, Spock, a Vulcan, was raised in a logic-based society that rejects all emotion. As fiery instinct clashes with calm reason, their unlikely but powerful partnership is the only thing capable of leading their crew through unimaginable danger, boldly going where no one has gone before. The human adventure has begun again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lV5OpzAss1z06YNagOVap1I35mH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q7M0JpPixbEYT8EhnI7wTEMONxz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Starship Troopers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120201</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Starship Troopers</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Set in the future, the story follows a young soldier named Johnny Rico and his exploits in the Mobile Infantry. Rico's military career progresses from recruit to non-commissioned officer and finally to officer against the backdrop of an interstellar war between mankind and an arachnoid species known as "the Bugs".</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cxCmv23O7p3hyHwqoktHYkZcGsY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7PR2yMwXuXelAcp3qpJ3isZCdd0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Sucker Punch[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0978764</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Sucker Punch</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young girl is institutionalized by her abusive stepfather. Retreating to an alternative reality as a coping strategy, she envisions a plan which will help her escape from the mental facility.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8oBc33JEnYm3rqPIwGtQXQbP96j.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qSL3dh4QaaZ02dktTmfTDW6caMh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Superman[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0078346</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Superman</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Mild-mannered Clark Kent works as a reporter at the Daily Planet alongside his crush, Lois Lane. Clark must summon his superhero alter-ego when the nefarious Lex Luthor launches a plan to take over the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d7px1FQxW4tngdACVRsCSaZq0Xl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v6MVBFnQOscITvmAy5N5ras2JKZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tenet[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6723592</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tenet</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Armed with only one word - Tenet - and fighting for the survival of the entire world, the Protagonist journeys through a twilight world of international espionage on a mission that will unfold in something beyond real time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aCIFMriQh8rvhxpN1IWGgvH0Tlg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yY76zq9XSuJ4nWyPDuwkdV7Wt0c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Terminator 2: Judgment Day[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103064</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Nearly 10 years have passed since Sarah Connor was targeted for termination by a cyborg from the future. Now her son, John, the future leader of the resistance, is the target for a newer, more deadly terminator. Once again, the resistance has managed to send a protector back to attempt to save John and his mother Sarah.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5M0j0B18abtBI5gi2RhfjjurTqb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xKb6mtdfI5Qsggc44Hr9CCUDvaj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Abyss[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096754</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Abyss</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A civilian oil rig crew is recruited to conduct a search and rescue effort when a nuclear submarine mysteriously sinks. One diver soon finds himself on a spectacular odyssey 25,000 feet below the ocean's surface where he confronts a mysterious force that has the power to change the world or destroy it.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jel2BuDv7Bq4fuv2pUrTfiBm69o.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aPB3jFuMSoNFk2uDZ5tX5CIGaSX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Boondock Saints[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0144117</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Boondock Saints</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Tired of the crime overrunning the streets of Boston, Irish Catholic twin brothers Conner and Murphy are inspired by their faith to cleanse their hometown of evil with their own brand of zealous vigilante justice. As they hunt down and kill one notorious gangster after another, they become controversial folk heroes in the community. But Paul Smecker, an eccentric FBI agent, is fast closing in on their blood-soaked trail.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gj3V39yiGPH1FAylXxzzVneflxA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tIJKAbESEi9eywpVflJpTHukPwR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Crow[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0109506</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Crow</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Exactly one year after young rock guitarist Eric Draven and his fiancée are brutally killed by a ruthless gang of criminals, Draven—watched over by a hypnotic crow—returns from the grave to exact revenge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iH5eExSCOv1kxJXH9npPyM0EAJF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8v5z3Wa6GbyjqvMxXz11PTmDCwS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Dark Knight[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0468569</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Dark Knight</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Batman raises the stakes in his war on crime. With the help of Lt. Jim Gordon and District Attorney Harvey Dent, Batman sets out to dismantle the remaining criminal organizations that plague the streets. The partnership proves to be effective, but they soon find themselves prey to a reign of chaos unleashed by a rising criminal mastermind known to the terrified citizens of Gotham as the Joker.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qJ2tW6WMUDux911r6m7haRef0WH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pbEkjhdfP7yuDcMB78YEZwgD4IN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Dark Knight Rises[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1345836</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Dark Knight Rises</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Following the death of District Attorney Harvey Dent, Batman assumes responsibility for Dent's crimes to protect the late attorney's reputation and is subsequently hunted by the Gotham City Police Department. Eight years later, Batman encounters the mysterious Selina Kyle and the villainous Bane, a new terrorist leader who overwhelms Gotham's finest. The Dark Knight resurfaces to protect a city that has branded him an enemy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/85cWkCVftiVs0BVey6pxX8uNmLt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Yrpb32j3eMpMVX7ND3TnOkHnbl.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Equalizer[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0455944</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Equalizer</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>McCall believes he has put his mysterious past behind him and dedicated himself to beginning a new, quiet life. But when he meets Teri, a young girl under the control of ultra-violent Russian gangsters, he can’t stand idly by – he has to help her. Armed with hidden skills that allow him to serve vengeance against anyone who would brutalize the helpless, McCall comes out of his self-imposed retirement and finds his desire for justice reawakened. If someone has a problem, if the odds are stacked against them, if they have nowhere else to turn, McCall will help. He is The Equalizer.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9u4yW7yPA0BQ2pv9XwiNzItwvp8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9vAoubhoZE8aSkUZoSfxs3UWZhO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Equalizer 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3766354</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Equalizer 2</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Robert McCall, who serves an unflinching justice for the exploited and oppressed, embarks on a relentless, globe-trotting quest for vengeance when a long-time girl friend is murdered.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cQvc9N6JiMVKqol3wcYrGshsIdZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z7noaCJ4KtmhwHw7QcNtnMMo4Qy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fast and the Furious[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0232500</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fast and the Furious</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Dominic Toretto is a Los Angeles street racer suspected of masterminding a series of big-rig hijackings. When undercover cop Brian O'Conner infiltrates Toretto's iconoclastic crew, he falls for Toretto's sister and must choose a side: the gang or the LAPD.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lgCEntS9mHagxdL5hb3qaV49YTd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jY9ef5nqY4xIIMu3yzW3qamUCoi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fifth Element[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119116</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fifth Element</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 2257, a taxi driver is unintentionally given the task of saving a young girl who is part of the key that will ensure the survival of humanity.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fPtlCO1yQtnoLHOwKtWz7db6RGU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dwN0kPGrLbFRxyL3F3J3t4ShQx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Gentlemen[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt8367814</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Gentlemen</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>American expat Mickey Pearson has built a highly profitable marijuana empire in London. When word gets out that he’s looking to cash out of the business forever it triggers plots, schemes, bribery and blackmail in an attempt to steal his domain out from under him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jtrhTYB7xSrJxR1vusu99nvnZ1g.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tintsaQ0WLzZsTMkTiqtMB3rfc8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Hunt[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt8244784</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hunt</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Twelve strangers wake up in a clearing. They don't know where they are—or how they got there. In the shadow of a dark internet conspiracy theory, ruthless elitists gather at a remote location to hunt humans for sport. But their master plan is about to be derailed when one of the hunted turns the tables on her pursuers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wxPhn4ef1EAo5njxwBkAEVrlJJG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9R2FuGT0BeZl8usfsfqIcO7KK7v.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Matrix[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0133093</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Matrix</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Set in the 22nd century, The Matrix tells the story of a computer hacker who joins a group of underground insurgents fighting the vast and powerful computers who now rule the earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f89U3ADr1oiB1s9GkdPOEpXUk5H.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/waCRuAW5ocONRehP556vPexVXA9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Running Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093894</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Running Man</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>By 2017, the global economy has collapsed and U.S. society has become a totalitarian police state, censoring all cultural activity. The government pacifies the populace by broadcasting a number of game shows in which convicted criminals fight for their lives, including the gladiator-style The Running Man, hosted by the ruthless Damon Killian, where “runners” attempt to evade “stalkers” and certain death for a chance to be pardoned and set free.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/GTAUOhO4BN0peJVvxGEQydJvUO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sCTD23P22WTILZlClKyC4bKRfYe.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Terminator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088247</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Terminator</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the post-apocalyptic future, reigning tyrannical supercomputers teleport a cyborg assassin known as the "Terminator" back to 1984 to kill Sarah Connor, whose unborn son is destined to lead insurgents against 21st century mechanical hegemony. Meanwhile, the human-resistance movement dispatches a lone warrior to safeguard Sarah. Can he stop the virtually indestructible killing machine?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvktm0BHcnmDpul4Hz01GIazWPr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wh4ze6klUbeichAj603OKZwY1W5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tomb Raider[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1365519</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tomb Raider</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Lara Croft, the fiercely independent daughter of a missing adventurer, must push herself beyond her limits when she finds herself on the island where her father disappeared.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ePyN2nX9t8SOl70eRW47Q29zUFO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bLJTjfbZ1c5zSNiAvGYs1Uc82ir.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Top Gun[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0092099</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Top Gun</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For Lieutenant Pete 'Maverick' Mitchell and his friend and co-pilot Nick 'Goose' Bradshaw, being accepted into an elite training school for fighter pilots is a dream come true. But a tragedy, as well as personal demons, will threaten Pete's dreams of becoming an ace pilot.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xUuHj3CgmZQ9P2cMaqQs4J0d4Zc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jILeJ60zPpIjjJHGSmIeY4eO30t.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Total Recall[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0100802</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Total Recall</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Construction worker Douglas Quaid's obsession with the planet Mars leads him to visit Recall, a company who manufacture memories. Something goes wrong during his memory implant turning Doug's life upside down and even to question what is reality and what isn't.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wVbeL6fkbTKSmNfalj4VoAUUqJv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cE9Gtz5KEVkien4VDSgXjtwfcs.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]True Lies[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0111503</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>True Lies</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A fearless, globe-trotting, terrorist-battling secret agent has his life turned upside down when he discovers his wife might be having an affair with a used car salesman while terrorists smuggle nuclear war heads into the United States.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pweFTnzzTfGK68woSVkiTgjLzWm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jRZ3joUcg8YDCQYl4Tog5xhY6wk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Twelve Monkeys[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114746</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Twelve Monkeys</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the year 2035, convict James Cole reluctantly volunteers to be sent back in time to discover the origin of a deadly virus that wiped out nearly all of the earth's population and forced the survivors into underground communities. But when Cole is mistakenly sent to 1990 instead of 1996, he's arrested and locked up in a mental hospital. There he meets psychiatrist Dr. Kathryn Railly, and patient Jeffrey Goines, the son of a famous virus expert, who may hold the key to the mysterious rogue group, the Army of the 12 Monkeys, thought to be responsible for unleashing the killer disease.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gt3iyguaCIw8DpQZI1LIN5TohM2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2aPrheKAOwyjJqu6YYd2TvsKv9a.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Under Siege[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0105690</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Under Siege</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Disgruntled ex-CIA operative Strannix, his assistant Krill and their group of terrorists seize the battleship with nuclear blackmail in mind. They've planned for every contingency but ignore the ship's cook, former Navy SEAL Casey Ryback -- an error that could be fatal.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/myHxm9p8fhEsXyaLO6DawYJKolg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/isFQiBiBiz4Xyx22sTs6CR1scL3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Underworld[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0320691</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Underworld</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Vampires and werewolves have waged a nocturnal war against each other for centuries. But all bets are off when a female vampire warrior named Selene, who's famous for her strength and werewolf-hunting prowess, becomes smitten with a peace-loving male werewolf, Michael, who wants to end the war.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zsnQ41UZ3jo1wEeemF0eA9cAIU0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y0wS3wYveeCGmtN3j6FXzvwziio.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Universal Soldier[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0105698</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Universal Soldier</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An American soldier who had been killed during the Vietnam War is revived 25 years later by the military as a semi-android, UniSols, a high-tech soldier of the future. After the failure of the initiative to erase all the soldier's memories, he begins to experience flashbacks that are forcing him to recall his past.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fp0mWrHl1SW9PhP8QcsgYPoVYFc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/505LZxTJd2o7BqpispO427M9bPI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Van Helsing[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0338526</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Van Helsing</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Famed monster slayer Gabriel Van Helsing is dispatched to Transylvania to assist the last of the Valerious bloodline in defeating Count Dracula. Anna Valerious reveals that Dracula has formed an unholy alliance with Dr. Frankenstein's monster and is hell-bent on exacting a centuries-old curse on her family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gsFun8nATm52aGHeT8ueAel98nE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mmfRdSMRy8BSgOULjYlpmuKwJ1o.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]World War Z[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0816711</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>World War Z</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Life for former United Nations investigator Gerry Lane and his family seems content. Suddenly, the world is plagued by a mysterious infection turning whole human populations into rampaging mindless zombies. After barely escaping the chaos, Lane is persuaded to go on a mission to investigate this disease. What follows is a perilous trek around the world where Lane must brave horrific dangers and long odds to find answers before human civilization falls.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1SWBSYJsnyhdNRfLI1T6RsCxAQ4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kg2FOT2Oe5PSCgs3L4vLel6B7ck.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Snowpiercer[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1706620</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Snowpiercer</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a future where a failed global-warming experiment kills off most life on the planet, a class system evolves aboard the Snowpiercer, a train that travels around the globe via a perpetual-motion engine.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nzccOvhrLGI0nvAknCEAk8bchD9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/33dV6HAnXBmwKl640gO3U4auqUN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
