<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Alien[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0078748</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During its return to the earth, commercial spaceship Nostromo intercepts a distress signal from a distant planet. When a three-member team of the crew discovers a chamber containing thousands of eggs on the planet, a creature inside one of the eggs attacks an explorer. The entire crew is unaware of the impending nightmare set to descend upon them when the alien parasite planted inside its unfortunate host is birthed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vfrQk5IPloGg1v9Rzbh2Eg3VGyM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AmR3JG1VQVxU8TfAvljUhfSFUOx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Aliens[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090605</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aliens</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Ripley's lifepod is found by a salvage crew over 50 years later, she finds that terra-formers are on the very planet they found the alien species. When the company sends a family of colonists out to investigate her story—all contact is lost with the planet and colonists. They enlist Ripley and the colonial marines to return and search for answers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r1x5JGpyqZU8PYhbs4UcrO1Xb6x.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jMBpJFRtrtIXymer93XLavPwI3P.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Alien Resurrection[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0118583</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien Resurrection</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Two hundred years after Lt. Ripley died, a group of scientists clone her, hoping to breed the ultimate weapon. But the new Ripley is full of surprises … as are the new aliens. Ripley must team with a band of smugglers to keep the creatures from reaching Earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bo6TCzRoyIuiedMhVX8nYoeQcky.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ikr0UILfvRerzMNoBTtJtyuWAEV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]AVP: Alien vs. Predator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0370263</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>AVP: Alien vs. Predator</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When scientists discover something in the Arctic that appears to be a buried Pyramid, they send a research team out to investigate. Little do they know that they are about to step into a hunting ground where Aliens are grown as sport for the Predator race.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qUZctuoFL3VKOqeKxhnLwuEE4oF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tOvoWzkUzCMJ8Ra5nkmNg7ehCET.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Aliens vs Predator: Requiem[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0758730</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aliens vs Predator: Requiem</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The iconic creatures from two of the scariest film franchises in movie history wage their most brutal battle ever—in our own backyard. The small town of Gunnison, Colorado becomes a war zone between two of the deadliest extra-terrestrial life forms—the Alien and the Predator. When a Predator scout ship crash-lands in the hills outside the town, Alien Facehuggers and a hybrid Alien/Predator are released and begin to terrorize the town.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d3xsKYqRO1Ys5UddRstbeb0Kf95.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y8yvIrmoM2PLuJcSto7OmOfsXQj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Prometheus[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1446714</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Prometheus</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A team of explorers discover a clue to the origins of mankind on Earth, leading them on a journey to the darkest corners of the universe. There, they must fight a terrifying battle to save the future of the human race.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qsYQflQhOuhDpQ0W2aOcwqgDAeI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hO97RyNjBIMfzfFpUjNhsm4zImh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Alien: Covenant[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2316204</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien: Covenant</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bound for a remote planet on the far side of the galaxy, the crew of the colony ship 'Covenant' discovers what is thought to be an uncharted paradise, but is actually a dark, dangerous world—which has a sole inhabitant: the 'synthetic', David, survivor of the doomed Prometheus expedition.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zecMELPbU5YMQpC81Z8ImaaXuf9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6jajFcaY2YsfGQstJ5HaqZNVseX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
