<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0029583</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs</title>
	<year>1937</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A beautiful girl, Snow White, takes refuge in the forest in the house of seven dwarfs to hide from her stepmother, the wicked Queen. The Queen is jealous because she wants to be known as "the fairest in the land," and Snow White's beauty surpasses her own.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9QKUh9UuIIT2ZA9Rby9R6vtNRKa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n3pJwYuPnkw7JX7tOMbH0GRfBPn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pinocchio[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0032910</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pinocchio</title>
	<year>1940</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Lonely toymaker Geppetto has his wishes answered when the Blue Fairy arrives to bring his wooden puppet Pinocchio to life. Before becoming a real boy, however, Pinocchio must prove he's worthy as he sets off on an adventure with his whistling sidekick and conscience, Jiminy Cricket.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bnZJrLRnoQHpzEJdka1KYfsAF3N.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1NQkxP7oe5iJHNb4ApqhlDFJ9dI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fantasia[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0032455</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantasia</title>
	<year>1940</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Walt Disney's timeless masterpiece is an extravaganza of sight and sound! See the music come to life, hear the pictures burst into song and experience the excitement that is Fantasia over and over again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5m9njnidjR0syG2gpVPVgcEMB2X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yRDU00odN8kHIFJQobkoCKcL6Le.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dumbo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0033563</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dumbo</title>
	<year>1941</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Dumbo is a baby elephant born with over-sized ears and a supreme lack of confidence. But thanks to his even more diminutive buddy Timothy the Mouse,  the pint-sized pachyderm learns to surmount all obstacles.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hKDdllslMtsU9JixAv5HR9biXlp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eEKpOowAkVAF3sKJKqY2h4h12GV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Bambi[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0034492</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bambi</title>
	<year>1942</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bambi's tale unfolds from season to season as the young prince of the forest learns about life, love, and friends.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wV9e2y4myJ4KMFsyFfWYcUOawyK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1pVf2KhIa1oNHZac5nkt46jKaji.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Saludos Amigos[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0036326</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Saludos Amigos</title>
	<year>1942</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Live-action segments show members of the Disney staff touring South America and recording their impressions in sketches. These segue into four animated sections: "Lake Titicaca" depicts tourist Donald Duck's troubles with a stubborn llama; "Pedro" tells of a little mail plane's adventures flying over the treacherous Andes; "El Gaucho Goofy" transplants an American cowboy into the Argentine pampas; and in "Aquarela do Brasil," Jose Carioca shows Donald the sights and sounds of Rio de Janiero.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jiNSrKpgKdLXEUasOvNaCBgEner.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/QpCgkh4RALIMACcCO79PZHiEjV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Three Caballeros[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0038166</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Three Caballeros</title>
	<year>1944</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For Donald's birthday he receives a box with three gifts inside. The gifts, a movie projector, a pop-up book, and a pinata, each take Donald on wild adventures through Mexico and South America.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nMfScRxw9wVLoO7LiEjziFAKLSK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kcWYiBWej3JdYbGEVaKYAQGfqYp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Make Mine Music[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0038718</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Make Mine Music</title>
	<year>1946</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the tradition of Fantasia, Make Mine Music is a glorious collection of nine musically charged animated shorts featuring such fun-filled favorites as "Peter And The Wolf", narrated by the beloved voice behind Winnie The Pooh. In addition, you'll enjoy such classic cartoon hits as "Casey At The Bat," "The Whale Who Wanted To Sing At The Met" and "Johnnie Fedora And Alice Bluebonnet."</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1iT4YrVjphB6r6L0ovuzvMSL3Cu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v3a6fM8QpNWZOQFgOYUeHu6RIad.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Melody Time[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0040580</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Melody Time</title>
	<year>1948</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the grand tradition of Disney's great musical classics, Melody Time features seven timeless stories, each enhanced with high-spirited music and unforgettable characters. You'll be sure to tap your toes and clap your hands in this witty feast for the eyes and ears.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aLij9PB33f4PscrJqin03TlnZtv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/unnlsb68YDJbaTwAbgXCh1qQZJ8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0041094</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad</title>
	<year>1949</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Wind in the Willows: Concise version of Kenneth Grahame's story of the same name. J. Thaddeus Toad, owner of Toad Hall, is prone to fads, such as the newfangled motor car. This desire for the very latest lands him in much trouble with the wrong crowd, and it is up to his friends, Mole, Rat and Badger to save him from himself. - The Legend of Sleepy Hollow: Retelling of Washington Irving's story set in a tiny New England town. Ichabod Crane, the new schoolmaster, falls for the town beauty, Katrina Van Tassel, and the town Bully Brom Bones decides that he is a little too successful and needs "convincing" that Katrina is not for him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1MpPEstGQPEsLJM9FGHqJUGtO6S.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wCfa6ZNdY9PPGt5rKqX6RA7gl2g.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Cinderella[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0042332</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Cinderella</title>
	<year>1950</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Cinderella has faith her dreams of a better life will come true. With help from her loyal mice friends and a wave of her Fairy Godmother's wand, Cinderella's rags are magically turned into a glorious gown and off she goes to the Royal Ball. But when the clock strikes midnight, the spell is broken, leaving a single glass slipper... the only key to the ultimate fairy-tale ending!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/avz6S9HYWs4O8Oe4PenBFNX4uDi.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wQraxOsaq0NwTO9rSwLo4Nc8hVG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Alice in Wonderland[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0043274</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alice in Wonderland</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>On a golden afternoon, young Alice follows a White Rabbit, who disappears down a nearby rabbit hole. Quickly following him, she tumbles into the burrow - and enters the merry, topsy-turvy world of Wonderland! Memorable songs and whimsical escapades highlight Alice's journey, which culminates in a madcap encounter with the Queen of Hearts - and her army of playing cards!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/20cvfwfaFqNbe9Fc3VEHJuPRxmn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hWbNlp9Qq9DdnHNxn2WlVpGbSfI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Peter Pan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0046183</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Peter Pan</title>
	<year>1953</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Leaving the safety of their nursery behind, Wendy, Michael and John follow Peter Pan to a magical world where childhood lasts forever. But while in Neverland, the kids must face Captain Hook and foil his attempts to get rid of Peter for good.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fJJOs1iyrhKfZceANxoPxPwNGF1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/D00lpEospyhTcwjnIYSW7VVtou.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Lady and the Tramp[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0048280</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lady and the Tramp</title>
	<year>1955</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Lady, a golden cocker spaniel, meets up with a mongrel dog who calls himself the Tramp. He is obviously from the wrong side of town, but happenings at Lady's home make her decide to travel with him for a while.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r9FiDSdBwNHdRwN0NMRrqfEHJGO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yGgEg4yimYQJLZrZg3Qhogp2raQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Sleeping Beauty[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0053285</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Sleeping Beauty</title>
	<year>1959</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A beautiful princess born in a faraway kingdom is destined by a terrible curse to prick her finger on the spindle of a spinning wheel and fall into a deep sleep that can only be awakened by true love's first kiss. Determined to protect her, her parents ask three fairies to raise her in hiding. But the evil Maleficent is just as determined to seal the princess's fate.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e3K5cLvVRXVxhw4mXQET92p1dnz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4CryneVBqNPqmXR206snm7491gT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]One Hundred and One Dalmatians[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0055254</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>One Hundred and One Dalmatians</title>
	<year>1961</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a litter of dalmatian puppies are abducted by the minions of Cruella De Vil, the parents must find them before she uses them for a diabolical fashion statement.
 In a Disney animation classic, Dalmatian Pongo is tired of his bachelor-dog life. He spies lovely Perdita and maneuvers his master, Roger, into meeting Perdita's owner, Anita. The owners fall in love and marry, keeping Pongo and Perdita together too. After Perdita gives birth to a litter of 15 puppies, Anita's old school friend Cruella De Vil wants to buy them all. Roger declines her offer, so Cruella hires the criminal Badun brothers to steal them -- so she can have a fur coat.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mRY84MJeWKnp9joev82QtslJFvk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vlLW4BPPS6XL8mxAvoJSppJV3Sv.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Sword in the Stone[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0057546</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Sword in the Stone</title>
	<year>1963</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Wart is a young boy who aspires to be a knight's squire. On a hunting trip he falls in on Merlin, a powerful but amnesiac wizard who has plans for him beyond mere squiredom. He starts by trying to give him an education, believing that once one has an education, one can go anywhere. Needless to say, it doesn't quite work out that way.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dYQhKThGXl3xQv71Ysw0RSmVmBA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m1TOfgljbT3jOez3b4l1I1tm82W.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Jungle Book[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0061852</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Jungle Book</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The boy Mowgli makes his way to the man-village with Bagheera, the wise panther. Along the way he meets jazzy King Louie, the hypnotic snake Kaa and the lovable, happy-go-lucky bear Baloo, who teaches Mowgli "The Bare Necessities" of life and the true meaning of friendship.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yN1kuupnPTLUprgfvC5WapgrxG4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zj8XS0l1cWStpKnuD1LFMB3VoV1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Aristocats[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0065421</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Aristocats</title>
	<year>1970</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Madame Adelaide Bonfamille leaves her fortune to Duchess and her children—Bonfamille’s beloved family of cats—the butler plots to steal the money and kidnaps the legatees, leaving them out on a country road. All seems lost until the wily Thomas O’Malley Cat and his jazz-playing alley cats come to the aristocats’ rescue.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GVekZRvV25OzUQIw1Gn4sikkVo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rnMwOM8gMqo6Gf6XXMpaJEayUwk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Robin Hood[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0070608</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Robin Hood</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>With King Richard off to the Crusades, Prince John and his slithering minion, Sir Hiss, set about taxing Nottingham's citizens with support from the corrupt sheriff - and staunch opposition by the wily Robin Hood and his band of merry men.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/alcY9jZBgKw9OB7hiPYVNvh03Sb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oegA1YBl1PszRbB0qj4UpVSr9Jt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fun and Fancy Free[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0039404</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fun and Fancy Free</title>
	<year>1947</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Jiminy Cricket hosts two Disney animated shorts: “Bongo,” about a circus bear escaping to the wild, and “Mickey and the Beanstalk,” a take on the famous fairy tale.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lmc6Ge5GuSj7sLkkLHyuZpuI8Ii.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gcLCXH7ZTr3Yk2JG1u7cXb7p1vy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Rescuers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0076618</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Rescuers</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>What can two little mice possibly do to save an orphan girl who's fallen into evil hands? With a little cooperation and faith in oneself, anything is possible! As members of the mouse-run International Rescue Aid Society, Bernard and Miss Bianca respond to orphan Penny's call for help. The two mice search for clues with the help of an old cat named Rufus.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gCJuDViPCEuHVmoZUvhOj1jyqfV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jToyymxSX9YU1iIabEa22XQucob.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fox and the Hound[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0082406</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fox and the Hound</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a feisty little fox named Tod is adopted into a farm family, he quickly becomes friends with a fun and adorable hound puppy named Copper. Life is full of hilarious adventures until Copper is expected to take on his role as a hunting dog -- and the object of his search is his best friend!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1382VHxqZDXu2t8i46zf4fP71JG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lNmIAX1IuPIEPMHhLBEm4wmhYX0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Black Cauldron[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088814</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Black Cauldron</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Taran is an assistant pigkeeper with boyish dreams of becoming a great warrior. However, he has to put the daydreaming aside when his charge, an oracular pig named Hen Wen, is kidnapped by an evil lord known as the Horned King. The villain hopes Hen will show him the way to The Black Cauldron, which has the power to create a giant army of unstoppable soldiers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/act8vtlXVEizdsUf9FcKbzSERew.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eb4MxDQJehL60EZO6cKFFiUq23J.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Great Mouse Detective[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091149</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Great Mouse Detective</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the diabolical Professor Ratigan kidnaps London's master toymaker, the brilliant master of disguise Basil of Baker Street and his trusted sidekick Dawson try to elude the ultimate trap and foil the perfect crime.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9uDr7vfjCFr39KGCcqrk44Cg7fQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3ugxkNhsN7MWwshk9jR6Xi7cFTR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Oliver & Company[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0095776</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Oliver & Company</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>This animated take on Oliver Twist re-imagines Oliver as an adorable orphaned kitten who struggles to survive in New York City and falls in with a band of canine criminals led by an evil human. First, Oliver meets Dodger, a carefree mutt with street savoir faire. But when Oliver meets wealthy Jenny on one of the gang's thieving missions, his life changes forever.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nijsZeuINn0SnNb5cQVz2L4Yhps.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y7CEs6kCuY1tQI6B9jO8g8xdufg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Little Mermaid[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0097757</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Little Mermaid</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>This colorful adventure tells the story of an impetuous mermaid princess named Ariel who falls in love with the very human Prince Eric and puts everything on the line for the chance to be with him. Memorable songs and characters -- including the villainous sea witch Ursula.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/plcZXvI310FkbwIptvd6rqk63LP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2ze42e0l0bPYEcJXInUukvNfZKk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Rescuers Down Under[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0100477</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Rescuers Down Under</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A lawless poacher wants to capture a majestic and rare golden eagle, so he kidnaps the boy who knows where to find the bird. Not to worry -- the Rescue Aid Society's top agents, heroic mice Miss Bianca and Bernard, fly to Australia to save the day. Accompanying the fearless duo are bumbling albatross Wilbur and local field operative Jake the Kangaroo Rat.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/udXDHGLqxBoDcBvqExFn8rIpiZM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/golKU8BEGcik0DLshnAeQAdSvsW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Beauty and the Beast[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0101414</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Beauty and the Beast</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Follow the adventures of Belle, a bright young woman who finds herself in the castle of a prince who's been turned into a mysterious beast. With the help of the castle's enchanted staff, Belle soon learns the most important lesson of all -- that true beauty comes from within.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6DDJ8o2d6T4fpGWECLF4xBGTyAM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jsgRkhPxYtzAhDFCUyNbvlX63tY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Aladdin[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103639</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aladdin</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Princess Jasmine grows tired of being forced to remain in the palace, so she sneaks out into the marketplace, in disguise, where she meets street-urchin Aladdin.  The couple falls in love, although Jasmine may only marry a prince.  After being thrown in jail, Aladdin becomes embroiled in a plot to find a mysterious lamp, with which the evil Jafar hopes to rule the land.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fhyun1mja3WwQsYr1a3x1x9BttP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5OeY4U2rzePxWq2rkqMajUx2gz7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lion King[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0110357</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lion King</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young lion prince is cast out of his pride by his cruel uncle, who claims he killed his father. While the uncle rules with an iron paw, the prince grows up beyond the Savannah, living by a philosophy: No worries for the rest of your days. But when his past comes to haunt him, the young prince must decide his fate: Will he remain an outcast or face his demons and become what he needs to be?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sKCr78MXSLixwmZ8DyJLrpMsd15.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wXsQvli6tWqja51pYxXNG1LFIGV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pocahontas[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114148</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pocahontas</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Pocahontas, daughter of a Native American tribe chief, falls in love with an English soldier as colonists invade 17th century Virginia.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kZ1ft0QZ4e3zDUPMBftEkwI9ftd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9YAVIwBcBrLXeukg2dgMGfYB1uu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Hunchback of Notre Dame[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116583</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hunchback of Notre Dame</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>At the urging of his gargoyle pals, Quasimodo leaves Notre Dame tower against the wishes of his guardian, the evil Judge Claude Frollo. He ventures out to the Festival of Fools and finds his first true friend, a Romani woman named Esmeralda, who entrusts him with a secret. When the secret is revealed, Quasi soon finds himself fighting to save the people and city he loves.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r7V92gY3AMO6li17MmGTixAnFcv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oslaee3VX9kJAjVezbjZKlEJDzn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Hercules[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119282</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hercules</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bestowed with superhuman strength, a young mortal named Hercules sets out to prove himself a hero in the eyes of his father, the great god Zeus. Along with his friends Pegasus, a flying horse, and Phil, a personal trainer, Hercules is tricked by the hilarious, hotheaded villain Hades, who's plotting to take over Mount Olympus!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dK9rNoC97tgX3xXg5zdxFisdfcp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/26FT7NBKiGvWJBB3VG9i72LnI8S.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mulan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120762</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mulan</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>To save her father from certain death in the army, a young woman secretly enlists in his place and becomes one of China's greatest heroines in the process.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5TYgKxYhnhRNNwqnRAKHkgfqi2G.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rFxWhQB3JmmwCU5kcQQFrnpzGtF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tarzan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120855</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tarzan</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Tarzan was a small orphan who was raised by an ape named Kala since he was a child. He believed that this was his family, but on an expedition Jane Porter is rescued by Tarzan. He then finds out that he's human. Now Tarzan must make the decision as to which family he should belong to...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ceGk1VcuI8pSXQhSlnqsqTFCPLD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3Skg7e94WFreLgQAR0PAYSk0Zv1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fantasia 2000[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120910</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantasia 2000</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Blending lively music and brilliant animation, this sequel to the original 'Fantasia' restores 'The Sorcerer's Apprentice' and adds seven new shorts.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5rwAtUaKEK48CPUijVfVU0IPKPZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wBQ2tSdXgAOAdH14VgXtN9qD0Ol.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Emperor's New Groove[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120917</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Emperor's New Groove</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Kuzco is a self-centered emperor who summons Pacha from a village and to tell him that his home will be destroyed to make room for Kuzco's new summer home. Kuzco's advisor, Yzma, tries to poison Kuzco and accidentally turns him into a llama, who accidentally ends up in Pacha's village. Pacha offers to help Kuzco if he doesn't destroy his house, and so they form an unlikely partnership.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xU635vn1lMD9DWDloeuKmuhxxnQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mZj8EUr6F1x2PWZjKPxaeYd5WRw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dinosaur[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0130623</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dinosaur</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An orphaned dinosaur raised by lemurs joins an arduous trek to a sancturary after a meteorite shower destroys his family home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rSje3FS7ycJSglowlngjsvDt7vO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/laeEtakR2pLKu3CeRwB2lU5Y53X.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Atlantis: The Lost Empire[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0230011</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Atlantis: The Lost Empire</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The world's most highly qualified crew of archaeologists and explorers is led by historian Milo Thatch as they board the incredible 1,000-foot submarine Ulysses and head deep into the mysteries of the sea. The underwater expedition takes an unexpected turn when the team's mission must switch from exploring Atlantis to protecting it.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8fUEFPUTF7kBMuKPiSQHxPvd8EZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fYr0fqT9NImOuaN1QgnDHgGh4Ci.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Lilo & Stitch[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0275847</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lilo & Stitch</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As Stitch, a runaway genetic experiment from a faraway planet, wreaks havoc on the Hawaiian Islands, he becomes the mischievous adopted alien "puppy" of an independent little girl named Lilo and learns about loyalty, friendship, and ʻohana, the Hawaiian tradition of family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m13Vbzv7R2GMAl3GXFrkmMEgCFQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oA4N0lrAdgD4uAHFkePNft7MUZp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Treasure Planet[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0133240</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Treasure Planet</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When space galleon cabin boy Jim Hawkins discovers a map to an intergalactic "loot of a thousand worlds," a cyborg cook named John Silver teaches him to battle supernovas and space storms on their journey to find treasure.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zMKatZ0c0NCoKzfizaCzVUcbKMf.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mVuH9hNGnxF9bbhlh1Tr9FuG3Uc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Brother Bear[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0328880</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Brother Bear</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When an impulsive boy named Kenai is magically transformed into a bear, he must literally walk in another's footsteps until he learns some valuable life lessons. His courageous and often zany journey introduces him to a forest full of wildlife, including the lovable bear cub Koda, hilarious moose Rutt and Tuke, woolly mammoths and rambunctious rams.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/otptPbEY0vBostmo95xwiiumMJm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6eJsw468dEwDg5FnVz6aOZtBXbq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Home on the Range[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0299172</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Home on the Range</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a greedy outlaw schemes to take possession of the "Patch Of Heaven" dairy farm, three determined cows, a karate-kicking stallion and a colorful corral of critters join forces to save their home. The stakes are sky-high as this unlikely animal alliance risk their hides and match wits with a mysterious band of bad guys.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9xIIo4FMquy5SRqn8hppyr2QadR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rQKlcMY8i3elENXEHlkAbQr3xiG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Chicken Little[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0371606</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Chicken Little</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the sky really is falling and sanity has flown the coop, who will rise to save the day? Together with his hysterical band of misfit friends, Chicken Little must hatch a plan to save the planet from alien invasion and prove that the world's biggest hero is a little chicken.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1wg65q3daTE8rGfaUhBxLdXk6NL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r819lbFc6LB88CUWTQ0BvJfluho.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Meet the Robinsons[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0396555</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Meet the Robinsons</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Lewis, a brilliant young inventor, is keen on creating a time machine to find his mother, who abandoned him in an orphanage. Things take a turn when he meets Wilbur Robinson and his family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dBFnxopMSB3vKPV4Zl1wDYuurCn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9NunpQrxyqpIKIfovfvJcVrEEbt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Bolt[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0397892</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bolt</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bolt is the star of the biggest show in Hollywood. The only problem is, he thinks it's real. After he's accidentally shipped to New York City and separated from Penny, his beloved co-star and owner, Bolt must harness all his "super powers" to find a way home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z9VHoUcZ1GiH3f3qYz7Me7Zc1Fd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uWIyXlBRwW2MIBcBysj50A9nv7D.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Princess and the Frog[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0780521</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Princess and the Frog</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A waitress, desperate to fulfill her dreams as a restaurant owner, is set on a journey to turn a frog prince back into a human being, but she has to face the same problem after she kisses him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yprv5PbnEksoVj2v6XEnDBg9joR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z62CBlBBBOoNUuuxZ1jMAcq5ARE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tangled[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0398286</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tangled</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the kingdom's most wanted-and most charming-bandit Flynn Rider hides out in a mysterious tower, he's taken hostage by Rapunzel, a beautiful and feisty tower-bound teen with 70 feet of magical, golden hair. Flynn's curious captor, who's looking for her ticket out of the tower where she's been locked away for years, strikes a deal with the handsome thief and the unlikely duo sets off on an action-packed escapade, complete with a super-cop horse, an over-protective chameleon and a gruff gang of pub thugs.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ym7Kst6a4uodryxqbGOxmewF235.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cWczNud8Y8i8ab0Z4bxos4myWYO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Wreck-It Ralph[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1772341</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Wreck-It Ralph</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Wreck-It Ralph is the 9-foot-tall, 643-pound villain of an arcade video game named Fix-It Felix Jr., in which the game's titular hero fixes buildings that Ralph destroys. Wanting to prove he can be a good guy and not just a villain, Ralph escapes his game and lands in Hero's Duty, a first-person shooter where he helps the game's hero battle against alien invaders. He later enters Sugar Rush, a kart racing game set on tracks made of candies, cookies and other sweets. There, Ralph meets Vanellope von Schweetz who has learned that her game is faced with a dire threat that could affect the entire arcade, and one that Ralph may have inadvertently started.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zWoIgZ7mgmPkaZjG0102BSKFIqQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ziC23LkMYj8gToQQYQGWSGJCLNF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Winnie the Pooh[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1449283</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Winnie the Pooh</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During an ordinary day in Hundred Acre Wood, Winnie the Pooh sets out to find some honey. Misinterpreting a note from Christopher Robin, Owl convinces Pooh, Tigger, Rabbit, Piglet, Kanga, Roo, and Eeyore that their young friend has been captured by a creature named "Backson" and they set out to rescue him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wMZU69sPEP8dSNU0nMWVt7b54EQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e0SlSnLQzIhdcr86akVJinA1Jau.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Frozen[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2294629</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Frozen</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Young princess Anna of Arendelle dreams about finding true love at her sister Elsa’s coronation. Fate takes her on a dangerous journey in an attempt to end the eternal winter that has fallen over the kingdom. She's accompanied by ice delivery man Kristoff, his reindeer Sven, and snowman Olaf. On an adventure where she will find out what friendship, courage, family, and true love really means.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kgwjIb2JDHRhNk13lmSxiClFjVk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9WHM084AoskcHCObAy4QnJg01eM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
