<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Aladdin[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103639</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aladdin</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Princess Jasmine grows tired of being forced to remain in the palace, so she sneaks out into the marketplace, in disguise, where she meets street-urchin Aladdin.  The couple falls in love, although Jasmine may only marry a prince.  After being thrown in jail, Aladdin becomes embroiled in a plot to find a mysterious lamp, with which the evil Jafar hopes to rule the land.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fhyun1mja3WwQsYr1a3x1x9BttP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5OeY4U2rzePxWq2rkqMajUx2gz7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Antz[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120587</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Antz</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A neurotic worker ant in love with a rebellious princess rises to unlikely stardom when he switches places with a soldier. Signing up to march in a parade, he ends up under the command of a bloodthirsty general. But he's actually been enlisted to fight against a termite army.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lWPjxbUMpAHFkJpZHHNWhQaRsax.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6eleaikeuXNtPh3llb0LK2Iy2r4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Arthur Christmas[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1430607</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Arthur Christmas</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Each Christmas, Santa and his vast army of highly trained elves produce gifts and distribute them around the world in one night. However, when one of 600 million children to receive a gift from Santa on Christmas Eve is missed, it is deemed ‘acceptable’ to all but one—Arthur. Arthur Claus is Santa’s misfit son who executes an unauthorised rookie mission to get the last present half way around the globe before dawn on Christmas morning.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sPCrGLdTMn0ud3oAJG37VDxpQfZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/i7W7x1EhLk0PXXFnHiCPBgUjBVC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Babe[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0112431</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Babe</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Babe is a little pig who doesn't quite know his place in the world. With a bunch of odd friends, like Ferdinand the duck who thinks he is a rooster and Fly the dog he calls mum, Babe realises that he has the makings to become the greatest sheep pig of all time, and Farmer Hogget knows it. With the help of the sheep dogs, Babe learns that a pig can be anything that he wants to be.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zKuQMtnbVTz9DsOnOJmlW71v4qH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/agkZziO4ZPAsVfKUrJD68lys08P.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Bambi[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0034492</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bambi</title>
	<year>1942</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bambi's tale unfolds from season to season as the young prince of the forest learns about life, love, and friends.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wV9e2y4myJ4KMFsyFfWYcUOawyK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1pVf2KhIa1oNHZac5nkt46jKaji.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Beauty and the Beast[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0101414</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Beauty and the Beast</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Follow the adventures of Belle, a bright young woman who finds herself in the castle of a prince who's been turned into a mysterious beast. With the help of the castle's enchanted staff, Belle soon learns the most important lesson of all -- that true beauty comes from within.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6DDJ8o2d6T4fpGWECLF4xBGTyAM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jsgRkhPxYtzAhDFCUyNbvlX63tY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Big Hero 6[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2245084</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Big Hero 6</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A special bond develops between plus-sized inflatable robot Baymax, and prodigy Hiro Hamada, who team up with a group of friends to form a band of high-tech heroes.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2mxS4wUimwlLmI1xp6QW6NSU361.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5tub2Kw6NboWFblA1CgDEwB59jP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Chicken Run[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120630</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Chicken Run</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Having been hopelessly repressed and facing eventual certain death at the British chicken farm where they are held, Ginger the chicken along with the help of Rocky the American rooster decide to rebel and lead their fellow chickens in a great escape from the murderous farmers Mr. and Mrs. Tweedy and their farm of doom.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sKr9uEqQ0NWQhb29XIJvpT43khk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t7aJ7hqsMLEoqBJk7yAXxcAVvcz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Coco[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2380307</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Coco</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Despite his family’s baffling generations-old ban on music, Miguel dreams of becoming an accomplished musician like his idol, Ernesto de la Cruz. Desperate to prove his talent, Miguel finds himself in the stunning and colorful Land of the Dead following a mysterious chain of events. Along the way, he meets charming trickster Hector, and together, they set off on an extraordinary journey to unlock the real story behind Miguel's family history.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gGEsBPAijhVUFoiNpgZXqRVWJt2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/askg3SMvhqEl4OL52YuvdtY40Yb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Coraline[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0327597</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Coraline</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young girl discovers an idealized parallel universe behind a secret door in her new home, unaware that it contains a sinister secret.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gPMh5rsVrDDAYMDbTcz6Up1DQ4z.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hofnlIyF6bePkgQOpcuRWLvzf15.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Duma[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0361715</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Duma</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An orphaned cheetah becomes the best friend and pet of a young boy living in South Africa.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/opoDxQW9S6SaiP8rY7urw16QVTL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/413WgZ1EE2REgBdqkxfTY0cvn4O.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dumbo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0033563</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dumbo</title>
	<year>1941</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Dumbo is a baby elephant born with over-sized ears and a supreme lack of confidence. But thanks to his even more diminutive buddy Timothy the Mouse,  the pint-sized pachyderm learns to surmount all obstacles.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hKDdllslMtsU9JixAv5HR9biXlp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eEKpOowAkVAF3sKJKqY2h4h12GV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083866</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An alien is left behind on Earth and saved by the 10-year-old Elliot who decides to keep him hidden in his home. While a task force hunts for the extra-terrestrial, Elliot, his brother, and his little sister Gertie form an emotional bond with their new friend, and try to help him find his way home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/an0nD6uq6byfxXCfk6lQBzdL2J1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mXLVA0YL6tcXi6SJSuAh9ONXFj5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Enchanted[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0461770</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Enchanted</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The beautiful princess Giselle is banished by an evil queen from her magical, musical animated land and finds herself in the gritty reality of the streets of modern-day Manhattan. Shocked by this strange new environment that doesn't operate on a "happily ever after" basis, Giselle is now adrift in a chaotic world badly in need of enchantment. But when Giselle begins to fall in love with a charmingly flawed divorce lawyer who has come to her aid - even though she is already promised to a perfect fairy tale prince back home - she has to wonder: Can a storybook view of romance survive in the real world?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8KCNzCArLlvLdQoHx6npua2VSVc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u4UpRDi0w84aNrigr9p049rMHiy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fantastic Mr. Fox[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0432283</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantastic Mr. Fox</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Fantastic Mr. Fox bored with his current life, plans a heist against the three local farmers. The farmers, tired of sharing their chickens with the sly fox, seek revenge against him and his family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/njbTizADSZg4PqeyJdDzZGooikv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qU4HDNKv7gjdlvMu74r70rISPwn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Finding Dory[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2277860</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Finding Dory</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Dory is reunited with her friends Nemo and Marlin in the search for answers about her past. What can she remember? Who are her parents? And where did she learn to speak Whale?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3UVe8NL1E2ZdUZ9EDlKGJY5UzE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1lqVrt3nEcAJV2GzKZfXvOsZcPQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Finding Nemo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0266543</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Finding Nemo</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Nemo, an adventurous young clownfish, is unexpectedly taken from his Great Barrier Reef home to a dentist's office aquarium. It's up to his worrisome father Marlin and a friendly but forgetful fish Dory to bring Nemo home -- meeting vegetarian sharks, surfer dude turtles, hypnotic jellyfish, hungry seagulls, and more along the way.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7DPFmp0q5RC1p582SdIuZ4KBF2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yzqaKAhglTrkeOfuIXYYArf0WnA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Frozen[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2294629</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Frozen</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Young princess Anna of Arendelle dreams about finding true love at her sister Elsa’s coronation. Fate takes her on a dangerous journey in an attempt to end the eternal winter that has fallen over the kingdom. She's accompanied by ice delivery man Kristoff, his reindeer Sven, and snowman Olaf. On an adventure where she will find out what friendship, courage, family, and true love really means.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kgwjIb2JDHRhNk13lmSxiClFjVk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9WHM084AoskcHCObAy4QnJg01eM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Frozen II[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4520988</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Frozen II</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Elsa, Anna, Kristoff and Olaf head far into the forest to learn the truth about an ancient mystery of their kingdom.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mINJaa34MtknCYl5AjtNJzWj8cD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AoSZyb37ljMAxw0RdeQEBHKtgcc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]How to Train Your Dragon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0892769</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>How to Train Your Dragon</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As the son of a Viking leader on the cusp of manhood, shy Hiccup Horrendous Haddock III faces a rite of passage: he must kill a dragon to prove his warrior mettle. But after downing a feared dragon, he realizes that he no longer wants to destroy it, and instead befriends the beast – which he names Toothless – much to the chagrin of his warrior father.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ygGmAO60t8GyqUo9xYeYxSZAR3b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aH9KWmXFMamXkHMgLjnQmSYjScL.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]How to Train Your Dragon 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1646971</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>How to Train Your Dragon 2</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Five years have passed since Hiccup and Toothless united the dragons and Vikings of Berk. Now, they spend their time charting unmapped territories. During one of their adventures, the pair discover a secret cave that houses hundreds of wild dragons -- and a mysterious dragon rider who turns out to be Hiccup's mother, Valka. Hiccup and Toothless then find themselves at the center of a battle to protect Berk from a power-hungry warrior named Drago.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d13Uj86LdbDLrfDoHR5aDOFYyJC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sKTFNMsuSgyAcwbD0xXVUXvvbY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Hugo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0970179</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hugo</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Orphaned and alone except for an uncle, Hugo Cabret lives in the walls of a train station in 1930s Paris. Hugo's job is to oil and maintain the station's clocks, but to him, his more important task is to protect a broken automaton and notebook left to him by his late father. Accompanied by the goddaughter of an embittered toy merchant, Hugo embarks on a quest to solve the mystery of the automaton and find a place he can call home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cFFkim9vRl250n50brtqfSvVF9k.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q7rVep73T1GDkPHGw3DjI0fPSkB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ice Age[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0268380</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ice Age</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>With the impending ice age almost upon them, a mismatched trio of prehistoric critters – Manny the woolly mammoth, Diego the saber-toothed tiger and Sid the giant sloth – find an orphaned infant and decide to return it to its human parents. Along the way, the unlikely allies become friends but, when enemies attack, their quest takes on far nobler aims.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gLhHHZUzeseRXShoDyC4VqLgsNv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a9ykRAWtQnI3SsZDfh8sCJo5cWI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1080016</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Times are changing for Manny the moody mammoth, Sid the motor mouthed sloth and Diego the crafty saber-toothed tiger. Life heats up for our heroes when they meet some new and none-too-friendly neighbors – the mighty dinosaurs.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cXOLaxcNjNAYmEx1trZxOTKhK3Q.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gkxSIlZPEwGPimQ8TEE8C52cOSO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ice Age: The Meltdown[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0438097</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ice Age: The Meltdown</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Diego, Manny and Sid return in this sequel to the hit animated movie Ice Age. This time around, the deep freeze is over, and the ice-covered earth is starting to melt, which will destroy the trio's cherished valley. The impending disaster prompts them to reunite and warn all the other beasts about the desperate situation.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vdluBXie4qDvh0dFX2Fpq8v16it.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wRTZaxAiDP0ZEeQsO0HiiSqYCSp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Incredibles 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3606756</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Incredibles 2</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Elastigirl springs into action to save the day, while Mr. Incredible faces his greatest challenge yet – taking care of the problems of his three children.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aTbRJHCrQwceSS5b8LYj7hC654I.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mabuNsGJgRuCTuGqjFkWe1xdu19.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Inside Out[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2096673</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Inside Out</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Growing up can be a bumpy road, and it's no exception for Riley, who is uprooted from her Midwest life when her father starts a new job in San Francisco. Riley's guiding emotions— Joy, Fear, Anger, Disgust and Sadness—live in Headquarters, the control centre inside Riley's mind, where they help advise her through everyday life and tries to keep things positive, but the emotions conflict on how best to navigate a new city, house and school.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2H1TmgdfNtsKlU9jKdeNyYL5y8T.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jJKZaTBNenlFclQyjrnvzkRmvWE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]James and the Giant Peach[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116683</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>James and the Giant Peach</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the young orphan boy James spills a magic bag of crocodile tongues, he finds himself in possession of a giant peach that flies him away to strange lands.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nl2oB6EbD1fHFuP2TLUHDtqs7Ux.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m8hh2IQTFqLN2EMDDiAngf6UYY8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Kung Fu Panda[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0441773</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Kung Fu Panda</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the Valley of Peace is threatened, lazy Po the panda discovers his destiny as the "chosen one" and trains to become a kung fu hero, but transforming the unsleek slacker into a brave warrior won't be easy. It's up to Master Shifu and the Furious Five -- Tigress, Crane, Mantis, Viper and Monkey -- to give it a try.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xCn3VOST64XpOA8x0gaQkQiZtZY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vndouqEyQqpvvk0FwIlkfceblrh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Kung Fu Panda 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1302011</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Kung Fu Panda 2</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Po is now living his dream as The Dragon Warrior, protecting the Valley of Peace alongside his friends and fellow kung fu masters, The Furious Five - Tigress, Crane, Mantis, Viper and Monkey. But Po’s new life of awesomeness is threatened by the emergence of a formidable villain, who plans to use a secret, unstoppable weapon to conquer China and destroy kung fu. It is up to Po and The Furious Five to journey across China to face this threat and vanquish it. But how can Po stop a weapon that can stop kung fu? He must look to his past and uncover the secrets of his mysterious origins; only then will he be able to unlock the strength he needs to succeed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mtqqD00vB4PGRt20gWtGqFhrkd0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7BdxZXbSkUiVeCRXKD3hi9KYeWm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Kung Fu Panda 3[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2267968</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Kung Fu Panda 3</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Continuing his "legendary adventures of awesomeness", Po must face two hugely epic, but different threats: one supernatural and the other a little closer to his home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oajNi4Su39WAByHI6EONu8G8HYn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uT5G4fA7jKxlJNfwYPMm353f5AI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Lady and the Tramp[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0048280</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lady and the Tramp</title>
	<year>1955</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Lady, a golden cocker spaniel, meets up with a mongrel dog who calls himself the Tramp. He is obviously from the wrong side of town, but happenings at Lady's home make her decide to travel with him for a while.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r9FiDSdBwNHdRwN0NMRrqfEHJGO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yGgEg4yimYQJLZrZg3Qhogp2raQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Lassie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0431213</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lassie</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A family in financial crisis is forced to sell Lassie, their beloved dog. Hundreds of miles away from her true family, Lassie escapes and sets out on a journey home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qB7NcROV5GzWLhHyFjSobPq9Eue.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ggVe1eacxS4D0Z805Liqecj6zHi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mary Poppins[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0058331</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mary Poppins</title>
	<year>1964</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Mr Banks is looking for a nanny for his two mischievous children and comes across Mary Poppins, an angelic nanny. She not only brings a change in their lives but also spreads happiness.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ei8hhYCMfURfPOXKBnyl61be2iV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/prVH6SyQ6yDmzVxxkcr57zhLM5C.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Moana[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3521164</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Moana</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In Ancient Polynesia, when a terrible curse incurred by Maui reaches an impetuous Chieftain's daughter's island, she answers the Ocean's call to seek out the demigod to set things right.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4JeejGugONWpJkbnvL12hVoYEDa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iYLKMV7PIBtFmtygRrhSiyzcVsF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]My Fair Lady[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0058385</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>My Fair Lady</title>
	<year>1964</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A snobbish phonetics professor agrees to a wager that he can take a flower girl and make her presentable in high society.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bTXVc29lGSNclf94VIZ49W4gGKl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xMoQjqa3JUc2unO4nF9PmM1JTQu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]One Hundred and One Dalmatians[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0055254</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>One Hundred and One Dalmatians</title>
	<year>1961</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a litter of dalmatian puppies are abducted by the minions of Cruella De Vil, the parents must find them before she uses them for a diabolical fashion statement.
 In a Disney animation classic, Dalmatian Pongo is tired of his bachelor-dog life. He spies lovely Perdita and maneuvers his master, Roger, into meeting Perdita's owner, Anita. The owners fall in love and marry, keeping Pongo and Perdita together too. After Perdita gives birth to a litter of 15 puppies, Anita's old school friend Cruella De Vil wants to buy them all. Roger declines her offer, so Cruella hires the criminal Badun brothers to steal them -- so she can have a fur coat.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mRY84MJeWKnp9joev82QtslJFvk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vlLW4BPPS6XL8mxAvoJSppJV3Sv.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Onward[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt7146812</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Onward</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a suburban fantasy world, two teenage elf brothers embark on an extraordinary quest to discover if there is still a little magic left out there.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f4aul3FyD3jv3v4bul1IrkWZvzq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xFxk4vnirOtUxpOEWgA1MCRfy6J.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Paddington[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1109624</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Paddington</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young Peruvian bear travels to London in search of a new home. Finding himself lost and alone at Paddington Station, he meets the kindly Brown family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wpchRGhRhvhtU083PfX2yixXtiw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kfofK4GzJsJZhCShqZY438c8Y4Y.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Paddington 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4468740</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Paddington 2</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Paddington, now happily settled with the Browns, picks up a series of odd jobs to buy the perfect present for his Aunt Lucy, but it is stolen.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1OJ9vkD5xPt3skC6KguyXAgagRZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zbdBYpte1Crlfjs8jPVzplOQBpN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pete's Dragon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2788732</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pete's Dragon</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For years, old wood carver Mr. Meacham has delighted local children with his tales of the fierce dragon that resides deep in the woods of the Pacific Northwest. To his daughter, Grace, who works as a forest ranger, these stories are little more than tall tales... until she meets Pete, a mysterious 10-year-old with no family and no home who claims to live in the woods with a giant, green dragon named Elliott. And from Pete's descriptions, Elliott seems remarkably similar to the dragon from Mr. Meacham's stories. With the help of Natalie, an 11-year-old girl whose father Jack owns the local lumber mill, Grace sets out to determine where Pete came from, where he belongs, and the truth about this dragon.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A9x4Ogk8KUXTfU649NS6lS9TCmu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ct9S0m2U2RTCFAVnq3y0nF0Tgb2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pinocchio[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0032910</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pinocchio</title>
	<year>1940</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Lonely toymaker Geppetto has his wishes answered when the Blue Fairy arrives to bring his wooden puppet Pinocchio to life. Before becoming a real boy, however, Pinocchio must prove he's worthy as he sets off on an adventure with his whistling sidekick and conscience, Jiminy Cricket.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bnZJrLRnoQHpzEJdka1KYfsAF3N.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1NQkxP7oe5iJHNb4ApqhlDFJ9dI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ralph Breaks the Internet[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5848272</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ralph Breaks the Internet</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Video game bad guy Ralph and fellow misfit Vanellope von Schweetz must risk it all by traveling to the World Wide Web in search of a replacement part to save Vanellope's video game, Sugar Rush. In way over their heads, Ralph and Vanellope rely on the citizens of the internet — the netizens — to help navigate their way, including an entrepreneur named Yesss, who is the head algorithm and the heart and soul of trend-making site BuzzzTube.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/44cb3fCGKUaSxxIjI2ejrgeYfye.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qDQEQbgP3v7B9IYLAUcYexNrVYP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ratatouille[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0382932</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ratatouille</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Remy, a resident of Paris, appreciates good food and has quite a sophisticated palate. He would love to become a chef so he can create and enjoy culinary masterpieces to his heart's delight. The only problem is, Remy is a rat. When he winds up in the sewer beneath one of Paris' finest restaurants, the rodent gourmet finds himself ideally placed to realize his dream.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t3vaWRPSf6WjDSamIkKDs1iQWna.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xgDj56UWyeWQcxQ44f5A3RTWuSs.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Shrek[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0126029</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shrek</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>It ain't easy bein' green -- especially if you're a likable (albeit smelly) ogre named Shrek. On a mission to retrieve a gorgeous princess from the clutches of a fire-breathing dragon, Shrek teams up with an unlikely compatriot -- a wisecracking donkey.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o04jZs5SXhbvhqO4981W7KJXOWZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bNTHSd3UqqLzIVwbDOGPnx3ScfF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Shrek 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0298148</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shrek 2</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Shrek, Fiona and Donkey set off to Far, Far Away to meet Fiona's mother and father. But not everyone is happy. Shrek and the King find it hard to get along, and there's tension in the marriage. The fairy godmother discovers that Shrek has married Fiona instead of her Son Prince Charming and sets about destroying their marriage.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2yYP0PQjG8zVqturh1BAqu2Tixl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l45UqyARB3WxpYNuACjMjndpe85.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Sleeping Beauty[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0053285</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Sleeping Beauty</title>
	<year>1959</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A beautiful princess born in a faraway kingdom is destined by a terrible curse to prick her finger on the spindle of a spinning wheel and fall into a deep sleep that can only be awakened by true love's first kiss. Determined to protect her, her parents ask three fairies to raise her in hiding. But the evil Maleficent is just as determined to seal the princess's fate.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e3K5cLvVRXVxhw4mXQET92p1dnz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4CryneVBqNPqmXR206snm7491gT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Soul[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2948372</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Soul</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Joe Gardner is a middle school teacher with a love for jazz music. After a successful audition at the Half Note Club, he suddenly gets into an accident that separates his soul from his body and is transported to the You Seminar, a center in which souls develop and gain passions before being transported to a newborn child. Joe must enlist help from the other souls-in-training, like 22, a soul who has spent eons in the You Seminar, in order to get back to Earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hm58Jw4Lw8OIeECIq5qyPYhAeRJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rQaHA74pevnGsxcKGaoZVGWe9TC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spy Kids[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0227538</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spy Kids</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Carmen and Juni think their parents are boring. Little do they know that in their day, Gregorio and Ingrid Cortez were the top secret agents from their respective countries. They gave up that life to raise their children. Now, the disappearances of several of their old colleagues forces the Cortez' return from retirement. What they didn't count on was Carmen and Juni joining the "family business."</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/urb5Wf4yffJQ2KwAuSPxCbOM8HA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eR0VaffxtxpUpzEsbww5nbAbQry.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tangled[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0398286</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tangled</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the kingdom's most wanted-and most charming-bandit Flynn Rider hides out in a mysterious tower, he's taken hostage by Rapunzel, a beautiful and feisty tower-bound teen with 70 feet of magical, golden hair. Flynn's curious captor, who's looking for her ticket out of the tower where she's been locked away for years, strikes a deal with the handsome thief and the unlikely duo sets off on an action-packed escapade, complete with a super-cop horse, an over-protective chameleon and a gruff gang of pub thugs.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ym7Kst6a4uodryxqbGOxmewF235.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cWczNud8Y8i8ab0Z4bxos4myWYO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Croods[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0481499</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Croods</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The prehistoric Croods family live in a particularly dangerous moment in time. Patriarch Grug, his mate Ugga, teenage daughter Eep, son Thunk, and feisty Gran gather food by day and huddle together in a cave at night. When a more evolved caveman named Guy arrives on the scene, Grug is distrustful, but it soon becomes apparent that Guy is correct about the impending destruction of their world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p7lJkqHlK01nr0zNacunUFI5Qxy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bNgqt819qpHcszjCzLCG5y16ldF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Croods: A New Age[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2850386</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Croods: A New Age</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Searching for a safer habitat, the prehistoric Crood family discovers an idyllic, walled-in paradise that meets all of its needs. Unfortunately, they must also learn to live with the Bettermans -- a family that's a couple of steps above the Croods on the evolutionary ladder. As tensions between the new neighbors start to rise, a new threat soon propels both clans on an epic adventure that forces them to embrace their differences, draw strength from one another, and survive together.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tbVZ3Sq88dZaCANlUcewQuHQOaE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ytTQoYkdpsgtfDWrNFCei8Mfbxu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Ice Age Adventures of Buck Wild[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt13634480</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Ice Age Adventures of Buck Wild</title>
	<year>2022</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The fearless one-eyed weasel Buck teams up with mischievous possum brothers Crash & Eddie as they head off on a new adventure into Buck's home: The Dinosaur World.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zzXFM4FKDG7l1ufrAkwQYv2xvnh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eG0oOQVsniPAuecPzDD1B1gnYWy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Incredibles[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0317705</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Incredibles</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bob Parr has given up his superhero days to log in time as an insurance adjuster and raise his three children with his formerly heroic wife in suburbia. But when he receives a mysterious assignment, it's time to get back into costume.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2LqaLgk4Z226KkgPJuiOQ58wvrm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/se5Hxz7PArQZOG3Nx2bpfOhLhtV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Iron Giant[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0129167</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Iron Giant</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the small town of Rockwell, Maine in October 1957, a giant metal machine befriends a nine-year-old boy and ultimately finds its humanity by unselfishly saving people from their own fears and prejudices.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ct04FCFLPImNG5thcPLRnVsZlmS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wfClZdRb1x4LZ8B73Y9RSn8XAPa.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Jungle Book[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0061852</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Jungle Book</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The boy Mowgli makes his way to the man-village with Bagheera, the wise panther. Along the way he meets jazzy King Louie, the hypnotic snake Kaa and the lovable, happy-go-lucky bear Baloo, who teaches Mowgli "The Bare Necessities" of life and the true meaning of friendship.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yN1kuupnPTLUprgfvC5WapgrxG4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zj8XS0l1cWStpKnuD1LFMB3VoV1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Kid Who Would Be King[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6811018</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Kid Who Would Be King</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Old-school magic meets the modern world when young Alex stumbles upon the mythical sword Excalibur. He soon unites his friends and enemies, and they become knights who join forces with the legendary wizard Merlin. Together, they must save mankind from the wicked enchantress Morgana and her army of supernatural warriors.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kBuvLX6zynQP0sjyqbXV4jNaZ4E.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9jRv507vXUJxOfD7fXYQKYFLC7q.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lego Batman Movie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4116284</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lego Batman Movie</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A cooler-than-ever Bruce Wayne must deal with the usual suspects as they plan to rule Gotham City, while discovering that he has accidentally adopted a teenage orphan who wishes to become his sidekick.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/snGwr2gag4Fcgx2OGmH9otl6ofW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eoMushgujydxFplE9yPZ54lwOvo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lego Movie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1490017</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lego Movie</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An ordinary Lego mini-figure, mistakenly thought to be the extraordinary MasterBuilder, is recruited to join a quest to stop an evil Lego tyrant from gluing the universe together.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9klB7qKC9aCeGyyM4uU5hSA6xDV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9531Jp42H0ppRXjkxxgCulnQNZp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lion King[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0110357</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lion King</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young lion prince is cast out of his pride by his cruel uncle, who claims he killed his father. While the uncle rules with an iron paw, the prince grows up beyond the Savannah, living by a philosophy: No worries for the rest of your days. But when his past comes to haunt him, the young prince must decide his fate: Will he remain an outcast or face his demons and become what he needs to be?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sKCr78MXSLixwmZ8DyJLrpMsd15.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wXsQvli6tWqja51pYxXNG1LFIGV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Little Mermaid[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0097757</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Little Mermaid</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>This colorful adventure tells the story of an impetuous mermaid princess named Ariel who falls in love with the very human Prince Eric and puts everything on the line for the chance to be with him. Memorable songs and characters -- including the villainous sea witch Ursula.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/plcZXvI310FkbwIptvd6rqk63LP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2ze42e0l0bPYEcJXInUukvNfZKk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Muppets[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1204342</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Muppets</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Kermit the Frog and the Muppets learn that their beloved theater is slated for demolition, a sympathetic human, Gary, and his puppet brother, Walter, swoop in to help the gang put on a show and raise the $10 million they need to save the day.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rsNbxonO8gtylIXwiv7JeqwJ4Kb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ysHWeVWSQZCIEBSEVf1nPddRn58.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Nightmare Before Christmas[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107688</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Nightmare Before Christmas</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Tired of scaring humans every October 31 with the same old bag of tricks, Jack Skellington, the spindly king of Halloween Town, kidnaps Santa Claus and plans to deliver shrunken heads and other ghoulish gifts to children on Christmas morning. But as Christmas approaches, Jack's rag-doll girlfriend, Sally, tries to foil his misguided plans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oQffRNjK8e19rF7xVYEN8ew0j7b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mWCoCdBumhNG3ZJAx0MS3JvaOXB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Peanuts Movie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2452042</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Peanuts Movie</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Snoopy embarks upon his greatest mission as he and his team take to the skies to pursue their arch-nemesis, while his best pal Charlie Brown begins his own epic quest.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/odpugRSNd7QCCxZqZZwv3vNEIph.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kbfPaXHnImSDSPgfmbbWjIDgwv8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Princess Bride[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093779</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Princess Bride</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In this enchantingly cracked fairy tale, the beautiful Princess Buttercup and the dashing Westley must overcome staggering odds to find happiness amid six-fingered swordsmen, murderous princes, Sicilians and rodents of unusual size. But even death can't stop these true lovebirds from triumphing.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dvjqlp2sAhUeFjUOfQDgqwpphHj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wD2Bp9RIF36EfsHiVqPNLq1SEOI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Wizard of Oz[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0032138</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wizard of Oz</title>
	<year>1939</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Young Dorothy finds herself in a magical world where she makes friends with a lion, a scarecrow and a tin man as they make their way along the yellow brick road to talk with the Wizard and ask for the things they miss most in their lives. The Wicked Witch of the West is the only thing that could stop them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bSA6DbAC5gdkaooU164lQUX6rVs.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zL4gtCeoPZkAFCKR0kNERpUiuPR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tom & Jerry[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1361336</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tom & Jerry</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Tom the cat and Jerry the mouse get kicked out of their home and relocate to a fancy New York hotel, where a scrappy employee named Kayla will lose her job if she can’t evict Jerry before a high-class wedding at the hotel. Her solution? Hiring Tom to get rid of the pesky mouse.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8XZI9QZ7Pm3fVkigWJPbrXCMzjq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9ns9463dwOeo1CK1JU2wirL5Yi1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Toy Story[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114709</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Toy Story</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Led by Woody, Andy's toys live happily in his room until Andy's birthday brings Buzz Lightyear onto the scene. Afraid of losing his place in Andy's heart, Woody plots against Buzz. But when circumstances separate Buzz and Woody from their owner, the duo eventually learns to put aside their differences.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uXDfjJbdP4ijW5hWSBrPrlKpxab.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3Rfvhy1Nl6sSGJwyjb0QiZzZYlB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Toy Story 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120363</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Toy Story 2</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Andy heads off to Cowboy Camp, leaving his toys to their own devices. Things shift into high gear when an obsessive toy collector named Al McWhiggen, owner of Al's Toy Barn kidnaps Woody. Andy's toys mount a daring rescue mission, Buzz Lightyear meets his match and Woody has to decide where he and his heart truly belong.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xVhEI1WCgNCCa5I86AqiwuZoog3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/91qfG6VaxRsCh1SbIi1w2vxknsL.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Toy Story 3[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0435761</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Toy Story 3</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Woody, Buzz, and the rest of Andy's toys haven't been played with in years. With Andy about to go to college, the gang find themselves accidentally left at a nefarious day care center. The toys must band together to escape and return home to Andy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AbbXspMOwdvwWZgVN0nabZq03Ec.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uAfhsySkr1UzQg1zdg3dZQRz9Fd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Toy Story 4[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1979376</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Toy Story 4</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Woody has always been confident about his place in the world and that his priority is taking care of his kid, whether that's Andy or Bonnie. But when Bonnie adds a reluctant new toy called "Forky" to her room, a road trip adventure alongside old and new friends will show Woody how big the world can be for a toy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/w9kR8qbmQ01HwnvK4alvnQ2ca0L.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q62bpQ67qaXY0u6b2wFEnQYIbPd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Up[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1049413</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Up</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Carl Fredricksen spent his entire life dreaming of exploring the globe and experiencing life to its fullest. But at age 78, life seems to have passed him by, until a twist of fate (and a persistent 8-year old Wilderness Explorer named Russell) gives him a new lease on life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vpbaStTMt8qqXaEgnOR2EE4DNJk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hGGC9gKo7CFE3fW07RA587e5kol.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Wallace & Gromit: The Curse of the Were-Rabbit[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0312004</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Wallace & Gromit: The Curse of the Were-Rabbit</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Cheese-loving eccentric Wallace and his cunning canine pal, Gromit, investigate a mystery in Nick Park's animated adventure, in which the lovable inventor and his intrepid pup run a business ridding the town of garden pests. Using only humane methods that turn their home into a halfway house for evicted vermin, the pair stumble upon a mystery involving a voracious vegetarian monster that threatens to ruin the annual veggie-growing contest.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hKwtMF4LdEl9sozLCr8Ur4l499p.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b1MAHWNzeJ8w9MqycPvJDdtu6Dq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Wreck-It Ralph[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1772341</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Wreck-It Ralph</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Wreck-It Ralph is the 9-foot-tall, 643-pound villain of an arcade video game named Fix-It Felix Jr., in which the game's titular hero fixes buildings that Ralph destroys. Wanting to prove he can be a good guy and not just a villain, Ralph escapes his game and lands in Hero's Duty, a first-person shooter where he helps the game's hero battle against alien invaders. He later enters Sugar Rush, a kart racing game set on tracks made of candies, cookies and other sweets. There, Ralph meets Vanellope von Schweetz who has learned that her game is faced with a dire threat that could affect the entire arcade, and one that Ralph may have inadvertently started.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zWoIgZ7mgmPkaZjG0102BSKFIqQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ziC23LkMYj8gToQQYQGWSGJCLNF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Yellow Submarine[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063823</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Yellow Submarine</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The wicked Blue Meanies take over Pepperland, eliminating all color and music. As the only survivor, the Lord Admiral escapes in the yellow submarine and journeys to Liverpool to enlist the help of the Beatles.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cjrGM2QYlwzV6vXz2yF7y6fdTRu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bkTfP6r7Vq6V0wXIuar7gb2inyb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
