<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120737</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Young hobbit Frodo Baggins, after inheriting a mysterious ring from his uncle Bilbo, must leave his home in order to keep it from falling into the hands of its evil creator. Along the way, a fellowship is formed to protect the ringbearer and make sure that the ring arrives at its final destination: Mt. Doom, the only place where it can be destroyed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6oom5QYQ2yQTMJIbnvbkBL9cHo6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tdmlSbLl84hfHx635AqHLB8Qh8M.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0167260</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Aragorn is revealed as the heir to the ancient kings as he, Gandalf and the other members of the broken fellowship struggle to save Gondor from Sauron's forces. Meanwhile, Frodo and Sam take the ring closer to the heart of Mordor, the dark lord's realm.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rCzpDGLbOoPwLjy3OAm5NUPOTrC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lXhgCODAbBXL5buk9yEmTpOoOgR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0167261</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Frodo and Sam are trekking to Mordor to destroy the One Ring of Power while Gimli, Legolas and Aragorn search for the orc-captured Merry and Pippin. All along, nefarious wizard Saruman awaits the Fellowship members at the Orthanc Tower in Isengard.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5VTN0pR8gcqV3EPUHHfMGnJYN9L.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kWYfW2Re0rUDE6IHhy4CRuKWeFr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0903624</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bilbo Baggins, a hobbit enjoying his quiet life, is swept into an epic quest by Gandalf the Grey and thirteen dwarves who seek to reclaim their mountain home from Smaug, the dragon.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yHA9Fc37VmpUA5UncTxxo3rTGVA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xyXmtuvsoM5J3yNad0nvcetpBdY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Hobbit: The Battle of the Five Armies[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2310332</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hobbit: The Battle of the Five Armies</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Immediately after the events of The Desolation of Smaug, Bilbo and the dwarves try to defend Erebor's mountain of treasure from others who claim it: the men of the ruined Laketown and the elves of Mirkwood. Meanwhile an army of Orcs led by Azog the Defiler is marching on Erebor, fueled by the rise of the dark lord Sauron. Dwarves, elves and men must unite, and the hope for Middle-Earth falls into Bilbo's hands.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xT98tLqatZPQApyRmlPL12LtiWp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zn13a7U9eMTJq8sHthe3bCgsVm4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1170358</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Dwarves, Bilbo and Gandalf have successfully escaped the Misty Mountains, and Bilbo has gained the One Ring. They all continue their journey to get their gold back from the Dragon, Smaug.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xQYiXsheRCDBA39DOrmaw1aSpbk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/npCPnwDyWfQltGfIZKN6WqeUXGI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
