<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spider-Man: No Way Home[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt10872600</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spider-Man: No Way Home</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Peter Parker is unmasked and no longer able to separate his normal life from the high-stakes of being a super-hero. When he asks for help from Doctor Strange the stakes become even more dangerous, forcing him to discover what it truly means to be Spider-Man.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uJYYizSuA9Y3DCs0qS4qWvHfZg4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/14QbnygCuTO0vl7CAFmPf1fgZfV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Eternals[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt9032400</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Eternals</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Eternals are a team of ancient aliens who have been living on Earth in secret for thousands of years. When an unexpected tragedy forces them out of the shadows, they are forced to reunite against mankind’s most ancient enemy, the Deviants.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lFByFSLV5WDJEv3KabbdAF959F2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c6H7Z4u73ir3cIoCteuhJh7UCAR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Shang-Chi and the Legend of the Ten Rings[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt9376612</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shang-Chi and the Legend of the Ten Rings</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Shang-Chi must confront the past he thought he left behind when he is drawn into the web of the mysterious Ten Rings organization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1BIoJGKbXjdFDAqUEiA2VHqkK1Z.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zxWAv1A34kdYslBi4ekMDtgIGUt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Black Widow[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3480822</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Black Widow</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Natasha Romanoff, also known as Black Widow, confronts the darker parts of her ledger when a dangerous conspiracy with ties to her past arises. Pursued by a force that will stop at nothing to bring her down, Natasha must deal with her history as a spy and the broken relationships left in her wake long before she became an Avenger.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kwB7d51AIcyzPOBOHLCEZJkmPhQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/keIxh0wPr2Ymj0Btjh4gW7JJ89e.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spider-Man: Far from Home[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6320628</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spider-Man: Far from Home</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Peter Parker and his friends go on a summer trip to Europe. However, they will hardly be able to rest - Peter will have to agree to help Nick Fury uncover the mystery of creatures that cause natural disasters and destruction throughout the continent.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4q2NNj4S5dG2RLF9CpXsej7yXl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ng6SSB3JhbcpKTwbPDsRwUYK8Cq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Avengers: Endgame[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4154796</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War, the universe is in ruins due to the efforts of the Mad Titan, Thanos. With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers must assemble once more in order to undo Thanos' actions and restore order to the universe once and for all, no matter what consequences may be in store.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/or06FN3Dka5tukK1e9sl16pB3iy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7RyHsO4yDXtBv1zUU3mTpHeQ0d5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Captain Marvel[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4154664</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Captain Marvel</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The story follows Carol Danvers as she becomes one of the universe’s most powerful heroes when Earth is caught in the middle of a galactic war between two alien races. Set in the 1990s, Captain Marvel is an all-new adventure from a previously unseen period in the history of the Marvel Cinematic Universe.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AtsgWhDnHTq68L0lLsUrCnM7TjG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/w2PMyoyLU22YvrGK3smVM9fW1jj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ant-Man and the Wasp[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5095030</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ant-Man and the Wasp</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Just when his time under house arrest is about to end, Scott Lang once again puts his freedom at risk to help Hope van Dyne and Dr. Hank Pym dive into the quantum realm and try to accomplish, against time and any chance of success, a very dangerous rescue mission.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4YDAODnSkxtPjvDDSJjm1JLIz0i.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iYdgEUE2W2aJkgqfSjf1x3gFfuV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Avengers: Infinity War[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4154756</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avengers: Infinity War</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7WsyChQLEftFiDOVTGkv3hFpyyt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mDfJG3LC3Dqb67AZ52x3Z0jU0uB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Black Panther[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1825683</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Black Panther</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>King T'Challa returns home to the reclusive, technologically advanced African nation of Wakanda to serve as his country's new leader. However, T'Challa soon finds that he is challenged for the throne by factions within his own country as well as without. Using powers reserved to Wakandan kings, T'Challa assumes the Black Panther mantle to join with ex-girlfriend Nakia, the queen-mother, his princess-kid sister, members of the Dora Milaje (the Wakandan 'special forces') and an American secret agent, to prevent Wakanda from being dragged into a world war.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uxzzxijgPIY7slzFvMotPv8wjKA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b6ZJZHUdMEFECvGiDpJjlfUWela.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Thor: Ragnarok[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3501632</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Thor: Ragnarok</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Thor is imprisoned on the other side of the universe and finds himself in a race against time to get back to Asgard to stop Ragnarok, the destruction of his home-world and the end of Asgardian civilization, at the hands of a powerful new threat, the ruthless Hela.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rzRwTcFvttcN1ZpX2xv4j3tSdJu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kaIfm5ryEOwYg8mLbq8HkPuM1Fo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spider-Man: Homecoming[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2250912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Following the events of Captain America: Civil War, Peter Parker, with the help of his mentor Tony Stark, tries to balance his life as an ordinary high school student in Queens, New York City, with fighting crime as his superhero alter ego Spider-Man as a new threat, the Vulture, emerges.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c24sv2weTHPsmDa7jEMN0m2P3RT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fn4n6uOYcB6Uh89nbNPoU2w80RV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3896198</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Guardians must fight to keep their newfound family together as they unravel the mysteries of Peter Quill's true parentage.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y4MBh0EjBlMuOzv9axM4qJlmhzz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aJn9XeesqsrSLKcHfHP4u5985hn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Logan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3315342</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Logan</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the near future, a weary Logan cares for an ailing Professor X in a hideout on the Mexican border. But Logan's attempts to hide from the world and his legacy are upended when a young mutant arrives, pursued by dark forces.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fnbjcRDYn6YviCcePDnGdyAkYsB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9X7YweCJw3q8Mcf6GadxReFEksM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Doctor Strange[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1211837</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Doctor Strange</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After his career is destroyed, a brilliant but arrogant surgeon gets a new lease on life when a sorcerer takes him under her wing and trains him to defend the world against evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uGBVj3bEbCoZbDjjl9wTxcygko1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qUv51IFUvVRAP2379ThmA3eLJx6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X-Men: Apocalypse[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3385516</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X-Men: Apocalypse</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After the re-emergence of the world's first mutant, world-destroyer Apocalypse, the X-Men must unite to defeat his extinction level plan.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lRxsDK4exeEgKoXqI4zdr0Vl0yk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sTQNRqLbfCXolrb5CizAW1dj528.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Captain America: Civil War[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3498820</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Captain America: Civil War</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Following the events of Age of Ultron, the collective governments of the world pass an act designed to regulate all superhuman activity. This polarizes opinion amongst the Avengers, causing two factions to side with Iron Man or Captain America, which causes an epic battle between former allies.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rAGiXaUfPzY7CDEyNKUofk3Kw2e.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wdwcOBMkt3zmPQuEMxB3FUtMio2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Deadpool[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1431045</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Deadpool</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who, after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter ego Deadpool. Armed with his new abilities and a dark, twisted sense of humor, Deadpool hunts down the man who nearly destroyed his life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fSRb7vyIP8rQpL0I47P3qUsEKX3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/en971MEXui9diirXlogOrPKmsEn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fantastic Four[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1502712</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantastic Four</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Four young outsiders teleport to a dangerous universe, which alters their physical form in shocking ways. Their lives irrevocably upended, the team must learn to harness their daunting new abilities and work together to save Earth from a former friend turned enemy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oeMpEsjmiT9PEJbRM1Fm7TZ1dE0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gzhVcfC5j0sTnS4WJzBrCS0Vkr0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ant-Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0478970</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ant-Man</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Armed with the astonishing ability to shrink in scale but increase in strength, master thief Scott Lang must embrace his inner-hero and help his mentor, Doctor Hank Pym, protect the secret behind his spectacular Ant-Man suit from a new generation of towering threats. Against seemingly insurmountable obstacles, Pym and Lang must plan and pull off a heist that will save the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4Ky7xCXPMKXGopstPjwPRd4ZDrj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a7sAqMKv5tkAdMzFfIhPqIBmQ9g.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Avengers: Age of Ultron[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2395427</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avengers: Age of Ultron</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Tony Stark tries to jumpstart a dormant peacekeeping program, things go awry and Earth’s Mightiest Heroes are put to the ultimate test as the fate of the planet hangs in the balance. As the villainous Ultron emerges, it is up to The Avengers to stop him from enacting his terrible plans, and soon uneasy alliances and unexpected action pave the way for an epic and unique global adventure.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4ssDuvEDkSArWEdyBl2X5EHvYKU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6YwkGolwdOMNpbTOmLjoehlVWs5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Guardians of the Galaxy[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2015381</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Light years from Earth, 26 years after being abducted, Peter Quill finds himself the prime target of a manhunt after discovering an orb wanted by Ronan the Accuser.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r7vmZjiyZw9rpJMQJdXpjgiCOk9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2UFxrUHVuSK3Tth7DvQQlF4mGTd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X-Men: Days of Future Past[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1877832</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X-Men: Days of Future Past</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The ultimate X-Men ensemble fights a war for the survival of the species across two time periods as they join forces with their younger selves in an epic battle that must change the past – to save our future.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tYfijzolzgoMOtegh1Y7j2Enorg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fctQU5MoXgJ5pNMljFzlEFXwfSu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Amazing Spider-Man 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1872181</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Amazing Spider-Man 2</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For Peter Parker, life is busy. Between taking out the bad guys as Spider-Man and spending time with the person he loves, Gwen Stacy, high school graduation cannot come quickly enough. Peter has not forgotten about the promise he made to Gwen’s father to protect her by staying away, but that is a promise he cannot keep. Things will change for Peter when a new villain, Electro, emerges, an old friend, Harry Osborn, returns, and Peter uncovers new clues about his past.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c3e9e18SSlvFd1cQaGmUj5tqL5P.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mPyiNWS0upEG1mGKOKyCQSoZpnp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Captain America: The Winter Soldier[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1843866</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Captain America: The Winter Soldier</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After the cataclysmic events in New York with The Avengers, Steve Rogers, aka Captain America is living quietly in Washington, D.C. and trying to adjust to the modern world. But when a S.H.I.E.L.D. colleague comes under attack, Steve becomes embroiled in a web of intrigue that threatens to put the world at risk. Joining forces with the Black Widow, Captain America struggles to expose the ever-widening conspiracy while fighting off professional assassins sent to silence him at every turn. When the full scope of the villainous plot is revealed, Captain America and the Black Widow enlist the help of a new ally, the Falcon. However, they soon find themselves up against an unexpected and formidable enemy—the Winter Soldier.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tVFRpFw3xTedgPGqxW0AOI8Qhh0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yHB0eNR8rvCpn0VdghEwBsXAC0N.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Thor: The Dark World[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1981115</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Thor: The Dark World</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Thor fights to restore order across the cosmos… but an ancient race led by the vengeful Malekith returns to plunge the universe back into darkness. Faced with an enemy that even Odin and Asgard cannot withstand, Thor must embark on his most perilous and personal journey yet, one that will reunite him with Jane Foster and force him to sacrifice everything to save us all.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wp6OxE4poJ4G7c0U2ZIXasTSMR7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4zTsF0RtO0av3YX1NaKDqGKPxYF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Wolverine[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1430132</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wolverine</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Wolverine faces his ultimate nemesis - and tests of his physical, emotional, and mortal limits - in a life-changing voyage to modern-day Japan.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xNi8daRmN4XY8rXHd4rwLbJf1cU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7D2PgX369YYePs4m44IQvROWM42.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Iron Man 3[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1300854</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Iron Man 3</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Tony Stark's world is torn apart by a formidable terrorist called the Mandarin, he starts an odyssey of rebuilding and retribution.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qhPtAc1TKbMPqNvcdXSOn9Bn7hZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tKa1gmGKAUVYnflYcadipeL3d9h.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Amazing Spider-Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0948470</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Amazing Spider-Man</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Peter Parker is an outcast high schooler abandoned by his parents as a boy, leaving him to be raised by his Uncle Ben and Aunt May. Like most teenagers, Peter is trying to figure out who he is and how he got to be the person he is today. As Peter discovers a mysterious briefcase that belonged to his father, he begins a quest to understand his parents' disappearance – leading him directly to Oscorp and the lab of Dr. Curt Connors, his father's former partner. As Spider-Man is set on a collision course with Connors' alter ego, The Lizard, Peter will make life-altering choices to use his powers and shape his destiny to become a hero.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jIfkQNARYyERqRAq1p1c8xgePp4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sLWUtbrpiLp23a0XDSiUiltdFPJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Avengers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0848228</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Avengers</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When an unexpected enemy emerges and threatens global safety and security, Nick Fury, director of the international peacekeeping agency known as S.H.I.E.L.D., finds himself in need of a team to pull the world back from the brink of disaster. Spanning the globe, a daring recruitment effort begins!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/RYMX2wcKCBAr24UyPD7xwmjaTn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9BBTo63ANSmhC4e6r62OJFuK2GL.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1071875</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the devil resurfaces with aims to take over the world in human form, Johnny Blaze reluctantly comes out of hiding to transform into the flame-spewing supernatural hero Ghost Rider -- and rescue a 10-year-old boy from an unsavory end.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fDtIZXLNreDHk3mOskJYABrQNOQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aHc765LRg5d5DtoS4LKiGEROWrq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Captain America: The First Avenger[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0458339</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Captain America: The First Avenger</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During World War II, Steve Rogers is a sickly man from Brooklyn who's transformed into super-soldier Captain America to aid in the war effort. Rogers must stop the Red Skull – Adolf Hitler's ruthless head of weaponry, and the leader of an organization that intends to use a mysterious device of untold powers for world domination.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vSNxAJTlD0r02V9sPYpOjqDZXUK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yFuKvT4Vm3sKHdFY4eG6I4ldAnn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X-Men: First Class[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1270798</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X-Men: First Class</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Before Charles Xavier and Erik Lensherr took the names Professor X and Magneto, they were two young men discovering their powers for the first time. Before they were arch-enemies, they were closest of friends, working together with other mutants (some familiar, some new), to stop the greatest threat the world has ever known.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vUvlOY575rztBuJV3a0dbHW5MQR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bMiOfPhplZu1Lql3hGTRV087QA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Thor[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0800369</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Thor</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Against his father Odin's will, The Mighty Thor - a powerful but arrogant warrior god - recklessly reignites an ancient war. Thor is cast down to Earth and forced to live among humans as punishment. Once here, Thor learns what it takes to be a true hero when the most dangerous villain of his world sends the darkest forces of Asgard to invade Earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/prSfAi1xGrhLQNxVSUFh61xQ4Qy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cDJ61O1STtbWNBwefuqVrRe3d7l.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Iron Man 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1228705</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Iron Man 2</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>With the world now aware of his dual life as the armored superhero Iron Man, billionaire inventor Tony Stark faces pressure from the government, the press and the public to share his technology with the military. Unwilling to let go of his invention, Stark, with Pepper Potts and James 'Rhodey' Rhodes at his side, must forge new alliances – and confront powerful enemies.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6WBeq4fCfn7AN0o21W9qNcRF2l9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7lmBufEG7P7Y1HClYK3gCxYrkgS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X-Men Origins: Wolverine[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0458525</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X-Men Origins: Wolverine</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After seeking to live a normal life, Logan sets out to avenge the death of his girlfriend by undergoing the mutant Weapon X program and becoming Wolverine.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yj8LbTju1p7CUJg7US2unSBk33s.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wvqdJLVh0mSblly7UnYFPEk04Wd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Punisher: War Zone[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0450314</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Punisher: War Zone</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Waging his one-man war on the world of organized crime, ruthless vigilante-hero Frank Castle sets his sights on overeager mob boss Billy Russoti. After Russoti is left horribly disfigured by Castle, he sets out for vengeance under his new alias: Jigsaw. With the "Punisher Task Force" hot on his trail and the FBI unable to take Jigsaw in, Frank must stand up to the formidable army that Jigsaw has recruited before more of his evil deeds go unpunished.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oOvKJgYUIpfswGHAdW6159bPbvM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dqPZpQy6PJINOJtld17NgIERusH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Incredible Hulk[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0800080</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Incredible Hulk</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Scientist Bruce Banner scours the planet for an antidote to the unbridled force of rage within him: the Hulk. But when the military masterminds who dream of exploiting his powers force him back to civilization, he finds himself coming face to face with a new, deadly foe.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gKzYx79y0AQTL4UAk1cBQJ3nvrm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jPu8yiadqgzwFPGKJmGo637ASVP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Iron Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0371746</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Iron Man</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After being held captive in an Afghan cave, billionaire engineer Tony Stark creates a unique weaponized suit of armor to fight evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/78lPtwv72eTNqFW9COBYI0dWDJa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cyecB7godJ6kNHGONFjUyVN9OX5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0486576</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Fantastic Four return to the big screen as a new and all powerful enemy threatens the Earth. The seemingly unstoppable 'Silver Surfer', but all is not what it seems and there are old and new enemies that pose a greater threat than the intrepid superheroes realize.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9wRfzTcMyyzkQxVDqBHv8RwuZOv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ff2FyFmskEFfmXHkxuqVr47DiG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spider-Man 3[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0413300</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spider-Man 3</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The seemingly invincible Spider-Man goes up against an all-new crop of villains—including the shape-shifting Sandman. While Spider-Man’s superpowers are altered by an alien organism, his alter ego, Peter Parker, deals with nemesis Eddie Brock and also gets caught up in a love triangle.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qFmwhVUoUSXjkKRmca5yGDEXBIj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6MQmtWk4cFwSDyNvIgoJRBIHUT3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ghost Rider[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0259324</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ghost Rider</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In order to save his dying father, young stunt cyclist Johnny Blaze sells his soul to Mephistopheles and sadly parts from the pure-hearted Roxanne Simpson, the love of his life. Years later, Johnny's path crosses again with Roxanne, now a go-getting reporter, and also with Mephistopheles, who offers to release Johnny's soul if Johnny becomes the fabled, fiery 'Ghost Rider'.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8LaVQiXBsnlo7MXCPK1nXTVARUZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7zS58YPAw002RNejOF1vNB3XHbW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X-Men: The Last Stand[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0376994</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X-Men: The Last Stand</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a cure is found to treat mutations, lines are drawn amongst the X-Men—led by Professor Charles Xavier—and the Brotherhood, a band of powerful mutants organised under Xavier's former ally, Magneto.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7RSSkRpwvkNN5iKO8zACtBA0KhQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nYJ9hQe6F82bem3ufHAWBRyYm9m.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fantastic Four[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120667</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantastic Four</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During a space voyage, four scientists are altered by cosmic rays: Reed Richards gains the ability to stretch his body; Sue Storm can become invisible; Johnny Storm controls fire; and Ben Grimm is turned into a super-strong … thing. Together, these "Fantastic Four" must now thwart the evil plans of Dr. Doom and save the world from certain destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8HLQLILZLhDQWO6JDpvY6XJLH75.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jkBEPKRq4HWlLwsMFMdDiYwaCle.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Elektra[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0357277</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Elektra</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Elektra the warrior survives a near-death experience, becomes an assassin-for-hire, and tries to protect her two latest targets, a single father and his young daughter, from a group of supernatural assassins.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9Azi1GBNj3gPPwmQWAMcATg7JOl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A8I20DNPLcusT0YFBAe1WumXiyU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade: Trinity[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0359013</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade: Trinity</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For years, Blade has fought against the vampires in the cover of the night. But now, after falling into the crosshairs of the FBI, he is forced out into the daylight, where he is driven to join forces with a clan of human vampire hunters he never knew existed—The Nightstalkers. Together with Abigail and Hannibal, two deftly trained Nightstalkers, Blade follows a trail of blood to the ancient creature that is also hunting him—the original vampire, Dracula.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rodqqX8NLe3cdcgBMc4CFTPidTy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/55885wQeb8XISRccwnfVJ7DDJFM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spider-Man 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0316654</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spider-Man 2</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Peter Parker is going through a major identity crisis. Burned out from being Spider-Man, he decides to shelve his superhero alter ego, which leaves the city suffering in the wake of carnage left by the evil Doc Ock. In the meantime, Parker still can't act on his feelings for Mary Jane Watson, a girl he's loved since childhood. A certain anger begins to brew in his best friend Harry Osborn as well...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/olxpyq9kJAZ2NU1siLshhhXEPR7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6al048Lat3eLVQOuKtc9h6Tu94d.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Punisher[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0330793</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Punisher</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When undercover FBI agent Frank Castle's wife and son are slaughtered, he becomes 'the Punisher' -- a ruthless vigilante willing to go to any length to avenge his family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7rmA1HwYp2GKM85BL0cVwCaosGr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4iypY05iUKFh3luIiVAGUofvsCb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Hulk[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0286716</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hulk</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Bruce Banner, a genetics researcher with a tragic past, suffers massive radiation exposure in his laboratory that causes him to transform into a raging green monster when he gets angry.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qnngKqAcqfH2pBxDoKu5lxzSbTo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kYd1ZMWvG9K2Jeop3XWXcTpJ2dB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0290334</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X2</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Professor Charles Xavier and his team of genetically gifted superheroes face a rising tide of anti-mutant sentiment led by Col. William Stryker. Storm, Wolverine and Jean Grey must join their usual nemeses—Magneto and Mystique—to unhinge Stryker's scheme to exterminate all mutants.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rtrd4qieMAhoUshu83Vi1GazM1O.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/loixNIKBURXfPcND4noz7E8FqCS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Daredevil[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0287978</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Daredevil</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A man blinded in a childhood accident fights crime using his superhumanly-elevated remaining senses.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oCDBwSkntYamuw8VJIxMRCtDBmi.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e7jIX02GiSwsgkU5lMpeKjwq2Zc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spider-Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0145487</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spider-Man</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After being bitten by a genetically altered spider at Oscorp, nerdy but endearing high school student Peter Parker is endowed with amazing powers to become the superhero known as Spider-Man.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gh4cZbhZxyTbgxQPxD0dOudNPTn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nyBtN2QqimXKZwYc7iTJlt18CfY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade II[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0187738</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade II</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A rare mutation has occurred within the vampire community - The Reaper. A vampire so consumed with an insatiable bloodlust that they prey on vampires as well as humans, transforming victims who are unlucky enough to survive into Reapers themselves. Blade is asked by the Vampire Nation for his help in preventing a nightmare plague that would wipe out both humans and vampires.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yDHwo3eWcMiy5LnnEnlGV9iLu9k.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g8cjJHZFeZQ5GRbFiDp5jXgfOZW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]X-Men[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120903</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>X-Men</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Two mutants, Rogue and Wolverine, come to a private academy for their kind whose resident superhero team, the X-Men, must oppose a terrorist organization with similar powers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bRDAc4GogyS9ci3ow7UnInOcriN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yGxMIIDSUvaXUjjJuIYZi40Jt3J.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120611</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Daywalker known as "Blade" - a half-vampire, half-mortal man - becomes the protector of humanity against an underground army of vampires.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hx0sdduAsr4rq03RZKZzglR25z7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hZnnUq0mrUQ3e54SJVca4mf2oAQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fantastic Four[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0109770</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fantastic Four</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Fantastic Four is an unreleased low-budget feature film completed in 1994. Created to secure copyright to the property, the producers never intended it for release although the director, actors, and other participants were not informed of this fact. It was produced by low-budget specialist Roger Corman and Bernd Eichinger (who also produced the 2005 Fantastic Four movie).</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2jJoV3Lze514jOAPagF4Fkp5Cl8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wQNYzjQKSZZ1eDJ0w1O62HPFDfN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Captain America[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103923</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Captain America</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During World War II, a brave, patriotic American Soldier undergoes experiments to become a new supersoldier, "Captain America". Racing to Germany to sabotage the rockets of Nazi baddie "Red Skull", Captain America winds up frozen until the 1990s. He reawakens to find that the Red Skull has changed identities and is now planning to kidnap the President of the United States.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lvHr3y3g63hrpXI3pSCLF62tRSZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/GfYVmaRWrNzOfyuoCvtFquaPLW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Punisher[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0098141</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Punisher</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The avenging angel of Marvel Comics fame comes brilliantly to life in this searing action-adventure thriller! Dolph Lundgren stars as Frank Castle, a veteran cop who loses his entire family to a mafia car bomb. His ex-partner believes Castle survived the blast and became the Punisher, living in the sewers and exacting vigilante violence against mob bosses throughout the city. When the populace is caught in the midst of a gang war that he caused, Castle must again emerge from the shadows and save the innocent.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/94uI2GcM1Za0dJVUSSuyI8gvQgX.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tFmrdnfXM0p6ihMTFpptYOKEfSl.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Howard the Duck[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091225</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Howard the Duck</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A scientific experiment unknowingly brings extraterrestrial life forms to the Earth through a laser beam. First is the cigar smoking drake Howard from the duck's planet. A few kids try to keep him from the greedy scientists and help him back to his planet. But then a much less friendly being arrives through the beam...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/30tnH0hy6S5FjGCfCdnkBd3wqS2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t3wX0hMH0esnx4SZEbugYCnCoMl.jpg</fanart>
</item>
