<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]2001: A Space Odyssey[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0062622</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>2001: A Space Odyssey</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Humanity finds a mysterious object buried beneath the lunar surface and sets off to find its origins with the help of HAL 9000, the world's most advanced super computer.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ve72VxNqjGM69Uky4WTo2bK6rfq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kCEXA22ASuq7Y29jnngyaisyA0X.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]A Clockwork Orange[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0066921</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Clockwork Orange</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a near-future Britain, young Alexander DeLarge and his pals get their kicks beating and raping anyone they please. When not destroying the lives of others, Alex swoons to the music of Beethoven. The state, eager to crack down on juvenile crime, gives an incarcerated Alex the option to undergo an invasive procedure that'll rob him of all personal agency. In a time when conscience is a commodity, can Alex change his tune?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4sHeTAp65WrSSuc05nRBKddhBxO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bR4U9n9YnZOvBUhOUNl316UNEyh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]A.I. Artificial Intelligence[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0212720</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A.I. Artificial Intelligence</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>David, a robotic boy—the first of his kind programmed to love—is adopted as a test case by a Cybertronics employee and his wife. Though he gradually becomes their child, a series of unexpected circumstances make this life impossible for David. Without final acceptance by humans or machines, David embarks on a journey to discover where he truly belongs, uncovering a world in which the line between robot and machine is both vast and profoundly thin.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8MZSGX5JORoO72EfuAEcejH5yHn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n7p6UTAZtkeoHkwCO42BEQaMFJY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Aliens[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090605</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aliens</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Ripley's lifepod is found by a salvage crew over 50 years later, she finds that terra-formers are on the very planet they found the alien species. When the company sends a family of colonists out to investigate her story—all contact is lost with the planet and colonists. They enlist Ripley and the colonial marines to return and search for answers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r1x5JGpyqZU8PYhbs4UcrO1Xb6x.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jMBpJFRtrtIXymer93XLavPwI3P.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Another Earth[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1549572</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Another Earth</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>On the night of the discovery of a duplicate Earth in the Solar system, an ambitious young student and an accomplished composer cross paths in a tragic accident.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvGJK3lFzpifAdyIupMNdWNX0qr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fJfpZnS2pvFCtyaDqoIgKLASvAT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Armageddon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120591</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Armageddon</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When an asteroid threatens to collide with Earth, NASA honcho Dan Truman determines the only way to stop it is to drill into its surface and detonate a nuclear bomb. This leads him to renowned driller Harry Stamper, who agrees to helm the dangerous space mission provided he can bring along his own hotshot crew. Among them is the cocksure A.J. who Harry thinks isn't good enough for his daughter, until the mission proves otherwise.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eTM3qtGhDU8cvjpoa6KEt5E2auU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sODk4VuMTt8S56zYFOr1Kx8BFqu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Avatar[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0499549</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avatar</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the 22nd century, a paraplegic Marine is dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission, but becomes torn between following orders and protecting an alien civilization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jRXYjXNq0Cs2TcJjLkki24MLp7u.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8I37NtDffNV7AZlDa7uDvvqhovU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Back to the Future[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088763</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Back to the Future</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Eighties teenager Marty McFly is accidentally sent back in time to 1955, inadvertently disrupting his parents' first meeting and attracting his mother's romantic interest. Marty must repair the damage to history by rekindling his parents' romance and - with the help of his eccentric inventor friend Doc Brown - return to 1985.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fNOH9f1aA7XRTzl1sAOx9iF553Q.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5bzPWQ2dFUl2aZKkp7ILJVVkRed.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Back to the Future Part II[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096874</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Back to the Future Part II</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Marty and Doc are at it again in this wacky sequel to the 1985 blockbuster as the time-traveling duo head to 2015 to nip some McFly family woes in the bud. But things go awry thanks to bully Biff Tannen and a pesky sports almanac. In a last-ditch attempt to set things straight, Marty finds himself bound for 1955 and face to face with his teenage parents -- again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hQq8xZe5uLjFzSBt4LanNP7SQjl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iGkZLNllCJH9QqKIAIkg5NSy8I6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Back to the Future Part III[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0099088</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Back to the Future Part III</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The final installment of the Back to the Future trilogy finds Marty digging the trusty DeLorean out of a mineshaft and looking for Doc in the Wild West of 1885. But when their time machine breaks down, the travelers are stranded in a land of spurs. More problems arise when Doc falls for pretty schoolteacher Clara Clayton, and Marty tangles with Buford Tannen.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/crzoVQnMzIrRfHtQw0tLBirNfVg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vKp3NvqBkcjHkCHSGi6EbcP7g4J.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade Runner[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083658</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade Runner</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the smog-choked dystopian Los Angeles of 2019, blade runner Rick Deckard is called out of retirement to terminate a quartet of replicants who have escaped to Earth seeking their creator for a way to extend their short life spans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/63N9uy8nd9j7Eog2axPQ8lbr3Wj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wfQTVBIQj1wJUe0jV3OZ4zOivIO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade Runner 2049[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1856101</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade Runner 2049</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Thirty years after the events of the first film, a new blade runner, LAPD Officer K, unearths a long-buried secret that has the potential to plunge what's left of society into chaos. K's discovery leads him on a quest to find Rick Deckard, a former LAPD blade runner who has been missing for 30 years.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gajva2L0rPYkEWjzgFlBXCAVBE5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sAtoMqDVhNDQBc3QJL3RF6hlhGq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Children of Men[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0206634</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Children of Men</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 2027, in a chaotic world in which humans can no longer procreate, a former activist agrees to help transport a miraculously pregnant woman to a sanctuary at sea, where her child's birth may help scientists save the future of humankind.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k9IAS4TehZFcKi4HVByxZNPfqex.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7cW7zHpDdl9fgaRXI5qAglV247P.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Close Encounters of the Third Kind[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075860</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Close Encounters of the Third Kind</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After an encounter with UFOs, an electricity linesman feels undeniably drawn to an isolated area in the wilderness where something spectacular is about to happen.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4zfedS25uMAhgm6YQhc9bhKHbLl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u9ZLyLvqHY5VDjn0Rs4LKAklsAV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Cloverfield[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1060277</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Cloverfield</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Five young New Yorkers throw their friend a going-away party the night that a monster the size of a skyscraper descends upon the city. Told from the point of view of their video camera, the film is a document of their attempt to survive the most surreal, horrifying event of their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qIegUGJqyMMCRjkKV1s7A9MqdJ8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6ms6RdNcQUAnjBY26aM85xC2wV0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Contact[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0118884</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Contact</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A radio astronomer receives the first extraterrestrial radio signal ever picked up on Earth. As the world powers scramble to decipher the message and decide upon a course of action, she must make some difficult decisions between her beliefs, the truth, and reality.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bCpMIywuNZeWt3i5UMLEIc0VSwM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x5Z2BjuUfEEwYWZccDwbU9KSEqj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Deep Impact[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120647</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Deep Impact</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A seven-mile-wide space rock is hurtling toward Earth, threatening to obliterate the planet. Now, it's up to the president of the United States to save the world. He appoints a tough-as-nails veteran astronaut to lead a joint American-Russian crew into space to destroy the comet before impact. Meanwhile, an enterprising reporter uses her smarts to uncover the scoop of the century.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a3vQS7JKqlOb3MdVJHuTCP9s7Mg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/w53FK3MoMLavk1sxErUiGMnLpf2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Demolition Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106697</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Demolition Man</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Simon Phoenix, a violent criminal cryogenically frozen in 1996, escapes during a parole hearing in 2032 in the utopia of San Angeles. Police are incapable of dealing with his violent ways and turn to his captor, who had also been cryogenically frozen after being wrongfully accused of killing 30 innocent people while apprehending Phoenix.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pxWuGsyzVQSqHWxVQLy4XUcopIL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4pl165EUdvveHCr4J4YcHVA1MnD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dredd[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1343727</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dredd</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the future, America is a dystopian wasteland. The latest scourge is Ma-Ma, a prostitute-turned-drug pusher with a dangerous new drug and aims to take over the city. The only possibility of stopping her is an elite group of urban police called Judges, who combine the duties of judge, jury and executioner to deliver a brutal brand of swift justice. But even the top-ranking Judge, Dredd, discovers that taking down Ma-Ma isn’t as easy as it seems in this explosive adaptation of the hugely popular comic series.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wLx65gtGVnUFCxceHWGszcruCZj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yeF9ewBnFp9d5nqdHMic4IAOqrs.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083866</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An alien is left behind on Earth and saved by the 10-year-old Elliot who decides to keep him hidden in his home. While a task force hunts for the extra-terrestrial, Elliot, his brother, and his little sister Gertie form an emotional bond with their new friend, and try to help him find his way home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/an0nD6uq6byfxXCfk6lQBzdL2J1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mXLVA0YL6tcXi6SJSuAh9ONXFj5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Edge of Tomorrow[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1631867</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Edge of Tomorrow</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Major Bill Cage is an officer who has never seen a day of combat when he is unceremoniously demoted and dropped into combat. Cage is killed within minutes, managing to take an alpha alien down with him. He awakens back at the beginning of the same day and is forced to fight and die again... and again - as physical contact with the alien has thrown him into a time loop.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xjw5trHV7Mwo61P0kCTy8paEkgO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4V1yIoAKPMRQwGBaSses8Bp2nsi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Elysium[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1535108</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Elysium</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the year 2159, two classes of people exist: the very wealthy who live on a pristine man-made space station called Elysium, and the rest, who live on an overpopulated, ruined Earth. Secretary Rhodes, a hard line government ofﬁcial, will stop at nothing to enforce anti-immigration laws and preserve the luxurious lifestyle of the citizens of Elysium. That doesn’t stop the people of Earth from trying to get in, by any means they can. When unlucky Max is backed into a corner, he agrees to take on a daunting mission that, if successful, will not only save his life, but could bring equality to these polarized worlds.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aRjuJuPXHtVs6YegfeeQWXGRs1E.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dgCfxotSzXcvSos7CBCxrQ1FPBu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Escape from New York[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0082340</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Escape from New York</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the future, crime is out of control and New York City's Manhattan is a maximum security prison. Grabbing a bargaining chip right out of the air, convicts bring down the President's plane in bad old Gotham. Gruff Snake Plissken, a one-eyed lone warrior new to prison life, is coerced into bringing the President, and his cargo, out of this land of undesirables.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bOXk4mF2TjMJVq8DZYUtblKOR92.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qcCo2yV6xoak7tMI9YfGSoJgxKW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ex Machina[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0470752</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ex Machina</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Caleb, a coder at the world's largest internet company, wins a competition to spend a week at a private mountain retreat belonging to Nathan, the reclusive CEO of the company. But when Caleb arrives at the remote location he finds that he will have to participate in a strange and fascinating experiment in which he must interact with the world's first true artificial intelligence, housed in the body of a beautiful robot girl.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dmJW8IAKHKxFNiUnoDR7JfsK7Rp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uqOuJ50EtTj7kkDIXP8LCg7G45D.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Flash Gordon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0080745</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Flash Gordon</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A football player and his mates travel to the planet Mongo and find themselves fighting the tyranny of Ming the Merciless to save Earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5PyiSSJ6lVsY8IbmPHBo1sp596h.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bTBm7HuTQylEzBRqw2SaIkF0ZlG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Forbidden Planet[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0049223</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Forbidden Planet</title>
	<year>1956</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Starship C57D travels to planet Altair 4 in search of the crew of spaceship "Bellerophon," a scientific expedition that has been missing for 20 years, only to find themselves unwelcome by the expedition's lone survivor and warned of destruction by an invisible force if they don't turn back immediately.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aq0OQfRS7hDDI8vyD0ICbH9eguC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9EUmwXS6EbY5djAhLtBGzUbBwNV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Frequency[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0186151</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Frequency</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a rare phenomenon gives police officer John Sullivan the chance to speak to his father, 30 years in the past, he takes the opportunity to prevent his dad's tragic death.  After his actions inadvertently give rise to a series of brutal murders he and his father must find a way to fix the consequences of altering time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aFuw2yow5Og0e2M7uEHQtpS5GPz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3N6iWYfL5spmk18d4s7rl4N89Pg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Galaxy Quest[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0177789</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Galaxy Quest</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For four years, the courageous crew of the NSEA protector - "Commander Peter Quincy Taggart" (Tim Allen), "Lt. Tawny Madison (Sigourney Weaver) and "Dr.Lazarus" (Alan Rickman) - set off on a thrilling and often dangerous mission in space...and then their series was cancelled! Now, twenty years later, aliens under attack have mistaken the Galaxy Quest television transmissions for "historical documents" and beam up the crew of has-been actors to save the universe. With no script, no director and no clue, the actors must turn in the performances of their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fZXSwgZknp81vmciTb86rw0MejV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uIyxbTK1FXJj2wINnlGZzxphlv5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Gattaca[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119177</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Gattaca</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a future society in the era of indefinite eugenics, humans are set on a life course depending on their DNA. Young Vincent Freeman is born with a condition that would prevent him from space travel, yet is determined to infiltrate the GATTACA space program.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mi8ow4MIoPvgBnWB1OKe0ph0woa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hPsCR1ny6GnctJkWqeJwihTDD7T.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]I Am Legend[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0480249</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>I Am Legend</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Robert Neville is a scientist who was unable to stop the spread of the terrible virus that was incurable and man-made. Immune, Neville is now the last human survivor in what is left of New York City and perhaps the world. For three years, Neville has faithfully sent out daily radio messages, desperate to find any other survivors who might be out there. But he is not alone.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iPDkaSdKk2jRLTM65UOEoKtsIZ8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lhVVIWKR13khBvjFz8XyZ2GM0JS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]I, Robot[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0343818</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>I, Robot</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 2035, where robots are commonplace and abide by the three laws of robotics, a technophobic cop investigates an apparent suicide. Suspecting that a robot may be responsible for the death, his investigation leads him to believe that humanity may be in danger.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/efwv6F2lGaghjPpBRSINHtoEiZB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lOXVbF2mBK0xUt8sLInF3TIk5YS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Inception[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1375666</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Inception</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Cobb, a skilled thief who commits corporate espionage by infiltrating the subconscious of his targets is offered a chance to regain his old life as payment for a task considered to be impossible: "inception", the implantation of another person's idea into a target's subconscious.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/edv5CZvWj09upOsy2Y6IwDhK8bt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8ZTVqvKDQ8emSGUEMjsS4yHAwrp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Independence Day[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116629</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Independence Day</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>On July 2, a giant alien mothership enters orbit around Earth and deploys several dozen saucer-shaped 'destroyer' spacecraft that quickly lay waste to major cities around the planet. On July 3, the United States conducts a coordinated counterattack that fails. On July 4, a plan is devised to gain access to the interior of the alien mothership in space, in order to plant a nuclear missile.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p0BPQGSPoSa8Ml0DAf2mB2kCU0R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uw4SnKFZ453Gxmj5XR5Susj8TNo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Interstellar[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0816692</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Interstellar</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The adventures of a group of explorers who make use of a newly discovered wormhole to surpass the limitations on human space travel and conquer the vast distances involved in an interstellar voyage.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gEU2QniE6E77NI6lCU6MxlNBvIx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rAiYTfKGqDCRIIqo664sY9XZIvQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Invasion of the Body Snatchers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0077745</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Invasion of the Body Snatchers</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Matthew Bennell notices that several of his friends are complaining that their close relatives are in some way different. When questioned later they themselves seem changed, as they deny everything or make lame excuses. As the invaders increase in number they become more open and Bennell, who has by now witnessed an attempted 'replacement', realises that he and his friends must escape or suffer the same fate.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5oNHdVo0vTsaC47Jv2Wb4eeo4V4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/psAYbe3Jjb5nxeGOsk5oSeFJ5tK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Jurassic Park[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107290</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Jurassic Park</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A wealthy entrepreneur secretly creates a theme park featuring living dinosaurs drawn from prehistoric DNA. Before opening day, he invites a team of experts and his two eager grandchildren to experience the park and help calm anxious investors. However, the park is anything but amusing as the security systems go off-line and the dinosaurs escape.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oU7Oq2kFAAlGqbU4VoAE36g4hoI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1FN6pHFDDlhT7oVhABKKGtG6ga7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Limitless[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1219289</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Limitless</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A paranoia-fueled action thriller about an unsuccessful writer whose life is transformed by a top-secret "smart drug" that allows him to use 100% of his brain and become a perfect version of himself. His enhanced abilities soon attract shadowy forces that threaten his new life in this darkly comic and provocative film.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hv5JMCrMVLvV6HKPf9FcBuyk2MG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vQGo5VjJcHxpzIa8lMBFzpAth1w.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Logan's Run[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0074812</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Logan's Run</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the 23rd century, inhabitants of a domed city freely experience all of life's pleasures — but no one is allowed to live past 30. Citizens can try for a chance at being "renewed" in a civic ceremony on their 30th birthday. Escape is the only other option.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v3ILN8ROPcrNRJ8S7GH24JyihH8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hssP6kKDIrhYxj5833lLcpmCm6E.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Looper[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1276104</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Looper</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the futuristic action thriller Looper, time travel will be invented but it will be illegal and only available on the black market. When the mob wants to get rid of someone, they will send their target 30 years into the past where a looper, a hired gun, like Joe is waiting to mop up. Joe is getting rich and life is good until the day the mob decides to close the loop, sending back Joe's future self for assassination.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sNjL6SqErDBE8OUZlrDLkexfsCj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8UiZP1dTIPRYkIcwR84zZTwgKpZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mad Max[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079501</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mad Max</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the ravaged near future, a savage motorcycle gang rules the road. Terrorizing innocent civilians while tearing up the streets, the ruthless gang laughs in the face ofa police force hell-bent on stopping them. But they underestimate one officer: Max Rockatansky. And when the bikers brutalize Max's best friend and family, they send him into a mad frenzy that leaves him with only one thing left in the world to live for – revenge!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LrI4GiCSrChgkdskVZiwv643Kg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uL5DoOuMho1QY7OK5IqacYH9QHK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mad Max: Fury Road[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1392190</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mad Max: Fury Road</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An apocalyptic story set in the furthest reaches of our planet, in a stark desert landscape where humanity is broken, and most everyone is crazed fighting for the necessities of life. Within this world exist two rebels on the run who just might be able to restore order.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8tZYtuWezp8JbcsvHYO0O46tFbo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nlCHUWjY9XWbuEUQauCBgnY8ymF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Mimic[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119675</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mimic</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A disease carried by common cockroaches is killing Manhattan children. In an effort to stop the epidemic an entomologist, Susan Tyler, creates a mutant breed of insect that secretes a fluid to kill the roaches. This mutant breed was engineered to die after one generation, but three years later Susan finds out that the species has survived and evolved into a large, gruesome monster that can mimic human form.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ieRRo78f8JzEKxfiCKqJyFg6l8o.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bouH0jYhfiAHn28B3AygP0XO6V8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Minority Report[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0181689</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Minority Report</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>John Anderton is a top 'Precrime' cop in the late-21st century, when technology can predict crimes before they're committed. But Anderton becomes the quarry when another investigator targets him for a murder charge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ccqpHq5tk5W4ymbSbuoy4uYOxFI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qq4H9JfBKQ5DarMLI6lhUQjn9D7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Moon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1182345</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Moon</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>With only three weeks left in his three year contract, Sam Bell is getting anxious to finally return to Earth. He is the only occupant of a Moon-based manufacturing facility along with his computer and assistant, GERTY. When he has an accident however, he wakens to find that he is not alone.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cJ6JnuLwCNbiAAOBuHDjRTP7bQJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xvNNdKrQo57gEEndrqoqZSzEjNj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Oblivion[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1483013</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Oblivion</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Jack Harper is one of the last few drone repairmen stationed on Earth. Part of a massive operation to extract vital resources after decades of war with a terrifying threat known as the Scavs, Jack’s mission is nearly complete. His existence is brought crashing down when he rescues a beautiful  stranger from a downed spacecraft. Her arrival triggers a chain of events that  forces him to question everything he knows and puts the fate of humanity in his hands.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eO3r38fwnhb58M1YgcjQBd3VNcp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/19AqfWi8S99tDmp7hskCeDQuwLU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pacific Rim[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1663662</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pacific Rim</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As war between humankind and monstrous sea creatures wages on, a former pilot and a trainee are paired up to drive a seemingly obsolete special weapon in a desperate effort to save the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8wo4eN8dWKaKlxhSvBz19uvj8gA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ig7qUy7drkEFZNCK7gi0hMn1WMN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Phenomenon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0117333</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Phenomenon</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An ordinary man sees a bright light descend from the sky, and discovers he now has super-intelligence and telekinesis.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5eK1HNf0Kl2vDPOeqf1kX4SKxrw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/15JUzyooElSbMXXYl2gnHX62A7X.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pitch Black[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0134847</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pitch Black</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When their ship crash-lands on a remote planet, the marooned passengers soon learn that escaped convict Riddick isn't the only thing they have to fear. Deadly creatures lurk in the shadows, waiting to attack in the dark, and the planet is rapidly plunging into the utter blackness of a total eclipse. With the body count rising, the doomed survivors are forced to turn to Riddick with his eerie eyes to guide them through the darkness to safety. With time running out, there's only one rule: Stay in the light.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3AnlxZ5CZnhKKzjgFyY6EHxmOyl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mZGwhwIwYuF0G9XLS8j23dhNfUC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Planet of the Apes[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063442</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Planet of the Apes</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Astronaut Taylor crash lands on a distant planet ruled by apes who use a primitive race of humans for experimentation and sport. Soon Taylor finds himself among the hunted, his life in the hands of a benevolent chimpanzee scientist.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2r9iKnlSYEk4daQadsXfcjHfIjQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dQS3L3USI7Zhcq41abzMZF8dXCm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Predator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093773</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Predator</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A team of elite commandos on a secret mission in a Central American jungle come to find themselves hunted by an extraterrestrial warrior.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k3mW4qfJo6SKqe6laRyNGnbB9n5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/YL3GPOiDcNraIJOVDCZsoOBoDy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Predestination[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2397535</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Predestination</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Predestination chronicles the life of a Temporal Agent sent on an intricate series of time-travel journeys designed to prevent future killers from committing their crimes. Now, on his final assignment, the Agent must stop the one criminal that has eluded him throughout time and prevent a devastating attack in which thousands of lives will be lost.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sYjpJZEdwELjdHy4OVzazeJVT0z.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u5JKxjMuKk0dVXqmS4e4gHo8pfg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Prometheus[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1446714</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Prometheus</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A team of explorers discover a clue to the origins of mankind on Earth, leading them on a journey to the darkest corners of the universe. There, they must fight a terrifying battle to save the future of the human race.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qsYQflQhOuhDpQ0W2aOcwqgDAeI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hO97RyNjBIMfzfFpUjNhsm4zImh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Quatermass and the Pit[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0062168</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Quatermass and the Pit</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An ancient Martian spaceship is unearthed in London, and proves to have powerful psychic effects on the people around.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AvruSt4xRIbXO8gVxPzHupbf5A2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4thlb8BV5BFWtD1whfH5a21bmJ8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Resident Evil[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120804</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Resident Evil</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a virus leaks from a top-secret facility, turning all resident researchers into ravenous zombies and their lab animals into mutated hounds from hell, the government sends in an elite military task force to contain the outbreak. Alice and Rain are charged with leading the mission. But they only have three hours before the pathogen becomes airborne and infects the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1UKNef590A0ZaMnxsscIcWuK1Em.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5pGWjnM62Zs0S1xRf3TDL1Xizr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Return of the Jedi[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086190</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Return of the Jedi</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Luke Skywalker leads a mission to rescue his friend Han Solo from the clutches of Jabba the Hutt, while the Emperor seeks to destroy the Rebellion once and for all with a second dreaded Death Star.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q6ydU8r1iYyy2bV7tPVaq266Y1k.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/soJdiy91Mcyj29GzEgZ5svFcuZg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Riddick[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1411250</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Riddick</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Betrayed by his own kind and left for dead on a desolate planet, Riddick fights for survival against alien predators and becomes more powerful and dangerous than ever before. Soon bounty hunters from throughout the galaxy descend on Riddick only to find themselves pawns in his greater scheme for revenge. With his enemies right where he wants them, Riddick unleashes a vicious attack of vengeance before returning to his home planet of Furya to save it from destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pUul9pGWOKT7X0smkTvsIEIQxcP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/naGU49u4BXynQ1o5L755pfs8dom.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]RoboCop[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093870</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>RoboCop</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a violent, near-apocalyptic Detroit, evil corporation Omni Consumer Products wins a contract from the city government to privatize the police force. To test their crime-eradicating cyborgs, the company leads street cop Alex Murphy into an armed confrontation with crime lord Boddicker so they can use his body to support their untested RoboCop prototype. But when RoboCop learns of the company's nefarious plans, he turns on his masters.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hHtOgGb3NihlyRATHlKPaFApbrd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vMGkly71Jm2KwHN407mxheMGUYR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Signs[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0286106</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Signs</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A family living on a farm finds mysterious crop circles in their fields which suggests something more frightening to come.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hyZkNEbNgnciUVTyu4NZTjlCh4L.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q5Y0IPNZvAhC5hpsLubH6jFTCxn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Solaris[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0307479</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Solaris</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A troubled psychologist is sent to investigate the crew of an isolated research station orbiting a bizarre planet.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/drdrB1hEZmzFlK1xtW5HMxK3LUJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/avjG5EPgWXyLvsUId6hEn0iqT4A.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Trek[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0796366</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The fate of the galaxy rests in the hands of bitter rivals. One, James Kirk, is a delinquent, thrill-seeking Iowa farm boy. The other, Spock, a Vulcan, was raised in a logic-based society that rejects all emotion. As fiery instinct clashes with calm reason, their unlikely but powerful partnership is the only thing capable of leading their crew through unimaginable danger, boldly going where no one has gone before. The human adventure has begun again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lV5OpzAss1z06YNagOVap1I35mH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q7M0JpPixbEYT8EhnI7wTEMONxz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084726</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>It is the 23rd century. The Federation Starship U.S.S. Enterprise is on routine training maneuvers and Admiral James T. Kirk seems resigned to the fact that this inspection may well be the last space mission of his career. But Khan is back. Aided by his exiled band of genetic supermen, Khan - brilliant renegade of 20th century Earth - has raided Space Station Regula One, stolen a top secret device called Project Genesis, wrested control of another Federation Starship and sets out in pursuit of the Enterprise, determined to let nothing stand in the way of his mission: kill Admiral Kirk... even if it means universal Armageddon.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uPyLsKl8Z0LOoxeaFXsY5MxhR5s.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oXs8kp1oX5N0Mte6U8UUAwmLwt6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Trek Into Darkness[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1408101</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek Into Darkness</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When the crew of the Enterprise is called back home, they find an unstoppable force of terror from within their own organization has detonated the fleet and everything it stands for, leaving our world in a state of crisis.  With a personal score to settle, Captain Kirk leads a manhunt to a war-zone world to capture a one man weapon of mass destruction. As our heroes are propelled into an epic chess game of life and death, love will be challenged, friendships will be torn apart, and sacrifices must be made for the only family Kirk has left: his crew.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eXbCboT5mMv9RH1E7ogzIytN302.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/npDrIM6ZbuD7nUxI7ZzNBxs4IRF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Trek: First Contact[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0117731</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek: First Contact</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Borg, a relentless race of cyborgs, are on a direct course for Earth. Violating orders to stay away from the battle, Captain Picard and the crew of the newly-commissioned USS Enterprise E pursue the Borg back in time to prevent the invaders from changing Federation history and assimilating the galaxy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vrC1lkTktFQ4AqBfqf4PXoDDLcw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wygUDDRNpeKUnkekRGeLCZM93tA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Wars[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0076759</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Wars</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Princess Leia is captured and held hostage by the evil Imperial forces in their effort to take over the galactic Empire. Venturesome Luke Skywalker and dashing captain Han Solo team together with the loveable robot duo R2-D2 and C-3PO to rescue the beautiful princess and restore peace and justice in the Empire.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6FfCtAuVAW8XJjZ7eWeLibRLWTw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aDYSnJAK0BTVeE8osOy22Kz3SXY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0121766</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The evil Darth Sidious enacts his final plan for unlimited power -- and the heroic Jedi Anakin Skywalker must choose a side.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xfSAoBEm9MNBjmlNcDYLvLSMlnq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uuh6uNEGqLCU7wQ2L4xMqYv0DPr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Stargate[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0111282</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Stargate</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An interstellar teleportation device, found in Egypt, leads to a planet with humans resembling ancient Egyptians who worship the god Ra.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kLacy1TrSedHrZcsup1JNHl1upk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/s2bqHApZlliCuwgyHod0qucrYqZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Starship Troopers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120201</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Starship Troopers</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Set in the future, the story follows a young soldier named Johnny Rico and his exploits in the Mobile Infantry. Rico's military career progresses from recruit to non-commissioned officer and finally to officer against the backdrop of an interstellar war between mankind and an arachnoid species known as "the Bugs".</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cxCmv23O7p3hyHwqoktHYkZcGsY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7PR2yMwXuXelAcp3qpJ3isZCdd0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Sunshine[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0448134</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Sunshine</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Fifty years into the future, the sun is dying, and Earth is threatened by arctic temperatures. A team of astronauts is sent to revive the Sun — but the mission fails. Seven years later, a new team is sent to finish the mission as mankind’s last hope.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x8umyFj5HPTFSdxBmuBuq9bpCgc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5AIAnucJKZ3sHpm7r1ykFVIoUHK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Super 8[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1650062</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Super 8</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 1979 Ohio, several youngsters are making a zombie movie with a Super-8 camera. In the midst of filming, the friends witness a horrifying train derailment and are lucky to escape with their lives. They soon discover that the catastrophe was no accident, as a series of unexplained events and disappearances soon follows. Deputy Jackson Lamb, the father of one of the kids, searches for the terrifying truth behind the crash.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sytFL6ALMAesKZoarlp7bIDKnns.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tQFwpwJg6Je7l6A8rgRZ8yefvdV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Tenet[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6723592</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tenet</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Armed with only one word - Tenet - and fighting for the survival of the entire world, the Protagonist journeys through a twilight world of international espionage on a mission that will unfold in something beyond real time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aCIFMriQh8rvhxpN1IWGgvH0Tlg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yY76zq9XSuJ4nWyPDuwkdV7Wt0c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Terminator 2: Judgment Day[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103064</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Nearly 10 years have passed since Sarah Connor was targeted for termination by a cyborg from the future. Now her son, John, the future leader of the resistance, is the target for a newer, more deadly terminator. Once again, the resistance has managed to send a protector back to attempt to save John and his mother Sarah.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5M0j0B18abtBI5gi2RhfjjurTqb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xKb6mtdfI5Qsggc44Hr9CCUDvaj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Abyss[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096754</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Abyss</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A civilian oil rig crew is recruited to conduct a search and rescue effort when a nuclear submarine mysteriously sinks. One diver soon finds himself on a spectacular odyssey 25,000 feet below the ocean's surface where he confronts a mysterious force that has the power to change the world or destroy it.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jel2BuDv7Bq4fuv2pUrTfiBm69o.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aPB3jFuMSoNFk2uDZ5tX5CIGaSX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Arrival[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0115571</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Arrival</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Zane Ziminski is an astrophysicist who receives a message that seems to have extraterrestrial origins. Eerily soon after his discovery, Zane is fired. He then embarks on a search to determine the origins of the transmission that leads him into a Hitchcockian labyrinth of paranoia and intrigue.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ARbqk8SqABU8QqANvpJCpMQ5nj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oJ597dVjLMICx56clM7iy3AUUsA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Butterfly Effect[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289879</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Butterfly Effect</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young man struggles to access sublimated childhood memories. He finds a technique that allows him to travel back into the past, to occupy his childhood body and change history. However, he soon finds that every change he makes has unexpected consequences.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l3ad5yv0Nn91zYPgeCjTvut2Nqg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aoL6L4PCn89MHTVyMnmjwBFLmWX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Day After Tomorrow[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0319262</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day After Tomorrow</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After years of increases in the greenhouse effect,  havoc is wreaked globally in the form of catastrophic hurricanes, tornadoes, tidal waves, floods and the beginning of a new Ice Age. Paleoclimatologist, Jack Hall tries to warn the world while also shepherding to safety his son, trapped in New York after the city is overwhelmed by the start of the new big freeze.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kNKy8eJemg6sCAMBgh4xrD0lleX.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fXJhA3pjLMDkHPgZ2GVhRDXA5M3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Day the Earth Stood Still[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0043456</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day the Earth Stood Still</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An alien and a robot land on Earth after World War II and tell mankind to be peaceful or face destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x2DquTpLTq54aPFDnqlwY7apCC3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3cxXe9mLoMiIeBxvjRh4lcC2TuK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Empire Strikes Back[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0080684</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Empire Strikes Back</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The epic saga continues as Luke Skywalker, in hopes of defeating the evil Galactic Empire, learns the ways of the Jedi from aging master Yoda. But Darth Vader is more determined than ever to capture Luke. Meanwhile, rebel leader Princess Leia, cocky Han Solo, Chewbacca, and droids C-3PO and R2-D2 are thrown into various stages of capture, betrayal and despair.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2l05cFWJacyIsTpsqSgH0wQXe4V.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dMZxEdrWIzUmUoOz2zvmFuutbj7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fifth Element[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119116</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fifth Element</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 2257, a taxi driver is unintentionally given the task of saving a young girl who is part of the key that will ensure the survival of humanity.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fPtlCO1yQtnoLHOwKtWz7db6RGU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dwN0kPGrLbFRxyL3F3J3t4ShQx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fly[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091064</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fly</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Seth Brundle makes a huge scientific and technological breakthrough in teleportation, he decides to test it on himself. Unbeknownst to him, a common housefly manages to get inside the device and the two become one.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8gZWMhJHRvaXdXsNhERtqNHYpH3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jsfIt1y0t7hNjYmC7mfsEIHwET8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Incredible Shrinking Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0050539</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Incredible Shrinking Man</title>
	<year>1957</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A dangerous combination of radiation and insecticide causes the unfortunate Scott Carey to shrink, slowly but surely, until he is only a few inches tall. His home becomes a wilderness where he must survive everything from spiders living in the cellar to his beloved cat.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1Tl2aeOhvUmEHSGHGH5SfmN19vQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vdVPrTGRNdTd6Bs1fr7ulodcQVm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Invisible Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1051906</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Invisible Man</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Cecilia's abusive ex takes his own life and leaves her his fortune, she suspects his death was a hoax. As a series of coincidences turn lethal, Cecilia works to prove that she is being hunted by someone nobody can see.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5EufsDwXdY2CVttYOk2WtYhgKpa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tweDJNQzBGgsWVF5MC8JhSAk07p.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Man from Earth[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0756683</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Man from Earth</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An impromptu goodbye party for Professor John Oldman becomes a mysterious interrogation after the retiring scholar reveals to his colleagues he never ages and has walked the earth for 14,000 years.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/V086R82gNgWrotaXZFO4JhdgB1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gt4EnUGbbGbNOX0q47YII3WxB48.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Man Who Fell to Earth[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0074851</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Man Who Fell to Earth</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Thomas Jerome Newton is an alien who has come to Earth in search of water to save his home planet. Aided by lawyer Oliver Farnsworth, Thomas uses his knowledge of advanced technology to create profitable inventions. While developing a method to transport water, Thomas meets Mary-Lou, a quiet hotel clerk, and begins to fall in love with her. Just as he is ready to leave Earth, Thomas is intercepted by the U.S. government, and his entire plan is threatened.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vNyjTDyUCjydCVH48pwOrY6Odn2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xvcOWLY6GHiD2LRrXbDwqqKjwQ4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Martian[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3659388</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Martian</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During a manned mission to Mars, Astronaut Mark Watney is presumed dead after a fierce storm and left behind by his crew. But Watney has survived and finds himself stranded and alone on the hostile planet. With only meager supplies, he must draw upon his ingenuity, wit and spirit to subsist and find a way to signal to Earth that he is alive.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5BHuvQ6p9kfc091Z8RiFNhCwL4b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3dPhs7hUnQLphDFzdkD407VZDYo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Matrix[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0133093</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Matrix</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Set in the 22nd century, The Matrix tells the story of a computer hacker who joins a group of underground insurgents fighting the vast and powerful computers who now rule the earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f89U3ADr1oiB1s9GkdPOEpXUk5H.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/waCRuAW5ocONRehP556vPexVXA9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Terminator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088247</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Terminator</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the post-apocalyptic future, reigning tyrannical supercomputers teleport a cyborg assassin known as the "Terminator" back to 1984 to kill Sarah Connor, whose unborn son is destined to lead insurgents against 21st century mechanical hegemony. Meanwhile, the human-resistance movement dispatches a lone warrior to safeguard Sarah. Can he stop the virtually indestructible killing machine?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvktm0BHcnmDpul4Hz01GIazWPr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wh4ze6klUbeichAj603OKZwY1W5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Thing[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084787</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Thing</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A team of American scientists investigate the empty, destroyed base of their Norwegian counterparts in Antarctica, only to discover a terrifying life force that can take the form of its prey.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tzGY49kseSE9QAKk47uuDGwnSCu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jaO8WurWoUBE55nskqtFqPZFFaO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Time Machine[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054387</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Time Machine</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A Victorian Englishman travels to the far future and finds that humanity has divided into two hostile species.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cq2kBK4t0ADB3Nc83NQ16TZqCiM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bUA6Fu0C2jGqrjn0A9AJwTRpq41.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Tomorrow War[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt9777666</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Tomorrow War</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The world is stunned when a group of time travelers arrive from the year 2051 to deliver an urgent message: Thirty years in the future, mankind is losing a global war against a deadly alien species. The only hope for survival is for soldiers and civilians from the present to be transported to the future and join the fight. Among those recruited is high school teacher and family man Dan Forester. Determined to save the world for his young daughter, Dan teams up with a brilliant scientist and his estranged father in a desperate quest to rewrite the fate of the planet.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/34nDCQZwaEvsy4CFO5hkGRFDCVU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yizL4cEKsVvl17Wc1mGEIrQtM2F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Truman Show[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120382</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Truman Show</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Truman Burbank is the star of The Truman Show, a 24-hour-a-day reality TV show that broadcasts every aspect of his life without his knowledge. His entire life has been an unending soap opera for consumption by the rest of the world. And everyone he knows, including his wife and his best friend is really an actor, paid to be part of his life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vuza0WqY239yBXOadKlGwJsZJFE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bxY7ve1LP8atCIuvr4jeeJMmU4w.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The War of the Worlds[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0046534</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The War of the Worlds</title>
	<year>1953</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The residents of a small town are excited when a flaming meteor lands in the hills, until they discover it is the first of many transport devices from Mars bringing an army of invaders invincible to any man-made weapon, even the atomic bomb.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gzc75Za4ArqfXIIr7STNnIE5rnA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/842AcW0eLEIagMTXLdbGVSsDHLh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The X Files[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120902</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The X Files</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Mulder and Scully, now taken off the FBI's X Files cases, must find a way to fight the shadowy elements of the government to find out the truth about a conspiracy that might mean the alien colonization of Earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yLIw6shz2WC3W3iI0jROsF4B2ha.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2ZuNdBOSUamCo6mU1Ew1KEaN8Zc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]They Live[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096256</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>They Live</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Nada, a wanderer without meaning in his life, discovers a pair of sunglasses capable of showing the world the way it truly is. As he walks the streets of Los Angeles, Nada notices that both the media and the government are comprised of subliminal messages meant to keep the population subdued, and that most of the social elite are skull-faced aliens bent on world domination. With this shocking discovery, Nada fights to free humanity from the mind-controlling aliens.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ngnybFTuopfbfmmEeX9jjBQQmF6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mq37KmVnHaB6MpAx1uiKBrVDrxG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Total Recall[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0100802</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Total Recall</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Construction worker Douglas Quaid's obsession with the planet Mars leads him to visit Recall, a company who manufacture memories. Something goes wrong during his memory implant turning Doug's life upside down and even to question what is reality and what isn't.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wVbeL6fkbTKSmNfalj4VoAUUqJv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cE9Gtz5KEVkien4VDSgXjtwfcs.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Twelve Monkeys[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114746</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Twelve Monkeys</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the year 2035, convict James Cole reluctantly volunteers to be sent back in time to discover the origin of a deadly virus that wiped out nearly all of the earth's population and forced the survivors into underground communities. But when Cole is mistakenly sent to 1990 instead of 1996, he's arrested and locked up in a mental hospital. There he meets psychiatrist Dr. Kathryn Railly, and patient Jeffrey Goines, the son of a famous virus expert, who may hold the key to the mysterious rogue group, the Army of the 12 Monkeys, thought to be responsible for unleashing the killer disease.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gt3iyguaCIw8DpQZI1LIN5TohM2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2aPrheKAOwyjJqu6YYd2TvsKv9a.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Videodrome[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086541</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Videodrome</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As the president of a trashy TV channel, Max Renn is desperate for new programming to attract viewers. When he happens upon "Videodrome," a TV show dedicated to gratuitous torture and punishment, Max sees a potential hit and broadcasts the show on his channel. However, after his girlfriend auditions for the show and never returns, Max investigates the truth behind Videodrome and discovers that the graphic violence may not be as fake as he thought.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dBqp1SxlqnJEHYDM9sNelXoQsO1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kIQszOniJOd1ULFUfdk4yDR0W5c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]War of the Worlds[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0407304</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>War of the Worlds</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Ray Ferrier is a divorced dockworker and less-than-perfect father. Soon after his ex-wife and her new husband drop off his teenage son and young daughter for a rare weekend visit, a strange and powerful lightning storm touches down.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6Biy7R9LfumYshur3YKhpj56MpB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nH6hPhJq3EEv9CnBZgXU3IQnpJo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Waterworld[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114898</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Waterworld</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a futuristic world where the polar ice caps have melted and made Earth a liquid planet, a beautiful barmaid rescues a mutant seafarer from a floating island prison. They escape, along with her young charge, Enola, and sail off aboard his ship.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nyCA6UfqEPsH1lqL6YVtVf0KwwN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hJleEkILmKzJsvzrU8o5d66jbPa.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]When Worlds Collide[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0044207</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>When Worlds Collide</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a group of astronomers calculate a star is on a course to slam into Earth, a few days before, it's accompanying planet will first pass close enough to the Earth to cause havoc on land and sea. They set about building a rocket so a few selected individuals can escape to the planet.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xUd6NOABGlU3TSNP42toxWhmMQ3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ws8eX1paKpgEVetOTg6OUlKtLXw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Metropolis[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0017136</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Metropolis</title>
	<year>1927</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a futuristic city sharply divided between the rich and the poor, the son of the city's mastermind meets a prophet who predicts the coming of a savior to mediate their differences.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hUK9rewffKGqtXynH5SW3v9hzcu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r8pUcom5Mw8igtBpj3AHSAUvH0R.jpg</fanart>
</item>
