<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Psycho[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054215</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Psycho</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When larcenous real estate clerk Marion Crane goes on the lam with a wad of cash and hopes of starting a new life, she ends up at the notorious Bates Motel, where manager Norman Bates cares for his housebound mother.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yz4QVqPx3h1hD1DfqqQkCq3rmxW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uif5fUshJrXyyDzfpzp1DLw3N0S.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Jaws[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0073195</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Jaws</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When an insatiable great white shark terrorizes the townspeople of Amity Island, the police chief, an oceanographer and a grizzled shark hunter seek to destroy the blood-thirsty beast.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lxM6kqilAdpdhqUl2biYp5frUxE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3nYlM34QhzdtAvWRV5bN4nLtnTc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Exorcist[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0070047</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Exorcist</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>12-year-old Regan MacNeil begins to adapt an explicit new personality as strange events befall the local area of Georgetown. Her mother becomes torn between science and superstition in a desperate bid to save her daughter, and ultimately turns to her last hope: Father Damien Karras, a troubled priest who is struggling with his own faith.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4ucLGcXVVSVnsfkGtbLY4XAius8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xcjJ5khg2yzOa282mza39Lbrm7j.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]North by Northwest[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0053125</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>North by Northwest</title>
	<year>1959</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Advertising man Roger Thornhill is mistaken for a spy, triggering a deadly cross-country chase.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8gvfRlVpcKaTVqipXpYOGWBN1aO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fONtQBk12LGjQo4q6bXDROVQmTy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Silence of the Lambs[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0102926</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Silence of the Lambs</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Clarice Starling is a top student at the FBI's training academy.  Jack Crawford wants Clarice to interview Dr. Hannibal Lecter, a brilliant psychiatrist who is also a violent psychopath, serving life behind bars for various acts of murder and cannibalism.  Crawford believes that Lecter may have insight into a case and that Starling, as an attractive young woman, may be just the bait to draw him out.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rplLJ2hPcOQmkFhTqUte0MkEaO2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aYcnDyLMnpKce1FOYUpZrXtgUye.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Alien[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0078748</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During its return to the earth, commercial spaceship Nostromo intercepts a distress signal from a distant planet. When a three-member team of the crew discovers a chamber containing thousands of eggs on the planet, a creature inside one of the eggs attacks an explorer. The entire crew is unaware of the impending nightmare set to descend upon them when the alien parasite planted inside its unfortunate host is birthed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vfrQk5IPloGg1v9Rzbh2Eg3VGyM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AmR3JG1VQVxU8TfAvljUhfSFUOx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Birds[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056869</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Birds</title>
	<year>1963</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Chic socialite Melanie Daniels enjoys a passing flirtation with an eligible attorney in a San Francisco pet shop and, on an impulse, follows him to his hometown bearing a gift of lovebirds. But upon her arrival, the bird population runs amok. Suddenly, the townsfolk face a massive avian onslaught, with the feathered fiends inexplicably attacking people all over Bodega Bay.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z0iYrJ6GsAMP3abOha7uGMuc5kZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q2XxGMCO8Zey8YDrvQGi8P8ns5F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The French Connection[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0067116</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The French Connection</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Tough narcotics detective 'Popeye' Doyle is in hot pursuit of a suave French drug dealer who may be the key to a huge heroin-smuggling operation.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5XSGvIKl2yPvOkieFjc3rzLw7x0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AsaW2VwcArvQmYjf2wsDjqWEn6f.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rosemary's Baby[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063522</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rosemary's Baby</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A young couple, Rosemary and Guy, moves into an infamous New York apartment building, known by frightening legends and mysterious events, with the purpose of starting a family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/s8pdaHjxNPLXIA1WjSTWm00RJTz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sd8UeAahns9ZwxI7WlSa90iUxqd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Raiders of the Lost Ark[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0082971</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Raiders of the Lost Ark</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When Dr. Indiana Jones – the tweed-suited professor who just happens to be a celebrated archaeologist – is hired by the government to locate the legendary Ark of the Covenant, he finds himself up against the entire Nazi regime.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ceG9VzoRAVGwivFU403Wc3AHRys.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c7Mjuip0jfHLY7x8ZSEriRj45cu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Godfather[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0068646</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Godfather</title>
	<year>1972</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Spanning the years 1945 to 1955, a chronicle of the fictional Italian-American Corleone crime family. When organized crime family patriarch, Vito Corleone barely survives an attempt on his life, his youngest son, Michael steps in to take care of the would-be killers, launching a campaign of bloody revenge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3bhkrj58Vtu7enYsRolD1fZdja1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tmU7GeKVybMWFButWEGl2M4GeiP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]King Kong[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0024216</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>King Kong</title>
	<year>1933</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Adventurous filmmaker, Carl Denham, sets out to produce a motion picture unlike anything the world has seen before. Alongside his leading lady Ann Darrow and his first mate Jack Driscoll, they arrive on an island and discover a legendary creature said to be neither beast nor man. Denham captures the monster to displayed on Broadway as Kong, the eighth wonder of the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lHlnxKL5GbgRibyRFI7n1Ey850i.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7hDdW3C17pi4MdSeYXs8bwIVA78.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Bonnie and Clyde[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0061418</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bonnie and Clyde</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the 1930s, bored waitress Bonnie Parker falls in love with an ex-con named Clyde Barrow and together they start a violent crime spree through the country, stealing cars and robbing banks.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hr7HVAcC9ZiUvfwApuha7i4leyP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fyzSiE8IWezmd3ls1amHNeOkrEf.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rear Window[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0047396</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rear Window</title>
	<year>1954</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A wheelchair-bound photographer spies on his neighbors from his apartment window and becomes convinced one of them has committed murder.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qitnZcLP7C9DLRuPpmvZ7GiEjJN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zGs5tZOlvc9cprdcU6kDOVNpujf.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Deliverance[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0068473</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Deliverance</title>
	<year>1972</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Intent on seeing the Cahulawassee River before it's turned into one huge lake, outdoor fanatic Lewis Medlock takes his friends on a river-rafting trip they'll never forget into the dangerous American back-country.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2TrAzNJlHyNYYSkQf6asg3rs2Xr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8Lq3D8wZofEsjWS06W2J79otZTL.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Chinatown[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0071315</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Chinatown</title>
	<year>1974</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Private eye Jake Gittes lives off of the murky moral climate of sunbaked, pre-World War II Southern California. Hired by a beautiful socialite to investigate her husband's extra-marital affair, Gittes is swept into a maelstrom of double dealings and deadly deceits, uncovering a web of personal and political scandals that come crashing together.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ljxmU9L0ugUvyyg0GBkFaarjEq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bsoAg22remHKL5O0xJH0m9DX6Pu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Manchurian Candidate[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056218</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Manchurian Candidate</title>
	<year>1962</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Near the end of the Korean War, a platoon of U.S. soldiers is captured by communists and brainwashed. Following the war, the platoon is returned home, and Sergeant Raymond Shaw is lauded as a hero by the rest of his platoon. However, the platoon commander, Captain Bennett Marco, finds himself plagued by strange nightmares and soon races to uncover a terrible plot.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2xQ856kd9hw6bB3OnusGyTvvkwB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7dX07NQv4p6kfzSkA9rf9LvlvVD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Vertigo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0052357</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Vertigo</title>
	<year>1958</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A retired San Francisco detective suffering from acrophobia investigates the strange activities of an old friend's wife, all the while becoming dangerously obsessed with her.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/15uOEfqBNTVtDUT7hGBVCka0rZz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/77aHwg1SCy89rfvQtiruPU58qEV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Great Escape[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0057115</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Great Escape</title>
	<year>1963</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The Nazis, exasperated at the number of escapes from their prison camps by a relatively small number of Allied prisoners, relocate them to a high-security 'escape-proof' camp to sit out the remainder of the war. Undaunted, the prisoners plan one of the most ambitious escape attempts of World War II. Based on a true story.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gBH4H8UMFxl139HaLz6lRuvsel8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1pz4ZArUTM1jrpR6XkYuDlEQncG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]High Noon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0044706</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>High Noon</title>
	<year>1952</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Will Kane, the sheriff of a small town in New Mexico, learns a notorious outlaw he put in jail has been freed, and will be arriving on the noon train. Knowing the outlaw and his gang are coming to kill him, Kane is determined to stand his ground, so he attempts to gather a posse from among the local townspeople.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bc1x6kIO9oF30y3IMFuKMJV2uOj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6S4gjpkd359UuMLfrnUV1M695DF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]A Clockwork Orange[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0066921</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Clockwork Orange</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In a near-future Britain, young Alexander DeLarge and his pals get their kicks beating and raping anyone they please. When not destroying the lives of others, Alex swoons to the music of Beethoven. The state, eager to crack down on juvenile crime, gives an incarcerated Alex the option to undergo an invasive procedure that'll rob him of all personal agency. In a time when conscience is a commodity, can Alex change his tune?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4sHeTAp65WrSSuc05nRBKddhBxO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bR4U9n9YnZOvBUhOUNl316UNEyh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Taxi Driver[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075314</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Taxi Driver</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A mentally unstable Vietnam War veteran works as a night-time taxi driver in New York City where the perceived decadence and sleaze feed his urge for violent action.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ekstpH614fwDX8DUln1a2Opz0N8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bjY8I16jze9XWVwpWXxOhB0oysS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Lawrence of Arabia[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056172</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lawrence of Arabia</title>
	<year>1962</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The story of British officer T.E. Lawrence's mission to aid the Arab tribes in their revolt against the Ottoman Empire during the First World War. Lawrence becomes a flamboyant, messianic figure in the cause of Arab unity but his psychological instability threatens to undermine his achievements.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AiAm0EtDvyGqNpVoieRw4u65vD1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mx2jS5Kaa5rmaldEFzKeKpDN9Q2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Double Indemnity[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0036775</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Double Indemnity</title>
	<year>1944</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A rich woman and a calculating insurance agent plot to kill her unsuspecting husband after he signs a double indemnity policy. Against a backdrop of distinctly Californian settings, the partners in crime plan the perfect murder to collect the insurance, which pays double if the death is accidental.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kkfKLeOTo7RjS9TxHKpknlL7huS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u546kDNwrZ1ii6q8NqqQgHwRvoW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Titanic[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120338</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Titanic</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>101-year-old Rose DeWitt Bukater tells the story of her life aboard the Titanic, 84 years later. A young Rose boards the ship with her mother and fiancé. Meanwhile, Jack Dawson and Fabrizio De Rossi win third-class tickets aboard the ship. Rose tells the whole story from Titanic's departure through to its death—on its first and last voyage—on April 15, 1912.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9xjZS2rlVxm8SFx8kPC3aIGCOYQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rzdPqYx7Um4FUZeD8wpXqjAUcEm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Maltese Falcon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0033870</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Maltese Falcon</title>
	<year>1941</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A private detective takes on a case that involves him with three eccentric criminals, a beautiful liar, and their quest for a priceless statuette.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bf4o6Uzw5wqLjdKwRuiDrN1xyvl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5lMm0MmAviP6DF45nxBVOT9LCwK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Star Wars[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0076759</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Wars</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Princess Leia is captured and held hostage by the evil Imperial forces in their effort to take over the galactic Empire. Venturesome Luke Skywalker and dashing captain Han Solo team together with the loveable robot duo R2-D2 and C-3PO to rescue the beautiful princess and restore peace and justice in the Empire.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6FfCtAuVAW8XJjZ7eWeLibRLWTw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aDYSnJAK0BTVeE8osOy22Kz3SXY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Fatal Attraction[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093010</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fatal Attraction</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>For Dan Gallagher, life is good. He is on the rise at his New York law firm, is happily married to his wife, Beth, and has a loving daughter. But, after a casual fling with a sultry book editor named Alex, everything changes. Jilted by Dan, Alex becomes unstable, her behavior escalating from aggressive pursuit to obsessive stalking. Dan realizes that his main problem is not hiding his affair, but rather saving himself and his family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6QWziDIbcVVpnTGuaKjcxXC9Kl4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x286ZITKvbohZakhcnxuUIyFeu5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Shining[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0081505</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Shining</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Jack Torrance accepts a caretaker job at the Overlook Hotel, where he, along with his wife Wendy and their son Danny, must live isolated from the rest of the world for the winter. But they aren't prepared for the madness that lurks within.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nRj5511mZdTl4saWEPoj9QroTIu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mmd1HnuvAzFc4iuVJcnBrhDNEKr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Deer Hunter[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0077416</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Deer Hunter</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A group of working-class friends decide to enlist in the Army during the Vietnam War and finds it to be hellish chaos -- not the noble venture they imagined. Before they left, Steven married his pregnant girlfriend -- and Michael and Nick were in love with the same woman. But all three are different men upon their return.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bbGtogDZOg09bm42KIpCXUXICkh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pCClmlbgfg4cEmn5aERxHRqhbpw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Close Encounters of the Third Kind[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075860</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Close Encounters of the Third Kind</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After an encounter with UFOs, an electricity linesman feels undeniably drawn to an isolated area in the wilderness where something spectacular is about to happen.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4zfedS25uMAhgm6YQhc9bhKHbLl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u9ZLyLvqHY5VDjn0Rs4LKAklsAV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Strangers on a Train[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0044079</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Strangers on a Train</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A deranged socialite accosts a tennis star with his theory that if two strangers trade murders, they can disguise their motives and avoid suspicion.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ihC083U7ef56Ui4x0P0dobojrZ1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dHW7uUcDKLrHYhoG9dpdYdSi5aF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Fugitive[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106977</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fugitive</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Wrongfully convicted of murdering his wife and sentenced to death, Richard Kimble escapes from the law in an attempt to find the real killer and clear his name.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b3rEtLKyOnF89mcK75GXDXdmOEf.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sdylVXKmMZb5nCRJiMUwfDzVDQJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Night of the Hunter[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0048424</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Night of the Hunter</title>
	<year>1955</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the Deep South, a serial-killing preacher hunts two young children who know the whereabouts of a stash of money.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rBka0nFWiHxabHRLr0KfIA8Yiaq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4hYxesnrRHiFLo1rctaKtzBiMvW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Jurassic Park[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107290</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Jurassic Park</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A wealthy entrepreneur secretly creates a theme park featuring living dinosaurs drawn from prehistoric DNA. Before opening day, he invites a team of experts and his two eager grandchildren to experience the park and help calm anxious investors. However, the park is anything but amusing as the security systems go off-line and the dinosaurs escape.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oU7Oq2kFAAlGqbU4VoAE36g4hoI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1FN6pHFDDlhT7oVhABKKGtG6ga7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Bullitt[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0062765</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bullitt</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Senator Walter Chalmers is aiming to take down mob boss Pete Ross with the help of testimony from the criminal's hothead brother Johnny, who is in protective custody in San Francisco under the watch of police lieutenant Frank Bullitt. When a pair of mob hitmen enter the scene, Bullitt follows their trail through a maze of complications and double-crosses. This thriller includes one of the most famous car chases ever filmed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uDg7tHvK8aFcG6DkN5eHiZAurOU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wu0Ad30NciUbR5c5Q1AglHZbRWJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Casablanca[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0034583</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Casablanca</title>
	<year>1942</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In Casablanca, Morocco in December 1941, a cynical American expatriate meets a former lover, with unforeseen complications.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5K7cOHoay2mZusSLezBOY0Qxh8a.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wOfzdzC0QZyhUIlyjeMuUYSb8Ax.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Notorious[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0038787</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Notorious</title>
	<year>1946</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In order to help bring Nazis to justice, U.S. government agent T.R. Devlin recruits Alicia Huberman, the American daughter of a convicted German war criminal, as a spy. As they begin to fall for one another, Alicia is instructed to win the affections of Alexander Sebastian, a Nazi hiding out in Brazil. When Sebastian becomes serious about his relationship with Alicia, the stakes get higher, and Devlin must watch her slip further undercover.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4RERYb1NIQrJHYY5e8nUlYM7t2z.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9K8MWPiEVNV1FkxiVTV0HuZvNfa.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Die Hard[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0095016</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>NYPD cop John McClane's plan to reconcile with his estranged wife is thrown for a serious loop when, minutes after he arrives at her office, the entire building is overtaken by a group of terrorists. With little help from the LAPD, wisecracking McClane sets out to single-handedly rescue the hostages and bring the bad guys down.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yFihWxQcmqcaBR31QM6Y8gT6aYV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rahJyvdMruvqUmSLWRQKYS57mx8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]2001: A Space Odyssey[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0062622</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>2001: A Space Odyssey</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Humanity finds a mysterious object buried beneath the lunar surface and sets off to find its origins with the help of HAL 9000, the world's most advanced super computer.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ve72VxNqjGM69Uky4WTo2bK6rfq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kCEXA22ASuq7Y29jnngyaisyA0X.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dirty Harry[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0066999</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dirty Harry</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a madman dubbed 'Scorpio' terrorizes San Francisco, hard-nosed cop, Harry Callahan – famous for his take-no-prisoners approach to law enforcement – is tasked with hunting down the psychopath. Harry eventually collars Scorpio in the process of rescuing a kidnap victim, only to see him walk on technicalities. Now, the maverick detective is determined to nail the maniac himself.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/UHxxkYe9tRdiPu0JFgcEL5hmQ4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ezrb56YdkoG59fZj50IxE9OnADx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Terminator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088247</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Terminator</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the post-apocalyptic future, reigning tyrannical supercomputers teleport a cyborg assassin known as the "Terminator" back to 1984 to kill Sarah Connor, whose unborn son is destined to lead insurgents against 21st century mechanical hegemony. Meanwhile, the human-resistance movement dispatches a lone warrior to safeguard Sarah. Can he stop the virtually indestructible killing machine?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvktm0BHcnmDpul4Hz01GIazWPr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wh4ze6klUbeichAj603OKZwY1W5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Wizard of Oz[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0032138</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wizard of Oz</title>
	<year>1939</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Young Dorothy finds herself in a magical world where she makes friends with a lion, a scarecrow and a tin man as they make their way along the yellow brick road to talk with the Wizard and ask for the things they miss most in their lives. The Wicked Witch of the West is the only thing that could stop them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bSA6DbAC5gdkaooU164lQUX6rVs.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zL4gtCeoPZkAFCKR0kNERpUiuPR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083866</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An alien is left behind on Earth and saved by the 10-year-old Elliot who decides to keep him hidden in his home. While a task force hunts for the extra-terrestrial, Elliot, his brother, and his little sister Gertie form an emotional bond with their new friend, and try to help him find his way home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/an0nD6uq6byfxXCfk6lQBzdL2J1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mXLVA0YL6tcXi6SJSuAh9ONXFj5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Saving Private Ryan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120815</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Saving Private Ryan</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As U.S. troops storm the beaches of Normandy, three brothers lie dead on the battlefield, with a fourth trapped behind enemy lines. Ranger captain John Miller and seven men are tasked with penetrating German-held territory and bringing the boy home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1wY4psJ5NVEhCuOYROwLH2XExM2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bdD39MpSVhKjxarTxLSfX6baoMP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Carrie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0074285</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Carrie</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Carrie White, a shy and troubled teenage girl who is tormented by her high school peers and her fanatically religious mother, begins to use her powers of telekinesis to exact revenge upon them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uc3OvgmbnYaS5Y0BOjSmC1EmSz1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kVthdQuL0lU51pjK4C4jlnRGsRe.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Invasion of the Body Snatchers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0049366</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Invasion of the Body Snatchers</title>
	<year>1956</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A small-town doctor learns that the population of his community is being replaced by emotionless alien duplicates.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8BrMQmgwGzIHSyBjCDOLOdi79fJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1qG8TfiE5mCMdaqrFioaGmhBrpY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dial M for Murder[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0046912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dial M for Murder</title>
	<year>1954</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An ex-tennis pro carries out a plot to have his wife murdered after discovering she is having an affair, and assumes she will soon leave him for the other man anyway. When things go wrong, he improvises a new plan—to frame her for murder instead.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4KKiFDvtEusJzqzlwHp7iMceXKS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uFZdPBbtJOJfuowufvpdVzhfyIw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Ben-Hur[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0052618</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ben-Hur</title>
	<year>1959</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In 25 AD,Judah Ben-Hur, a Jew in ancient Judea, opposes the occupying Roman empire.  Falsely accused by a Roman childhood friend-turned-overlord of trying to kill the Roman governor, he is put into slavery and his mother and sister are taken away as prisoners.  Three years later and freed by a grateful Roman galley commander whom he has rescued from drowning, he becomes an expert charioteer for Rome, all the while plotting to return to Judea, find and rescue his family, and avenge himself on his former friend.  All the while, the form and work of Jesus move in the background of his life...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m4WQ1dBIrEIHZNCoAjdpxwSKWyH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sU3gFo7Gn67zjtKXIvzJ4omcUbH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Marathon Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0074860</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Marathon Man</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A graduate student and obsessive runner in New York is drawn into a mysterious plot involving his brother, a member of the secretive Division.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uPNgubSiri2yvBQRPtP77ViYjN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t3j3HwSgOcpKHDg5CaYE4WnPQDC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Raging Bull[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0081398</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Raging Bull</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The life of boxer Jake LaMotta, whose violence and temper that led him to the top in the ring destroyed his life outside of it.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rEviyDWNbAFmvvCPlkMRPAGUElG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wgq2oA1aJiawBlRDIU8agXk7DQQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rocky[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075148</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rocky</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When world heavyweight boxing champion, Apollo Creed wants to give an unknown fighter a shot at the title as a publicity stunt, his handlers choose palooka Rocky Balboa, an uneducated collector for a Philadelphia loan shark. Rocky teams up with trainer  Mickey Goldmill to make the most of this once in a lifetime break.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hEjK9A9BkNXejFW4tfacVAEHtkn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yPgAHVzCF0yJGhxupwVwknOHdJj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Pulp Fiction[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0110912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pulp Fiction</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A burger-loving hit man, his philosophical partner, a drug-addled gangster's moll and a washed-up boxer converge in this sprawling, comedic crime caper. Their adventures unfurl in three stories that ingeniously trip back and forth in time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d5iIlFn5s0ImszYzBPb8JPIfbXD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/suaEOtk1N1sgg2MTM7oZd2cfVp3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0064115</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid</title>
	<year>1969</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In late 1890s Wyoming, Butch Cassidy is the affable, clever and talkative leader of the outlaw Hole in the Wall Gang. His closest companion is the laconic dead-shot Sundance Kid. As the west rapidly becomes civilized, the law finally catches up to Butch, Sundance and their gang.  Chased doggedly by a special posse, the two decide to make their way to South America in hopes of evading their pursuers once and for all.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gFmmykF1Ym3OGzENo50nZQaD1dx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/C6jcUqld8M6hZQmzBxgwHuQ4qT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Wait Until Dark[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0062467</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Wait Until Dark</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>After a flight back home, Sam Hendrix returns with a doll he innocently acquired along the way. As it turns out, the doll is actually stuffed with heroin, and a group of criminals led by the ruthless Roat has followed Hendrix back to his place to retrieve it. When Hendrix leaves for business, the crooks make their move -- and find his blind wife, Susy, alone in the apartment. Soon, a life-threatening game begins between Susy and the thugs.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8WJOL49WakZcV3JIcIyl8vYq3mw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ckBanU1PZ4Vo5oDDQoWKjSVwE4T.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Frankenstein[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0021884</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Frankenstein</title>
	<year>1931</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Dr. Henry Frankenstein attempts to create life by assembling a creature from body parts of the deceased. Aided by his loyal misshapen assistant, Fritz, Frankenstein succeeds in animating his monster, but, confused and traumatized, it escapes into the countryside and begins to wreak havoc. Frankenstein searches for the elusive being and eventually must confront his tormented creation.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gKaSFyd6HMTkXqU3UVVNWhVUiiO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tyGLg0Tw7xZPgnuR2ctjCNgbjlF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]All the President's Men[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0074119</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>All the President's Men</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>During the 1972 elections, two reporters' investigation sheds light on the controversial Watergate scandal that compels President Nixon to resign from his post.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cPtSHR7D2WGsDBfnC5DxV927hKn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvLjTAwwQTcAiYXxnGaXctlqUJ6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Bridge on the River Kwai[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0050212</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Bridge on the River Kwai</title>
	<year>1957</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The classic story of English POWs in Burma forced to build a bridge to aid the war effort of their Japanese captors. British and American intelligence officers conspire to blow up the structure, but Col. Nicholson , the commander who supervised the bridge's construction, has acquired a sense of pride in his creation and tries to foil their plans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7paXMt2e3Tr5dLmEZOGgFEn2Vo7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cX4xeWZ0DebcpFoxCXeKbBOZQs4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Planet of the Apes[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063442</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Planet of the Apes</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Astronaut Taylor crash lands on a distant planet ruled by apes who use a primitive race of humans for experimentation and sport. Soon Taylor finds himself among the hunted, his life in the hands of a benevolent chimpanzee scientist.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2r9iKnlSYEk4daQadsXfcjHfIjQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dQS3L3USI7Zhcq41abzMZF8dXCm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Sixth Sense[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0167404</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Sixth Sense</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Following an unexpected tragedy, a child psychologist named Malcolm Crowe meets an nine year old boy named Cole Sear, who is hiding a dark secret.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4AfSDjjCy6T5LA1TMz0Lh2HlpRh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/paUKxrbN2ww0JeT2JtvgAuaGlPf.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Cape Fear[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0055824</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Cape Fear</title>
	<year>1962</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Sam Bowden witnesses a rape committed by Max Cady and testifies against him. When released after 8 years in prison, Cady begins stalking Bowden and his family but is always clever enough not to violate the law.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9BzUTJMoH1mQUiqI1C9glrWEuxa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gTAR1VR3KSLEp5jIFuOQbZeiBrB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Spartacus[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054331</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spartacus</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The rebellious Thracian Spartacus, born and raised a slave, is sold to Gladiator trainer Batiatus. After weeks of being trained to kill for the arena, Spartacus turns on his owners and leads the other slaves in rebellion. As the rebels move from town to town, their numbers swell as escaped slaves join their ranks. Under the leadership of Spartacus, they make their way to southern Italy, where they will cross the sea and return to their homes.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/biaUMHb8xsdQHlEF6rHmlKxSARy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aheSIG4h3JNxWeDvdb1NxKzgjaM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]What Ever Happened to Baby Jane?[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056687</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>What Ever Happened to Baby Jane?</title>
	<year>1962</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A former child star torments her paraplegic sister in their decaying Hollywood mansion.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/msGYzyWwtjAaA3DScdgmvJ5MReG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gkXL5ka6ciU4A4KYSvLIAXtvh7k.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Touch of Evil[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0052311</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Touch of Evil</title>
	<year>1958</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a car bomb explodes on the American side of the U.S./Mexico border, Mexican drug enforcement agent Miguel Vargas begins his investigation, along with American police captain Hank Quinlan. When Vargas begins to suspect that Quinlan and his shady partner, Menzies, are planting evidence to frame an innocent man, his investigations into their possible corruption quickly put himself and his new bride, Susie, in jeopardy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1pvRgmfBaoMczIJBOi9gCOZ4FMC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vZBHQfRbBZNsFbqw3B6MQPOa8S6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Dirty Dozen[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0061578</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Dirty Dozen</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>12 American military prisoners in World War II are ordered to infiltrate a well-guarded enemy château and kill the Nazi officers vacationing there. The soldiers, most of whom are facing death sentences for a variety of violent crimes, agree to the mission and the possible commuting of their sentences.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iFpgjfE4gt7guOLvrqgZZoO4Rjk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ccegwWa7I2vxxaoXrGB8Wl1g5nl.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Matrix[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0133093</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Matrix</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Set in the 22nd century, The Matrix tells the story of a computer hacker who joins a group of underground insurgents fighting the vast and powerful computers who now rule the earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f89U3ADr1oiB1s9GkdPOEpXUk5H.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/waCRuAW5ocONRehP556vPexVXA9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Treasure of the Sierra Madre[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0040897</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Treasure of the Sierra Madre</title>
	<year>1948</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Fred C. Dobbs and Bob Curtin, both down on their luck in Tampico, Mexico in 1925, meet up with a grizzled prospector named Howard and decide to join with him in search of gold in the wilds of central Mexico. Through enormous difficulties, they eventually succeed in finding gold, but bandits, the elements, and most especially greed threaten to turn their success into disaster.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pWcst7zVbi8Z8W6GFrdNE7HHRxL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sj5R5SGor3YMFBuabMj8gPbyBmh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Halloween[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0077651</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Halloween</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Fifteen years after murdering his sister on Halloween Night 1963, Michael Myers escapes from a mental hospital and returns to the small town of Haddonfield, Illinois to kill again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wijlZ3HaYMvlDTPqJoTCWKFkCPU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2iCHBuCExV7dHovb6hG9b5zsqBU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Wild Bunch[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0065214</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wild Bunch</title>
	<year>1969</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An aging group of outlaws look for one last big score as the "traditional" American West is disappearing around them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8j9yEC3xjy1PJDSizIbaxcHaSph.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3VOMg5qurrIGoZrg3cfbxhEW5Ye.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dog Day Afternoon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0072890</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dog Day Afternoon</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Based on the true story of would-be Brooklyn bank robbers John Wojtowicz and Salvatore Naturale. Sonny and Sal attempt a bank heist which quickly turns sour and escalates into a hostage situation and stand-off with the police. As Sonny's motives for the robbery are slowly revealed and things become more complicated, the heist turns into a media circus.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mavrhr0ig2aCRR8d48yaxtD5aMQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m10uqk0HI5JcITAbxNJIIiGA8HP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Goldfinger[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0058150</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Goldfinger</title>
	<year>1964</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Special agent 007 comes face to face with one of the most notorious villains of all time, and now he must outwit and outgun the powerful tycoon to prevent him from cashing in on a devious scheme to raid Fort Knox -- and obliterate the world's economy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6fTzum7gSpLWww26WvWjETNqfD9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lh65Y0sUQcRh5UVVgnTOfMUbN2c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Platoon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091763</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Platoon</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>As a young and naive recruit in Vietnam, Chris Taylor faces a moral crisis when confronted with the horrors of war and the duality of man.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8hDlxJZYCJJLRHbSk7hsRQ9SNp7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2WZLSN9cdHCkJFbkj0oMfOfVHn8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Laura[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0037008</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Laura</title>
	<year>1944</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A police detective falls in love with the woman whose murder he's investigating.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AtZFZSLN3rSMxTQYN9LRpQzDOgh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qmYT05tR9mfsUHD07MXw0o0zcfx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blade Runner[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083658</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blade Runner</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the smog-choked dystopian Los Angeles of 2019, blade runner Rick Deckard is called out of retirement to terminate a quartet of replicants who have escaped to Earth seeking their creator for a way to extend their short life spans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/63N9uy8nd9j7Eog2axPQ8lbr3Wj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wfQTVBIQj1wJUe0jV3OZ4zOivIO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Third Man[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0041959</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Third Man</title>
	<year>1949</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In postwar Vienna, Austria, Holly Martins, a writer of pulp Westerns, arrives penniless as a guest of his childhood chum Harry Lime, only to learn he has died. Martins develops a conspiracy theory after learning of a "third man" present at the time of Harry's death, running into interference from British officer Major Calloway, and falling head-over-heels for Harry's grief-stricken lover, Anna.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oIF3l7Dxp7Eyye10BNyM611wtKa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mYI1VlxvuSnHoK6GYwkFzAgcJXh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Thelma & Louise[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103074</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Thelma & Louise</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Whilst on a short weekend getaway, Louise shoots a man who had tried to rape Thelma. Due to the incriminating circumstances, they make a run for it and thus a cross country chase ensues for the two fugitives. Along the way, both women rediscover the strength of their friendship and surprising aspects of their personalities and self-strengths in the trying times.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gQSUVGR80RVHxJywtwXm2qa1ebi.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h682VsV5eIo5Ek50rDt7srYXFm4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Terminator 2: Judgment Day[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103064</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Nearly 10 years have passed since Sarah Connor was targeted for termination by a cyborg from the future. Now her son, John, the future leader of the resistance, is the target for a newer, more deadly terminator. Once again, the resistance has managed to send a protector back to attempt to save John and his mother Sarah.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5M0j0B18abtBI5gi2RhfjjurTqb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xKb6mtdfI5Qsggc44Hr9CCUDvaj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Gaslight[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0036855</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Gaslight</title>
	<year>1944</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A newlywed fears she's going mad when strange things start happening at the family mansion.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gXKszCl5Q1KrgWRWpPcqn94CP58.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fEVYmqXuD9iqesoYexOTHSGXIWK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Magnificent Seven[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054047</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Magnificent Seven</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An oppressed Mexican peasant village hires seven gunfighters to help defend their homes.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e5ToxOyJwuZD4VOfI0qEn5uIjeJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2aC3284N1p86o6S4Uyj9AaryYeR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Rebecca[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0032976</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rebecca</title>
	<year>1940</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Story of a young woman who marries a fascinating widower only to find out that she must live in the shadow of his former wife, Rebecca, who died mysteriously several years earlier. The young wife must come to grips with the terrible secret of her handsome, cold husband, Max De Winter. She must also deal with the jealous, obsessed Mrs. Danvers, the housekeeper, who will not accept her as the mistress of the house.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oagejoHmaDRMUo7MpEaihmNohFW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jKgLVAhoq4fXBs1C9Gjvap93fxd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Omen[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075005</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Omen</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Immediately after their miscarriage, the US diplomat Robert Thorn adopts the newborn Damien without the knowledge of his wife. Yet what he doesn’t know is that their new son is the son of the devil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p0LcWxOIoBx0MEZMn8tFcrvDXR1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gw9vOHSYDEuKcNKgQWS2iePcfjk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Day the Earth Stood Still[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0043456</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day the Earth Stood Still</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>An alien and a robot land on Earth after World War II and tell mankind to be peaceful or face destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x2DquTpLTq54aPFDnqlwY7apCC3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3cxXe9mLoMiIeBxvjRh4lcC2TuK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Phantom of the Opera[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0016220</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Phantom of the Opera</title>
	<year>1925</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A grotesquely disfigured composer known as "The Phantom" haunts Paris' opera house, where he's secretly grooming Christine Daae to be an opera diva. Luring her to his remote underground lair, The Phantom declares his love. But Christine loves Raoul de Chagny and plans to elope with him. When The Phantom learns this, he abducts Christine.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mvaYpAYj957C2tlq3vVJPSzGJXK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6FSs7jMimg1PBYdhZtPNQhtKtEc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Poltergeist[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084516</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Poltergeist</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Steve Freeling lives with his wife, Diane, and their three children, Dana, Robbie, and Carol Anne, in Southern California where he sells houses for the company that built the neighborhood. It starts with just a few odd occurrences, such as broken dishes and furniture moving around by itself. However, when he realizes that something truly evil haunts his home, Steve calls in a team of parapsychologists led by Dr. Lesh to help before it's too late.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xPazCcKp62IshnLVf9BLAjf9vgC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bvkPno6U02lLyvPWCnmibq4eIaN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Dracula[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0021814</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dracula</title>
	<year>1931</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>British estate agent Renfield travels to Transylvania to meet with the mysterious Count Dracula, who is interested in leasing a castle in London and is, unbeknownst to Renfield, a vampire. After Dracula enslaves Renfield and drives him to insanity, the pair sail to London together, and as Dracula begins preying on London socialites, the two become the subject of study for a supernaturalist professor, Abraham Van Helsing.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ueVSPt7vAba0XScHWTDWS5tNxYX.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cemjdP7HrUyJAry85vRT19Hidbi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Picture of Dorian Gray[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0037988</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Picture of Dorian Gray</title>
	<year>1945</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Posing for a portrait, Dorian Gray talks with Lord Henry Wotton, who says that men should pursue their sensual longings, but laments that only the young get to do so. Taken with the idea, Dorian imagines a scenario in which the painting will age as he stays youthful. His wish comes true, and his boyish looks aid him as he indulges his every whim. But when a stunning revelation forces him to see what he's become, Dorian faces some very dangerous questions.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mfvcsmAzdie8YuWI0JpO2u1uzfF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hBwvoggQOzAODHRYInZA60qtR7h.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Thing from Another World[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0044121</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Thing from Another World</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Scientists and US Air Force officials fend off a blood-thirsty alien organism while investigating at a remote arctic outpost.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rm2w8dEhOGDuckB6i0Spz9lTzpR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/30aHDHSHGX4HEeKlrgCwhTU72QP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]12 Angry Men[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0050083</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>12 Angry Men</title>
	<year>1957</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The defense and the prosecution have rested and the jury is filing into the jury room to decide if a young Spanish-American is guilty or innocent of murdering his father. What begins as an open and shut case soon becomes a mini-drama of each of the jurors' prejudices and preconceptions about the trial, the accused, and each other.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ppd84D2i9W8jXmsyInGyihiSyqz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qqHQsStV6exghCM7zbObuYBiYxw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Guns of Navarone[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054953</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Guns of Navarone</title>
	<year>1961</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A team of allied saboteurs are assigned an impossible mission: infiltrate an impregnable Nazi-held island and destroy the two enormous long-range field guns that prevent the rescue of 2,000 trapped British soldiers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rBnNHKhSHFuac0I6qPYiVLJ6ohy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AsBJ7JjNR7wcONrfkUW027C8D5c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Poseidon Adventure[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0069113</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Poseidon Adventure</title>
	<year>1972</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When their ocean liner capsizes, a group of passengers struggle to survive and escape.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6RGiA5BfhelU9zoD0b1GAG4GWWf.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v1QEIuBM1vvpvfqalahhIyXY0Cm.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Braveheart[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0112573</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Braveheart</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Enraged at the slaughter of Murron, his new bride and childhood love, Scottish warrior William Wallace slays a platoon of the local English lord's soldiers. This leads the village to revolt and, eventually, the entire country to rise up against English rule.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/or1gBugydmjToAEq7OZY0owwFk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vXhTr0cN54R0TbSD9iG5cuAEWcT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Body Heat[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0082089</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Body Heat</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>In the midst of a searing Florida heat wave, a woman convinces her lover, a small-town lawyer, to murder her rich husband.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rpD7tjNhyAuShm2mOiaJixMyxkk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o8wqyVw3s31vXVWG4R8Gd4Twail.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Night of the Living Dead[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063350</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Night of the Living Dead</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A disparate group of individuals takes refuge in an abandoned house when corpses begin to leave the graveyard in search of fresh human bodies to devour. The pragmatic Ben does his best to control the situation, but when the murderous zombies surround the house, the other survivors begin to panic.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b6yJXwYAXgqJKNdOrEQxxbQ8oG4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d0NwvSRJQQzkubWKsidX4caQ6Yi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The China Syndrome[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0078966</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The China Syndrome</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>While doing a series of reports on alternative energy sources, opportunistic reporter Kimberly Wells witnesses an accident at a nuclear power plant. Wells is determined to publicize the incident, but soon finds herself entangled in a sinister conspiracy to keep the full impact of the incident a secret.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uHwwQIlt4XwpTFhX9ZT1A8xSW7F.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvlSLwRbTw0bY0fJmsRxzbnRHyt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Full Metal Jacket[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093058</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Full Metal Jacket</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>A pragmatic U.S. Marine observes the dehumanizing effects the U.S.-Vietnam War has on his fellow recruits from their brutal boot camp training to the bloody street fighting in Hue.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kMKyx1k8hWWscYFnPbnxxN4Eqo4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yozBWKbyeXtPGN75PlHurOaVvEz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blue Velvet[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090756</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blue Velvet</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The discovery of a severed human ear found in a field leads a young man on an investigation related to a beautiful, mysterious nightclub singer and a group of criminals who have kidnapped her child.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7hlgzJXLgyECS1mk3LSN3E72l5N.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vB5hoogPuLO5Hpbb63c8yFB7WPf.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Safety Last![/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0014429</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Safety Last!</title>
	<year>1923</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>When a store clerk organizes a contest to climb the outside of a tall building, circumstances force him to make the perilous climb himself.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fycYVsLKJLiZ324236pvBQMeW7A.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oC6EnuxAE4ZR15rUPqV5nFNCLLB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Blood Simple[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086979</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Blood Simple</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>The owner of a seedy small-town Texas bar discovers that one of his employees is having an affair with his wife. A chaotic chain of misunderstandings, lies and mischief ensues after he devises a plot to have them murdered.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n8D1gVXUgmW4kkDzUzzoezAmUUa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rGPoNNk4fvgG2mvkNAxJJPlszOu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]Speed[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0111257</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Speed</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Los Angeles SWAT cop Jack Traven is up against bomb expert Howard Payne, who's after major ransom money. First it's a rigged elevator in a very tall building. Then it's a rigged bus--if it slows, it will blow, bad enough any day, but a nightmare in LA traffic. And that's still not the end.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xKxYPmN4ZVHbNbmgm1ya2ivBn2P.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bWjvYgY2kfhnfzvEDk96yiCz2oJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=white]The Adventures of Robin Hood[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0029843</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Adventures of Robin Hood</title>
	<year>1938</year>
	</meta>
	<link>search</link>
	
	
	
	<summary>Robin Hood fights nobly for justice against the evil Sir Guy of Gisbourne while striving to win the hand of the beautiful Maid Marian.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c7LX3GMf9uXQTgVm3uxpm7E6Woc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h8uoKyYoNfgrb5gf4Nddh5Y2UNp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
